[JO1 & JAM 2nd Birthday Party Eve]
Hey everyone, calm down
Let's do our greeting first
Ready, go
Go to the Top, it's JO1!
Today, we JO1, thanks to JAM
Are able to have our 2nd anniversary!
[JO1 turns 2!!!!]
Yay! Thank you!
It's so fast
2 years have passed so fast!
In a blink of an eye
This 1 year passed so fast
It did
What was your top memory of this year?
Our live concert
- Right
- It must be our live, after all
Since we were able to meet JAM in person
The best memory
Do you remember what day it is tomorrow?
Of course, that's a given
Shall we say it on the count of 3?
Yes, let's
Here we go, ready, go!
JAM DAY!
[JAM, Happy 2nd Anniversary!]
Today, let's prepare for JO1 & JAM's 2nd anniversary party!
[JO1 & JAM 2nd Birthday Party Eve]
We are going to make a cake & put up decorations
We shall split into 2 teams to do it
Firstly, who wants to make the cake?
I want to!
Oh, that's great
When it comes to cooking, it's me!
No that's wrong
It's me
When it comes to eating, it's me! (?)
That's not what it's about
Can I be in charge of cooking as well?
Sure, it's true that for cooking-
It's perfect
Yeah, perfectly-
[Wall]
Takumi: Why??
Then these 5 will make the cake
[Ren, Syoya, Junki, Shion, Sho]
Yes!
Sho: And the remaining 5 will decorate-
Keigo: Sleep
Keigo: Ah, decorate?
Sho: Don't sleep
Ren: Don't rest
Shion: Why are you resting?
Clean up the room!
I think it already looks nice though
It's already nice, but make it even nicer
Keigo: Okay
Shosei: Leave it to us
Let's do our best
Then, let's start work!
[Cake making group]
JO1 cooking!
Today, we'll like to make a delicious cake
with these ingredients prepared for us
I look forward to working together
Before we start cooking, we have to wash our hands
So let's wash our hands before we start
[First, let's clean our hands!]
Sho: That's great~
Hold on, let me try this once
Right, check the freshness
[Nom]
- It's fine
- It's fine?
Go wash your hands again
[In-charge of fresh cream]
The first topsoil work
Be careful
Shion, I think it's slanting downwards
Ah, it's going down here
Oh no! x3
Here
[PASS to Syoya]
Leave it to me
That's quick!
Ren: Syoya you're good at this!
Shion: You're good!
Syoya: At home I cut a block of raw ham, so...
As expected
[Skillful]
Whoa!! Wow!!
Look at this cross section!
It's here! x3
[Fresh cream is coming along well]
Wow!
It smells great
[Concentrating]
[It's Shion]
[Searching for a tasting spoon]
Sho-kun, is this ok?
This is all they have
[Super huge spoon!?]
That would finish everything
Junki, taste it
How is the taste?
Itadakimasu
Yummy
No! Please wash your hands
[Store Manager Shion who is picky about cleanliness]
[On the other hand, how is the decoration team doing?]
With this, we shall...
Take it easy
We're having a party, so...
A party-like...
A cute, exciting, party room
Shall we start?
[Party decoration team starts work too!]
Isn't this awesome?
That's scary! Stop it! That's scary!
Keigo-kun is the best at decorating
Okay, how is it?
Keigo-kun & Shosei seem good at it
I will be assisting them
Let's make the surrounding of the table cute too
Ohira will work on it
[Tall Keigo concentrates on the decorations above]
Leave the balloons to me!
[Decoration team steadily progresses]
Mame-chan?
- What is it?
- Where should this go?
'What is it?' (LOL)
[Putting the donut balloon on the wall too]
- I'll put it?
- Okay
I'm putting it
Wow!
Junki: Syoya, spread it out
[Spreading the fresh cream on the sponge]
It's like this
You're good
[Spreading the fresh cream on the sponge]
Turn the bottom
It's good!
It's beautiful
You're good at this, seriously
[Putting fruit]
I'll put it on
[Put another layer of sponge above]
Wow! Looks like the real deal!
It's a hamburger!
[Ren is in-charge of toppings:
Making 'JAM & JO1' with strawberries]
It's cute
[Both teams progressing smoothly]
Is there something like a heart?
There is x2
I wanna put it in the middle
Here
[The essential ♥ between JAM & JO1]
Isn't it nice?
[Super satisfied]
[Decorate Ruki too~!]
With this, it's done
It suits you
There we go
[Polaroid time]
I want to put it somewhere it's easily seen
[Shosei goes to take picture of the cake making team]
Ohira is going off for a bit~
[Putting up the polaroids]
I'll put these here
That's stylish~
[STAY photo album]
What about this? It's too heavy
It's heavy
Ok, I know
[Enthusiastic]
[Not forgetting to put out the STAY photo album!]
[Lastly, put up the polaroid of everyone]
[Decorations for the party complete!]
[Just a little more for the cake!]
Syoya: Like this?
Sho: Fill it up
Go! Syoya!
[Putting on the strawberry decoration made by Ren]
You can do it
[Decoration on the side of the cake as well]
It's good!
Cute!
[Skillful!]
Ren: Sho-kun is dexterous
He's amazing. Even though his hands are big
[Lastly, topping sugar]
Go crazy with it
It's a little too high (LOL)
That's good
Wow!
Cute
Sho: It has a Christmas feeling
Syoya: Isn't this amazing?
Shion: It's amazing!
[Cake-making complete!]
Complete!
The party decorations and cake is complete!
[Good work with cake-making & decorations!]
Looks yummy! Wow!
- Isn't this epic?
- That's amazing
- Wow
- Looks yummy
Sho: We made it properly
Where was this bought from?
Don't say that! We made it
Everything is homemade
The decorations are amazing too
The photos are amazing
JAM loves JO1
Read the word
- It says 'JAM'
- Yes
And this is...
Eh, wait?
(Counting) ...11!
It's JO1!
We managed to get JO1 and JAM on the same stage
The design is awesome
We have a cake, we have decorations
- It feels like a party, doesn't it!
- Yes!
Today is JO1 & JAM 2nd Anniversary Party Eve!
Tomorrow on JAM day,
we will have party with JAM at real-time!
Great
Well then, shall we cut this?
Shosei: Thank you Junki-kun
Sho: Yes~ We cut it
Ren: Everyone take one~
Shion: Everyone, get your plates
- Happy birthday JO1
- Congrats JAM & JO1
Sho: Strawberry is yummy!
I'll eat the chicken
- Is it yummy?
- Mm!
Takumi: I'm happy!
How's the cake?
The cake is delicious
Mame is done eating too!
Eat the chicken, Mame!
I wanted to eat the chicken
We've finished eating the cake
So let's play UFO catcher
[UFO Catcher
1) One-by-one, come up to get one]
[2) Answer the question or mission inside
3) If time's up, punishment game]
- First, Shion!
- Yes! I'll go with a special attack
Takumi: I wanna watch
Shosei: UFO catcher, wow
This is up
Do your best Shion!
Do your best!~~~
This is down
This is as intense as Koshien
Go Shion!
[Concentrating]
Do your best!!
You can do it!
Press this
Exquisite
What is it?
What is an album concept you'd like to try?
We haven't done it before, the tough kind
- The tough kind
- Yes
Tough
Like with sirens blaring
I want to try something like that
Thank you
You're good at this
Do your best~~
When did a member make your heart race (make you happy)?
Eh~ but...
It seems Shosei wants you to talk about him
Shosei wants me to talk about him...
The members
Make my heart race everyday
[Touched]
I can't pick one
But for Shosei...
When he immediately comes to teach me dance
It makes my heart race
I'm happy
That makes me happy
Takumi is aiming for the macaron
The macaron is difficult
No no! Come back
[Punishment: Express your current feelings by rap]
Time is up!
Yo yo~ What's your feelings yo~
Yo~ Hey~ My feelings now
I have to do this punishment game
You guys got me
Our story that began that day
I won't pass by you
Let's walk this road together forever
[Ears are bright red]
[Takumi is the best]
[Pro UFO catcher appears?!]
Is there a purpose for that?
How is it? Going well?
You were a little early
[Desperate]
Time is up!
Mame's punishment game is 3 types of hearts!
That's easy?!
Mame, we're starting
He's thinking about it
Mame's 3 types of hearts, ready, go!
Oh I've never seen that one before!
That's a diamond
That's the first macaron
[First time the yellow paper appears!]
And it's yellow
- A reward?
- This could be a win!
Keigo has stopped
[No way...]
What's this?
- Hurry up
- This is strange
Why?!
[Punishment: Weird face]
It says weird face
[As he did the weird face with all his might, it can't be shown.
JAM, we seek your understanding <3]
Sho: Time is running out
The earth will be destroyed tomorrow. What do you do?
Eh? Should I talk in depth?
In the normal case, I would eat yummy food
single-mindedly, the whole day
What will you eat?
I like meat, so yakiniku, hamburg, sweets etc.
Without worrying about calories
I will eat all the things I like
Well I guess it's like that after all
How about y'all?
Keigo?
Eh~ I'll probably make a weird face
Lies!
For the whole day?
[Next, Ren GETs it because of course he does]
What?
It's yellow
[Yellow paper again, punishment game is confirmed]
2x speedup dance
[Skillful!]
Wow it's fun just watching
[Successfully completed]
I'll catch a macaron!
Isn't this the smoothest so far?
The most fun MV filming?
So far there's...(everyone listing the MVs)
We filmed STAY too
Then I think I'll go with STAY
We all had barbeque together, it was fun
I choose STAY's MV!
You can do it!
Aren't I good at this?
Favorite hairstyle/hair color during JO1 activities
Can I choose one that I've done but haven't shown?
Before I dyed my hair orange for OEO, my hair was blonde
Blonde
Yes, my blonde & long hair, I want to try it again
- That wasn't shown?
- It wasn't
I thought it was
Thank you!
[Last is Junki]
Oh, time is almost up-
Ohhhh!!
Go go go!
Let me go home
Oh no!
[Capsule got caught at the exit]
Syoya: If you release it you can do it!
Sho: Don't shake it!
Oh no!
[Rescue boat keigo?]
Here...here...
[What is he doing LOL]
[Punishment: Sing as a lion]
[Junki lion - This song is...?]
Keigo: What is it?
Shion: I have no clue~
[Enthusiastic Singing]
Y'ALL KNOW IT, DON'T YOU!!!
You know it!
No one said you could stop
Hurry do it
His face is bright red
[Cry T~T]
We may know it after hearing the rap part
[Burst out laughing]
Y'ALL KNOW IT!!!
Um, please sing the exciting part at the end
You know it...
Let's ask Shosei for the answer
Shosei, the answer is?
Correct
[By the way, this wasn't a quiz showdown ^^;]
[Anyway, thank you Junki <3]
How was the UFO catcher game, everyone?
It was fun, wasn't it?
Yes!
Junki are you ok? You look burnt out
[After-effect of gao gao]
I went all out for the gao gao
It took quite a lot of stamina
Tomorrow may be even more exciting
Everyone, it was a really fun eve party
Thank you very much!
That has been JO1!
See you tomorrow~~!
[Look forward to JO1 & JAM 2nd Birthday Party tomorrow]