Come here!
I'll be going~!
Good morning
I'm still sleepy
Today is my day off after a long while
So I hope you'll stay with me for the day
First of all
It's my morning routine
Shower!
I'll take a quick shower
To wake myself up
Then I'll make some breakfast
Well then see you after shower
Ah by the way the banyan bonsai are also here
[Introducing Okinawa corner]
Chibimaru
Bosumaru
And then Okinawan guardian deity, shisa
Here's my Okinawa corner
I'll take a shower now~
Alright
Before I make my breakfast
I'll put on a BGM
Alright, here I go~
I'm making french toast for today
[SHO's JO1 Kitchen ~French Toast edition~]
(+ Egg)
(+ Milk)
[SHO's JO1 Kitchen ~French Toast edition~]
[ Step 1: Mix egg and milk ]
(+ Bread)
[ Step 2: Soak the bread in the mix made in step 1 ]
( Vibing )
[ Step 3: Heat the frying pan and toast the bread from step 2 ]
I'm putting it in~
And we'll toast it thoroughly like this
Looks delicious~
It looks good
What do you think?
Looks delicious!
French toast and...
Ice coffee that I always have every morning
It's freshly brewed
It's wonderful
It's a great morning ☀️
I'm digging in~
It must be delicious
So good
So tasty
It's really delicious
I'm back to life~
( Big nom )
I always want to have a slow relaxing morning
When I have my breakfast
I watch YouTube videos while having breakfast
What should I watch~
PROCESS JO1 is already up
Let's watch this one
It brings back memories
It's nostalgic
Mame, Ren
I finished eating everything~
It's cleanly done
I'm stuffed after having breakfast
I'll take it slow for a bit~
[ Guitar practice (feat. STAY) ]
Ah this one
Now I'll be heading to a certain place!
Since it's my day off
I'm going to go somewhere that soothes me
I'll be going~
Amazing
It's like scenes from Ghibli
Excuse me~
There's already 1 in here
So cute
Nice to meet you
What's your name?
It seems to be the cool type
It's the cool type
So fluffy
So cute
You're sleepy?
Nice to meet you
I'm JO1's Yonashiro Sho
I'm the leader in JO1
Alright so
Here we are
It's a cat cafe!
I wanted to go here!
I wanted to go here 😹
In here
There are cat treats too
Le'ts get some!
It's ticklish~
They're coming
I could do this forever
I'm sorry I'm out of treats
It's gone
It's looking for food
It keeps looking for food
I don't have it
I'm out of them
See you
Since I've given the cats some treats
I'm going to give myself some treats too
Royal milk tea
It's tasty
You don't have to eat in such a rush
Amazing~
This place is huge
There's a small place here, like a cat's point of view
I'm entering cat's point of view
It's like a secret base
I'll give some more treats
Here it is the big eater
You're a big eater, hm?
( Give me food )
Please wait a bit
You've been eating since before
I don't have food anymore
Empty
It's empty
It's already empty
So cute
They're super cute
It's the best~
It's the best day off
It's not over yet
I still have time until the next place
I' want go to a nearby park for a bit
It's a big park
I've arrived
[ Arrived at the park ]
Somehow it's...
It's like in "The Garden of Words"
That's based on Shinjuku Gyoen National Garden though
So it feels like this
A rainy park is indeed quite nice
I feel like drawing too
Let's go to somewhere with a roof
It feels nice
Amazing
It's like a scene out of an anime
Come here~
Something like that
Amazing
It's diving in
It's eating something
Awesome
So cute~
How was it everyone?
My VLOG? For a day?
I hope you can enjoy this video
Bye bye~
[ Translated by yokousho. May contain inaccuracies ]