I bought it
Hello! This is Ohira Shosei
Today, I'm going to see autumn leaves
And I also want to go to various places
Everyone, please follow me!
Firstly, I will go to a place called "Awesome Store"
Here it is
[Arrival at The Store]
I'm going in~
(excited)
It's my first time in "Awesome Store"
Awesome! It's so cute~
Eh?!
Look! It's a sponge with ruler shape
Cool!
I saw this place on the television
Since then I've always wanted to visit here
The purpose of this shopping is..
I wanted some Christmas stuff
So I came here
I also wanted to give something for the members
I'm considering that
This is amazing! This hanger is very convenient, isn't it?
What do you hang on it?
I want some chopsticks
Hyaa~~
I've arrived
I'm here
🎄🎁 Christmas Corner 🎁🎄
Wow!
So many varieties of stuff
The size for small kid is cute
Is it for boys?
I want to give this to my little niece
(fits perfectly)
I want to film J-LOG around Christmas time
JAMs, look forward to it!
There are various places I want to visit
[All-out Shopping Starts]
Okay
This hat is nice
I will buy for all members
Okay!
Only for this once
I will bring them back for the members
I'll buy and bring them home
May I have the bill please?
Thank you very much
I bought these successfully
For the members
And for me
🍮 Nice 🍮
It's a nice day. It's a good start
I'm a bit hungry, so I will go to a café
Bye bye~
Shosei's recent news is that
He's laughing cheerfully everyday
Anything else?
I wonder what
What is it?
I started to play Pokémon Diamond and Pearl*
(*T/N: A video game)
I'm moving forward with a good feeling
You know what? Today is really..
When I walk outside
I always wear a hat
I've always worn it for the past 2 or 3 years
It's been a long time since I walked outside without a hat
[Arrived at A Café!]
I have arrived
It's the next..
It's the next target
It looks so tasty
(laughs)
Looks so delicious
He's doing a thumbs up with a smug face
He's going to make a fist
Perhaps it's quite delicious then
Wait!
Even tomato pasta with pork and chickpeas
With salad, soup, and drink is here
For me it's seaweed paella after all
Th- Thanks for your hard..
(laughs)
Seaweed paella
Yes!
And the drink is cola
Thanks for your help
I said "Thank you for your hard work" when I met the waiter for the first time
[Selfie Time]
Very nice!
This is definitely a Twitter-upload worthy
Thank you for the food
By the way
Seems like the paella needs to be eaten immediately
Awesome!
Nom~ Nom~
My mother told me
That I should never leave my meal unfinished
When I asked why..
Eh? Was it my grandmother?
She told me "Gods dwell in each grain of rice"*
(*T/N: A saying usually being told to Japanese children. We shouldn't waste a single grain that was grown and delivered to us by various beings)
I didn't believe it at all
(laughs)
Honestly, I think Gods do exist
Well, I think they have affection (towards me)
I was raised
With this kind of teaching
Back then, my way of holding chopsticks was really bad
I had been doing it like this all the time
My mother worked really hard to fix this
But I didn't get better at all
When I entered high school, I watched YouTube and got it fixed
I thought YouTube was great
My mother was surprised
It was delicious
Thank you for the food
Then the last thing is
It's autumn foliage season now
So I came to a ginkgo tree-lined avenue
Wow that's so beautiful! Amazing
(Tada!)
So pretty~
Awesome
The weather is nice too
It's like we're in Harry Potter
Wait a minute
You see
Too many people here
For Ohira who is not good at having too many people around him
The pressure was quite on a high level
But I was glad I could enjoy it for a bit
As soon as I said the avenue was full of people
I spotted a good place
Alright!
So nice!
Yes! Umm~
It's getting cold so I'm going home~