SUKAI: I'm going to try it on
SUKAI: J-LOG viewers, hello
SUKAI: I'm Kinjo Sukai
SUKAI: Today I'm shooting my J-LOG
SUKAI: It's raining now, but we have a guest today
RUKI: Hello, I'm Shiroiwa Ruki
SUKAI: I'm Kinjo Sukai
RUKI: Hello everyone
RUKI: Today I'll be joining Sukai's J-LOG
SUKAI: Right
RUKI: Yes, we've arrived at a café
RUKI: The rain is falling down
RUKI: So we'll go in now
RUKI & SUKAI: Let's go in!
[Café Time]
SUKAI: Do you want a drink?
RUKI: I'm torn between milk tea and cocoa drink
SUKAI: Oh, nice picks
(What should we order~?)
SUKAI: This looks delicious
(Bites)
Nom~ Nom~
(Completely finished the plate)
SUKAI: We've arrived
[Arrived at Shimokitazawa]
RUKI: We've arrived
SUKAI: We're at Shimokitazawa
[Arrived at Shimokitazawa]
RUKI: Yes!
SUKAI: Finally we're able to come here
RUKI: That's right
SUKAI: I'm so excited now
RUKI: Oh~ Nice!
RUKI: We really came here
SUKAI: We're here now
SUKAI: I'm so excited for real
RUKI: Me too
RUKI: Do you have anything you're looking for?
SUKAI: I'm looking for shirts or other tops
SUKAI: Like T-shirts..
RUKI: You want to look for shirts?
SUKAI: Since it's getting hot now
SUKAI: And also other stuff
RUKI: Should we start looking?
[Entering A Vintage Shop]
RUKI: Feels refreshing to me because I've never really gone to this kind of place
SUKAI: I've also only been here once
RUKI: Eh~ Wow!
RUKI: So this is how it feels like
[Flamingo Shimokitazawa Store]
SUKAI: What do you think?
SUKAI: Look here, it looks really good on you
SUKAI: How is it?
RUKI: Looking good
RUKI: Ah, I think this one is better
SUKAI: I really like this one and this one
RUKI: Then I'll go with this too
SUKAI: This?
SUKAI: We'll be buying these
SUKAI: Nice!
SUKAI: Cute
SUKAI: This looks good with that
RUKI: If I also put on the glasses that I just bought before
RUKI: HAHAHA
SUKAI: So loud! Your laugh is so loud
RUKI: I'm sorry
RUKI: Because they go so well together
SUKAI: They indeed look nice
RUKI: Sorry, I just let out a loud laugh
(Does it fit me?)
Hahah 😁
SUKAI: I'm going to try it on
RUKI: Cue!
Tada!!
RUKI: Oooooh, nice!
RUKI: Trousers? Looking nice on you
SUKAI: This one
SUKAI: What do you think?
RUKI: So refreshing
RUKI: It's giving off a summer vibe
SUKAI: Awesome! I'm buying these
SUKAI: We bought them
RUKI: We bought quite many
SUKAI: We kind of took our time there
SUKAI: But we've made a good buy
RUKI: That's right
SUKAI: Look!
Shopping bags - In both hands
SUKAI: We've been strolling around here in Shimokitazawa
SUKAI: But I-
SUKAI: I have a shop I wanted to visit here
SUKAI: Let's make that shop for our last visit!
RUKI: Okay
SUKAI: Let's go!
RUKI: Let's go!
SUKAI: This shop looks nice too
RUKI: All looks nice
SUKAI: Excuse me
SUKAI: Is this shop closed already?
SHOP OWNER: Yes! We're sorry
SUKAI: Ahh!
(Sad)
SUKAI: We got rejected
SUKAI: Excuse us and thank you very much
(Sad)
SUKAI: We've finished our shopping
RUKI: Yes~!
SUKAI: We bought quite a lot, really
RUKI: Yeah so many
SUKAI: It's getting dark here
SUKAI: And we're getting hungry
SUKAI: So, we're going to eat meat
SUKAI: And call it a day
RUKI: Oh, that's great! Closing it with yakiniku
SUKAI: Well then-
SUKAI: See you at the restaurant!
RUKI: Let's go!
[Closing with Yakiniku]
RUKI: Thanks for today! Cheers!
RUKI: So good!
RUKI: It's so good, right?
SUKAI: Yes!
SUKAI: Should we go to sleep now?
RUKI: We went to a cafe
RUKI: And went to see the vintage clothing shop
RUKI: And now eating yakiniku at night
RUKI: Isn't that the best?
SUKAI: The best?
RUKI: The best!
RUKI: I'm so happy
RUKI: Because Sukai invited me
RUKI: We've always said "Let's go!"
RUKI: Like going to vintage clothing shop, we've been saying that for so long
SUKAI: That's what we've always been saying
RUKI: Should we grill it?
SUKAI: Let's grill it!
RUKI: Tongue! It's the tongue that we both love
RUKI: Since tongue is now ready, I'll try it now
SUKAI: They look so appetizing for real
RUKI: Wow, it's so tender! Wait a second
RUKI: Dip in the lemon
RUKI: I'll eat now~
RUKI: It's SO tender!
SUKAI: Really?
RUKI: It's so good!
SUKAI: I'll eat now~
RUKI: It's so tender, isn't it?
RUKI: How is it?
SUKAI: This is too good
SUKAI: I'll eat this
SUKAI: Hmm~
SUKAI: Delicious!
SUKAI: Delicious?
RUKI: Delicious ❣
SUKAI: We finished eating now
SUKAI: How is it? Are you full now?
RUKI: This was so delicious
SUKAI: It was so good for real
SUKAI: We wanted to eat meat before
RUKI: Yeah~
SUKAI: I wonder how much the bill for all of this
RUKI: Pretty high I think
SUKAI: Well, it's not exactly a rule in JO1
SUKAI: But we sometimes decide who would pay after a meal
RUKI: We always decide through hide-and-seek, right?
RUKI: So let's play hide-and-seek now
SUKAI: As if we can!
SUKAI: No one does that!
RUKI: Should we decide by rock paper scissors then?
RUKI: The winner will pay
SUKAI: Well, that's what we call manly
RUKI: But deciding through rock paper scissors at time like this isn't manly
SUKAI: You’re right
RUKI: Should we do it?
Sukai: Should we?
[Paying The Bill by Rock Paper Scissors]
RUKI: Then the winner will pay
[Paying The Bill Via Rock Paper Scissors]
SUKAI & RUKI: Rock paper scissors!
RUKI: AHAHAHA 🤣
RUKI: That was close!
RUKI: I suppose the bill will be pretty expensive
SUKAI: Definitely..
RUKI: Are you okay?
RUKI: Because you've only had 25 yen before
SUKAI: I'm okay
SUKAI: Barely.. Barely okay
RUKI: Rock paper scissors!
RUKI: That was close!
RUKI: What? You haven't finished your meal!
RUKI: Is he for real?
SUKAI: Thank you for the food
RUKI: This guy.. His rice bowl came when we had already deciding on who would pay
RUKI: You know what?
RUKI: I know there'll be a dessert too (coming out after this)
SUKAI: Correct
RUKI: You really eat a lot!
SUKAI: Delicious~
RUKI: Your big appetite alone is on another level
SUKAI: So good~ It's so good!
SUKAI: Let's do rock paper scissors for once
RUKI: For once
SUKAI: This is the third round
RUKI: Rock paper scissors!
SUKAI: What's with his reaction just now?
RUKI: Usually the loser will pay
RUKI: But I just remembered..
SUKAI: Please replay his reaction just now
RUKI: Rock paper scissors!
RUKI: UWAAH!
RUKI: Oh!
RUKI: Huh?
RUKI: I thought the winner will pay
RUKI: Thank you for the meal
RUKI: Shiroiwa Ruki is supporting Kinjo Sukai's activities
RUKI: We've had a great meal!
RUKI: Well, he's the one eating a lot anyway