So fast
I was charging it
It's definitely charging
Oh, it has started
HELLO, I'M RUKI!!!
Sorry to have made you waiting
HELLO, I'M OHIRA SHOSEI!!!
Please take care of us!
- Everyone, sorry to have made you wait
- Thank you for waiting
Your smile is "Love & Peace"
This is "Louis Vuitton" Shiroiwa Ruki.
Please take care of me
Uhh.. "A heart.. in your heart".
I am Ohira Shosei
Please take care of us
We will start it
To everyone who is bored staying at home
I hope you find energy even if it's just a little
We, JO1, are doing live broadcast since yesterday
And we change the members in charge everyday!
Oh~ Nice kids
I'll get right to it, please look at the back!
There's homework given by Shion and Sho-kun yesterday
- And that homework is..
- The homework is..
Blow a kiss, please!
What should we do? Doing this early in the morning, from the beginning?
Or should we do it as a gift for the viewers
Who are watching till the end?
- Let's do that! Let's do it at the end
- Then, let's leave it until the end
You might probably be busy, but everyone please watch until the end! My apologies
My apologies
Okay! So first of all, let's do the first segment!
The first segment is JO1's weather talk!
The curtains are closed, so I don't know the weather today
According to the information I know, it seems it's raining
- It seems like it, right?
- Right
- So, you should dry your laundry inside the house
- Yes!
- Also for everyone not to go out much, right?
- Yep! Try not to go out
In times like this and it's raining. It's dangerous,
so if possible! Please refrain from it
And it's getting warm these days.
The temperature difference between night and day is huge
So, please bring your coat when you go out
Also since we started 5 minutes late,
we will end the live broadcast at 10:25!
- Everyone, I'm looking forward to work with you!
- Looking forward!
So, what about the area where you live?
How is the weather?
- By the way, it's raining in our place, isn't it?
- It's raining for us
How many people are watching this?
Is there anyone from a sunny area?
Rain in Saitama, rain in Aomori too
"It's s clear sky here!"
Clear sky is nice
It's sunny in Kyushu too, isn't it?
Sho-san's energy always goes down on rainy days
There are a lot of comments. I'm happy
16,000 viewers? Awesome!
I've done some live broadcasts back then
- So, I kinda get it. Comments like these..
- Nostalgic
They lift up your spirit for sure, right?
There is a comment, "Do you like Todoroki-kun? Do you like HeroAca*?"
(*T/N: The anime 'My Hero Academia'. Shosei's Zoom nickname is Todoroki-kun, a character from the show)
- Well, Shosei and I like Todoroki and Bakugo
- Yes
- I love HeroAca, too
- I love Todoroki. He is cool
I attached a protector on the tip of my iPhone's charger...On this part..
They sell Todoroki and Bakugo ones, so I use them
- I want to buy it, too. It's so nice
- Yeah, it's so cute
They said, "It's sunny in Shikoku", "Osaka, too"
So, it's raining in the eastern region I guess
It's also cloudy in Aichi
Then, let's go to the next segment!
Next up is JO1's "Omikuji!"*
(*T/N: fortune-telling paper strip)
- Shosei, please explain
- Alright
There are fortune cookies here
We will claim both of our and JAM's lot, then I will read the fortune
I only have to pick two of these, right? Probably
That's right. Are we doing this one by one?
- Ah, one by one. Then Shosei..
- Is it alright if we eat this?
- You take out the paper, right?
- Ah, that's..
Since it's not something to eat
Okay, I'll read it
This is awesome
Oh!
Okay, my fortune is..
"Shokichi"*.. That's how you read this, right?
(*T/N: slightly good luck, fourth best fortune)
In the Shokichi, "You might get a stomachache"
And the lucky item is yellow monkey!
Here
- Are you saying it's Junki?
- Yup, that's what I'm talking about
If it's yellow monkey (then it's him)
Then I'll go with this
You're eating it!
Here I go
"Daikichi*!!"
(*T/N: excellent luck, the best fortune)
It says, "Let's go at our own pace today"
- My pace~ ♪
- It's "Young"
And the lucky item is..
This one is Junki as well
- Carbonara
- You're lying!
- Amazing!
- That's what it said
- Then I will go to Junki's room after this ends
- Yes. Me too
- This is JAM's lot
- Yes, please do JAM's turn
Alright. Here it is
OH!!
I'll do it
It's "Daidaikichi"!*
(*T/N: grand luck, best of the best fortune)
- Daidaikichi?
- There is Daidaikichi, you know? Wow!
What is that? Daidaikichi..
"Doing something embarrassing may bring good things!"
Your lucky item is JO1's members' wink
If that so, please do it
3, 2, 1! (winks)
Okay
Ruki-kun, please
Do we stick this on here?
Can you take this off?
So it's like that
I'm so bad at winking
I can't do it. Really
- Look! See it?
- Ahaha
I'm really bad at it
Then we'll stick these on
Here
I'm not good at winking since a long time ago
I got it. So, it's like this
Ah, is that so?
Where do I have to stick this on?
Oh, I thought I was supposed to stick it on like this
- It was a mistake
- Really?
- Is this going to work?
- Yep
On the wall too
- Shosei, write for mine too
- Okay
- And write for JAM's paper too later
- Ah, there is JAM's one here, too!
- Yes JAM's is already written
Thank you
- "It's 20,000 viewers soon!", they said. I'm glad!
- Crazy! Since morning..
Everyone, I'm so happy like this
It's amazing... They are joining Asakatsu (morning activity) for us
"Ruki-kun, please do a peace sign"
Haha, me too
"Shosei, put your hood on!"
With that, is it alright to move on to the next segment?
Then the next segment is..
Ah! Is it this one? Is this the next one?
The next segment is JO1's observation diary!
- Observation diary!
- That's right
What is that, Shosei-san?
Umm.. There is an exchange diary written by Shion-kun and Sho-san here. Let's read it!
- This diary, right?
- Yes!
Alright. I will read it~
Name..
Name: Kamome-chan
Date: May 18th
Weather: Cloudy
Things I've learnt: The container was too big for the sprouts to reach the water
The name is Kamome
It's name is Kamome-chan
- Kamome-chan?
- Correct
Then we will raise Kamome-chan
Yes. It's like that
So, what are we going to do?
Ah~! The staff soaked it in the water
I got it
Shall we see it?
Kamome-chan
Ah, I like this BGM
It seems the way they did it yesterday was wrong
The staff has helped to soak it in the water properly
"Let's write the name", they said
Do you mean to write Kamome-chan here?
Eh? What do you mean?
Then can I work on it?
- Ah, will you?
- Yes
OK. Then I'll read the comments
Oh.. It's nice, isn't it?
Isn't it a nostalgic sight?
There is a lot of comments like "Naoto's (Manager) way to raise the sprouts was wrong"
- Naoto-san..
- Yes
Well, Naoto-san got that side. He's clumsy
Alright
For your information, this isn't a choker but my clothes' tie
It's attached on here
So I just wrapped it around my neck and made it like a choker
The fashionable point
The tie is a bit long, so I'm just making it like a choker
Right
"Ruki, what time did you sleep last night?"
But these days.. I'm trying to sleep early diligently
Yesterday, too. Since there is this broadcast, I think I fell asleep around 1 a.m
Everyone, what time do you usually go to sleep?
"Ruki, wear your hood"
I don't wear it often
The reason I was late today isn't because the carriage is delayed. I'm sorry
I was in various meetings, so I was late. My apologies
Wonderful! A lot of comments are coming. I'm pleased
There is so many
Like this..
Amazing, right?
"I slept around that time, too"
Awesome!
Okay. I did it
Kamome-chan
Ah, Kamome has finally arrived
- Yes
The assignment is, we took the sprouts out of the water and sprayed them from the top
It seems there's a lot of things will be coming up from here
- Are you sure?
- Yes
- A week.. This would be possible in a week, right?
- Right!
I think it's fast
- Is it done?
- Yes, it is
This segment is for observation
- "Please put on the aluminum foil lid"
- Okay~
Is this right? Is it alright?
Is it correct this time?
I think it's correct this time
JAMs also have been together with us doing this since yesterday
Is there anyone among JAMs who grows this?
- I wonder if there is one
- It would be great if there is one
"Who drew the Kamome illustration?"
Ah, but there is already "Shion" written in here
But you won't see it clearly
It's nice, right?
- He signed it properly, too
- Okay
"What did you have for breakfast?"
I haven't eaten yet
Shosei, have you eaten already?
I left half of my breakfast
There wasn't time
Alright, it's done!
It's like this. I'll wrap this up
That's all. This has been our observation
We need to record the diary here properly later, right?
Well, then. Tomorrow..
Our observation diary
Should we go to the next segment?
The next one is..
- It's Higawari* segment, isn't it?
(*T/N: a segment that would change everyday)
Today's Higawari segment for me and Shosei is this one
Our Higawari segment is..
Ruki and Shosei's Zoom Impromptu Talk!
Let me tell you about this.. I don't like it.
I can't do things like this
It makes me a bit nervous
He has been like that even before the live broadcast started
You have to improvise, right?!
- Isn't it difficult?
- It is! Very difficult
- What should we do?
Well, wouldn't the vibe work out somehow?
You said you wanted to do something, right?
I knew there's something that Shosei wants to do
But he didn't tell me at all before the live broadcast
I'm scared of what's going to happen
- Anyway.. Should we do it?
- OK
- We can do it with that, right? The background
- Yes. We can do that
If you please
Umm..
There it is. There it is
Ah, wait a second. This is difficult
Oops! Wait a minute
This is dangerous
How do you change this?
Can you do it?
My friend's picture just came up
No! Wait a moment
How can I turn this off?
Stupid!!! x4
Stupid! x3
This isn't it! Dummy!
Ah, is this it? Is this it? Okay~
That was dangerous!! You!
Is this it?
- Dangerous.. That was very dangerous
- It was really scary
Absolutely dangerous!
It was insane for a moment
So it's reversed. If you use
this virtual (background)
Now with this, the place is a basketball court
I was originally a soccer fan, so I'm not very familiar with basketball court
How- how are we going to sort this out?
Shall we get started?
Today is.. mini drama?
- I want to reenact the best scene in basketball
- That scene?
- Is that so?
- Yes!
I got it! How.. what should we do?
Which part.. How would we do it?
Which part are we going to do?
Then, I'll play the female role
Okay! x3
You see, Shosei and I..
Long time ago...It's not that long time ago though
During a filming a month ago, when we got some free time
Unexpectedly there was a basketball court in the studio
So both of us...There was also a basketball
Right? We played basketball a brief, right?
Please see our trifling fast and short passes back then
- Let's say this Pompompurin is a ball
- Okay
Shosei will play the female role
♪♪ ♪♪♪♪♪ ♪♪ ♪♪♪♪♪*
(*T/N: Ichibu to Zenbu by B'z, OST of Buzzer Beat drama)
I'll do it
"I'm strong. I'm strong"
- "Riko!"
- "Yes~"
- "If this goes in, go out with me!"
- "Fine~!
- "I can do it. If it's me then I can do it!"
- "Do your best!"
"I am powerful!"
Everything~ ♪
(*T/N: chorus part in the OST)
"Riko!!!"
I want to upload the video when the outfit for the filming is revealed someday
- Yes, I want to upload it
- We took a video of it
We want to upload it.
Please look forward to it
Umm, I have a question for Shosei. Do you mind?
I've never asked this to anyone
This is trending nowadays.
I'm not sure whether you know this or not though
Let's say Shosei has a girlfriend a few years later
Kiss that girlfriend and get 10,000 yen
Or the world's.. Kiss the world's most beautiful woman and get 70,000 yen
What would you do, Shosei?
- No but it's definitely the one I like...
- Girlfriend?
-Yes. My girlfriend
- You would kiss her and get the 10,000 yen?
- Yes. I will get the 10,000 yen
- Eh~
What do you understand from this?
If I were you, I'd kiss the world's most beautiful woman and get 80,000 yen
Do you understand the meaning?
Since my girlfriend is the most beautiful woman in the world
Thus I will get the 10,000 and 70,000 yen. It's 80,000 in total
......
(*T/N: Shosei is lost for words)
Thank you very much!
Yes. So it's like that
Scary x3
What are you talking about?
- You understand, right?
- I get it. I get it
You understand, right?.
Yes, that's right
Because this is popular these days, so I thought asking Shosei about this
- It's interesting
- Interesting, isn't it?
Should we move on to the next situation?
Can we finish this on time?
- ♪♪ ♪♪♪♪♪~
- It's scary!
For basketball I could more or less figure out how to do the scenario
What should I do? What would we do?
The background..
- Did it work?
- It did. It did
- Next, I'll do the girl role
- Okay
- "Ah~ Today is also cold"
- "It's cold"
"So cold. I'm in distress for some reason,
what should I do next?"
Oi! Shosei, your background is still
the basketball court, you know?
-Ah! It's changed. It's changed
- It's changed
Okay. We'll do it
"What do I do? I'm in distress. What should I do from now on?"
"Is that so?"*
(*T/N: Ruki is fooling around since 遭難 and そうなん? are homophones)
- "Eh? So, were we in distress?"
- "That's right"
- "Is that so?"
- "It is"
- "Shosei-kun! It's cold!"
- "Eh.. What to do~?"
- "I will give you my warmth"
- "Ah, too close"
Alright. Too close is not good, so that's it~
- That was the heart-fluttering scene
- Yes
This would be heart-fluttering for sure
- Please be thrilled
- What kind of situation is this?
Snow...Is that when you're in distress?
- This is distress. The theme is distress
- I see
When you're in distress with Shosei, he would warm you up?
- Yes, that's correct
- I got it
Please call me anytime
Oh, right! We haven't blown a kiss yet
We have to blow a kiss, at the end
- Please do it
- Alright
Oii!
Well then. See you again
Homework for the two members tomorrow
What is it?
Homework
Homework?
Is anything alright? What do we do?
Two persons in charge tomorrow are
Ren-kun and Sukai, The Tibetan Fox pair
The homework that we want the Tibetan Fox pair to do
- If we think about that..
- What should they do?
Then.. Let's see how good they are at talking with snow background
- Ah, you're talking about this, right?
- Correct!
I see
Just like this
Let's see how much they can hype things with this snow background
- We'd want the.. Tibetan Fox pair to do it tomorrow!
- Please do us this favor!
Everyone, please check out the live broadcast tomorrow, too!
- That's all. This has been JO1's Ohira Shosei and..
- Shiroiwa Ruki!
Alright. Bye bye!