Oh! It has started
- Has it started?
- Yep!
- Well, then. Good morning, everyone!
- Good morning!
We'll start it
Asakatsu* JO1! Today it will be by JO1's Kinjo Sukai and
(*T/N: Morning activity)
Kawashiri Ren!
I look forward to work with you
As the time of everyone staying home continues
we hope to bring some energy to JAM through this
So since yesterday the JO1 members change daily to do a live stream
Isn't it the third day? Yes, I think so
Yes
To you who might be exhausted by this self-restrai... self-restraintment
- Such a difficult word
- Well, it's morning
We would like to bring some encouragement to everyone who is exhausted by the self-restrainment
So I will go first!
Good morning, everyone!
Thanks for getting up early
Let's spend a wonderful morning together with me and Sukai and make it a great day!
Ah, I'm so nervous
You are Kinjo?
[TN: Kinjo, his family name sounds similar to 'kincho', meaning 'nervous']
I am nervous
- Alright, good morning everyone!
- Good morning!
Hey, you who is rubbing your eyes!
Have you brushed your teeth already?
Have you eaten breakfast?
Let's stay healthy and do our best today!
Did our feelings reach you?
- Wonder if they did?
- They did~
I think we can overcome this situation if we try our best a little longer, so everyone let's do our best together!
Yes
Well~
We got some homework from Ruki and Shosei yesterday
- Amazing
- This has such an amazing analogue feeling
They did their best putting this on the wall
- What's that?
- Yes
We gonna do a funny improvisational talk in front of a snow mountain scenery
And I am the worst at this
Yeah, I am also not good at that
They wrote it should be funny, so we have no chance
We gonna suck at this. For sure
It is not funny but-
In a previous Jamming with JO1 radio broadcast
There was the task to talk about your oldest memory
The most past thing you could remember
- I talked there about when I fell in a hole at a skiing place
- Eh?
I was a small child back then
When I noticed it, I was slipping already
And before I knew it I had fallen into the hole
I was riding a sleigh with my older brother
But when I see this I can only think of falling into a hole back then
- What happened to your brother?
- He was under me
- Oh, under you?
- Yes
So scary
How about you? Do you have something related to snowy mountains?
In my case... There is snowboarding
With a friend- Ah! The father of a friend took me along for this
It was my first time doing this but
I was confident I could do it
There were 3 routes: Beginners, Intermediate and Advanced
And for some reason I took the Advanced route
- But it was your first time, right?
- Yes, it was
Well, he taught me how to do it to some extent but
In the beginning he taught me how slide from side to side
But there's no exhilaration from that
Because everyone was riding down so fast
And sliding from side to side. I hated how I was going down slowly
So I thought I'm gonna try it
So I turned my board from sideways to vertical
- ...and slid like this
- Dangerous! That's dangerous
and while I thought wow
The board became stuck somehow and I fell down
I rolled over twice and broke my wrist in just one day
- That's what I remember
- That's scary
- We only have memories of getting hurt
- Right!
- These are nowhere close to be funny
- Not funny, but
It's not funny at all. What should we do?
- Well it is important to be careful at snowy mountains
- Right
Was our homework OK?
- It is OK
- Is it okay for you, Shosei and Ruki?
- Could we do it well?
- We sadly couldn't make it funny
Next up is this segment
JO1's weather talk!
I think today, too, it is cloudy in the area we are living
- Hmm... It is a bit cloudy
- Yes, a bit
But when I checked the weather earlier it was stated it might be raining later
- Everyone!
- How about your place?
It is sunny in other regions, right?
Wait, let me look at the comments
"It is cloudy in Hokkaido"
Ah, it seems cloudy at a lot of places
"It is sunny in Kanagawa"
"Today will be cloudy"
Yes, today seems to be quite a cloudy day
- "It's sunny in Osaka"
- Really? That's nice
- It's Osaka, Sukai.
- It's Osaka. I'm glad it's sunny there.
[T/N: Osaka is Sukai's hometown]
- The comments are too fast
- Yes, they are
It is amazing how many are coming
There are places where it is sunny but overall it is cloudy
- Seems like it
- It is cloudy at a lot of places
- Also, when we went out earlier, it was a bit chilly
- Indeed
It has been quite warm lately, but it was chilly earlier
"It is cloudy in Sukai's hometown"
But weren't there comments that it was sunny over there before?
Sukai's... Shhh! Shhh!
I guess someone who knows Sukai's hometown is watching
If it is cloudy the laundry won't dry well. Well, mom, I am...
... we don't need to do that?
"Chibesuna, please clear the clouds from JAM's hearts!"
Is what Naoto-san wrote
- That's what we're going to do?
- How do we do that?
- It's funny
- We directly start to joke around
And with that should we move to the next segment?
Let's ignore it and move on
Next up is JO1's fortune telling!
It's fortune telling now
As there are fortune cookies over there
We will open two for us and for JAM, too
- Should we?
- I will do it directly
And we get them... from here
- Then, let's start with Sukai, me, and JAM!
- Got it
I'll start!
- They look good
- Right
- It doesn't matter which one I take?
- Yes
And I eat this now? Really?
I have to eat it? For real?
Ah, I have to break it first?
Naoto-san really...
Oh, I can't get the paper
I can't take it out
Ah, there it is!
Ah, I'm hungry today~
Ta-da!
Eh? Scary! Look at it, everyone
- What's wrong?
- Can you see it?
Can you see it?
- Letting your guard down for a bit may be fatal
- Eh?!
It is terrible luck
[T/N: The worst possible fortune you can get]
You better avoid snowy mountains
- Right, they seem dangerous
- You can't go there
This is awful
But let me think of it as something positive
It might be terrible luck, it can't be worse than this
I'm sorry, let's make it something happy
It is really just that I had the terrible luck of pulling this, right?
- It can only get better from now on
- Exactly
- Okay, I will go next!
- Please do so
This one screams that it wants to be picked but I won't do so
So I'll pick this one
I can take it out without break it apart
- As expected! I'm surprised
- What could be?
- No way
Eh, no way?
Can you see it?
Bad luck
I got bad luck
- Today ...
- What does it say?
Please be careful not to forget something
Your lucky item is Pokka Lemon
[T/N: It is a drink]
Our luck is a kinda bad
Ah, I didn't read my lucky item!
Your lucky item is a pot handle
A pot handle? Just the handle?
- Ah the fry pan I am using for cooking got a handle you can remove
- Ah, these!
You can remove it
Ah, isn't it that chichiri one?
[T/N: Apparently that's the jingle of the ad]
- Chi- Chichiri... I don't know
- But today, you can only raise from the bottom
- That's right
- Lastly, let's pick one for JAM
- Yes
Sukai, pick it!
Ah, I'm so sorry everyone. I have the worst luck
Because we are already out of luck
- I will go with this one
- Okay
I'm scared!
Okay~
What?!
This is awful, too
Please look at it!
It is future good luck
I'm so sorry everyone. I cannot apologize enough
So... You might knock your little toe against the corner of a cupboard
Your lucky item is Pompom Purin
Oh~ It is Shosei!
- Shosei!
- Shosei, come here!
Come here! Come right now!
Everyone I am sorry for pulling just future good luck, but it will come
It certainly will come
- Let's think of it positively
- Because it has only started now
Hey, look!
We got these!
- Today gonna be lucky~
- Lucky~
Naoto-san immediately brought us our lucky items
Yes, that's it
Alright, let's put our fortune from today on the wall
- Let's do it!
Ah, yes
Letting your guard down for a bit may be fatal
This...
But I thought so. I might be targeted by someone
- Sukai pulled a future good luck for JAM
- Yes, I did
- 18,000 people are watching right now
- I see
So 18,000 people will have good luck only in the future
I'm so sorry everyone
I am really sorry
I will put this here
- Me too
- Can you see it?
And the one for JAM
Oh, it seems like there is someone who hit their toe on the corner of a cupboard earlier
Eh? I am so sorry!
I am truly sorry for this!
I will pat you as an apology later. I am sorry!
- Should we move on?
- Yes, let's move on
- And the next segment is...
JO1's observation diary!
- Eh?
- What is that?
There is a observation diary, so let's check out the observation from the last two days
- Is it this one?
- Yes
Eh? So this is one day?
"Day 1"
"What we noticed: The container was too big, so the water wasn't enough"
- "We named it Kamome"
- Its name is Kamome
[T/N: Kamome = seagull]
"Shion..."
It says Shion drew it. It's by him
Next! 19th of May
- That's yesterday.
- "What we noticed:"
"We evened out the seeds under the aluminum foil"
"By Ohira and Shiroiwa"
Wait a second!
The picture
- Wow!
- It's so bad
Shion did quite well on the first day
- He drew every single one. That's typical of Shion
- Eh?
- Then, Sukai...
Let's take a look on how it looks like today!
How Kamome-chan is doing today
Oh, the water might spill!
- Be careful. Because I have terrible luck today
-Yes
Oh~ It looks great!
Apparently the water wasn't enough yesterday, so Naoto-san filled it up again
- Eh, is that so?
- Thank you very much
Wait, I can't show it
I can't show it, right?
Unless it's titled I can't show it
- That's how it looks like
- Oh~ Be careful
That's how it looks like~
What's going on with it?
- Some... have sprouted already
- Really?
There are some sprouted ones
Alright! We will publish our observation from today on our official SNS. So please look forward to this!
Ah, I spilled some water!
-Ah, that's your terrible luck
Yes, there it is
Alright, I will go and change the water~
See you!
- Please take over for now, Ren-kun
- See you~
Oh? There are only comments saying "As expected from Naoto-san"
Yes, they have sprouted
I wonder whether it can grow in just one week
What will we do if it takes longer?
I'm getting worried about this
Wow! It says, "I didn't expect anything else from Sukai's terrible luck"
But from now on, it's only getting better
- Comeback! Sukai has come back!
- Welcome back
I'm back~
They are asking, "Which white socks am I wearing?"
Which ones are those?
Today, they are from Hanes
- Nice
- They are cute
Then, I'll wrap them up in the aluminum foil again
- Okay
- Good night
- Nighty~ Grow big!
- Grow big! I'm counting on you
Do so in a week!
Show us your rapid growth in just one week!
You can do it! I know you can
You just need to work hard, so do your best
We will give you lots of water
Yes~
And with that let's move forward
How about the daily segment next?
Hey, when you heard about it earlier
- You were like, "I don't wanna~ I don't wanna~"
- It's the second 'I don't wanna' today
So, Sukai, what is the daily segment?
The daily segment today is...
The game of Chibesuna dedicating an "I love you" to JAM!
I don't wanna~
We got our third "I don't wanna" today!
Yes that's the game for today
It is a card game in which we come up with a proposal right away and propose to JAM
Well the rules are kinda difficult and I have troubles understanding them so
- Let me read them
- Okay!
The guide...
The guide writes the play time is about 15 to 30 minutes, however
Uh...
I would like to play it. In an easy version
So... Hmm...
There are these flash cards?
You combine... These flash cards with these other cards
- You combine them to make a proposal
- Alright, alright
So, you take 6 cards?
You pull 6 cards and...
You pull 6 cards of those, too, and then you have 6 + 6 cards, so 12 cards altogether
And then you make a proposal with these 12 cards
- I get it
- I don't wanna~
- I really don't wanna~
-So, I don't wanna...
- I don't wanna
- Should we start?
- Should we?
- So I will...
- Let's draw first!
- Is it okay if I do it first?
- 6 of these and 6 of the other ones
- Do I take one of the another?
- No
You can do as you want
You can combine the 6 & 6 cards as you feel like
And it seems okay not to use some cards
Ah, then I'm gonna start
So I have 6 cards now
- Do you also have 6 of those?
- Ah, I need them too?
You have 6 + 6 cards
What is this?
Four?
What is the one that says 4?
- It seems like you can use it for anything
- Makes sense
Ah! I finally got the rules!
I think...
- You put them like that?
- You do this
Like this and they'll make a sentence
- I see
- You connect the arrow to make a sentence
And it doesn't matter if you do it like this or like that
Ah, we are doing this for more than 20 minutes already!
I want to have some more fun with everyone
Eh, this is so difficult!
- Ah, some time to arrange...
- Please give us some time for this
Please give that to us!
In the meantime Naoto-san will take over
He is waving his hands like this a lot
You use that word during a propose?
[T/N: The card says "Hole"]
"Hole" is written there
- Hole...
- "When I was digging a hole..."
So difficult~
"When I did that, I met a guy with white hair..."
- Wah, this is crazy
- I don't want to... I don't wanna... I just don't
This is fun, right?
I got the same one twice?
The same card twice? What a waste!
Ah, this is good!
Eh, wait, can we only use the words from the cards?
Only those?
This gonna sound so awkward
- Let's just go with it
- Ah! Intentionally?
Well, it's such a game
Wait a bit, I dunno what to do
Because I never proposed to anyone
Indeed
Wait!
- It's difficult
- It's impossible
Honestly it is
- Wait~
- How should I do this?
"You..."
- Got one!
- Eh, so fast!
- Wait a minute!
- I, too... Yes I managed to make one
19,000 people are watching us
I will start in the meantime
I want another "You"
"You..."
A comment says, "Proposing is not an easy thing to do"
That's right
We make a proposal out of this?
Yes
With the meaning, "Let's get married"?
- But there is nothing that feels like "Let's get married"
- Indeed
"Sukai's so fast"
- Yes, I am
- He really is
What? What is it?
Something that whispers love
I don't wanna~
"What did you eat for breakfast?"
I didn't eat anything
But I made a smoothie for myself this morning
I'm gonna drink this
Everyone do you do something like making smoothies in the morning?
Or did you make breakfast?
I... have started this quite recently
I have no idea
My nose is itchy
"Sukai, what are you into lately?"
What I am into lately is...
Well...
It's just for fun, but I'm into making clothes
And writing lyrics. Nothing that special
Ah, there seems a lot people who make smoothies
Please, tell me if you have a recommended recipe
Sukai, buy me another 20 minutes
Yes, I will do that
Eh? Is it really impossible for me?
Ah, yes! Among the ingredients for the smoothie are blueberries
Help!
So fast! There are so many comments
Please make more and more comments
I will answer everything
Seems like
Some forcefulness in a proposal is okay according to (Naoto) Okawa-san's sign
I think mine is quite forceful
Please forgive me for this
This game is impossible for me
My eyesight is bad, yes
Ren-kun, you can do it!
Okay, let's try. Let's do it!
Can we start?
Help! This is so bad
Mine isn't connected at all however
So you can't say anything that is not written here?
A little bit is okay? Right?
There is a comment, saying "You said Okawa-san"
(T/N: Until this day, their manager was only known as Naoto, so they accidentally revealed his full name for the first time)
"You said Okawa-san"?
It's okay
- Let's start!
- Yes!
I don't wanna!
I'm done!
Is it okay to show one by one?
Because you know, showing all at once is impossible
I will start now!
The first one "From
the bottom of my heart
my love
for you
is boiling
and that's
all I need
in this world"
- And now it's Ren-kun's turn!
- I don't wanna...
My one was quite good, right?
Alright, I'll do it
Is it okay if I cheat a little?
It should be
Okay, here I go
Here I go
"I love you
I will make sure to cherish you
If it is the two of us, we can create a wonderful future together
Don't you think so, too?"
- Amazing, isn't it? That was amazing
- I don't wanna anymore... I don't wanna. I don't... I just don't
- "My love is boiling for you"
- I managed to do that
My love is boiling!
What do you think, everyone?
We would like you to decide
Which one of us was better
- That's right!
Then, we will wait for 15 seconds and you write it in the comments
Please do so
Ah! This one says I left out the "hole" one
It was impossible to use "hole" for this
- What homework should we give for tomorrow?
- The homework for tomorrow is...
What should we give them?
What do you think would be good, everyone?
- What would be good?
- Are the members for tomorrow still a secret?
Tomorrow is Junki's and Syoya's turn
It will be Junki and Syoya
Because they both can cook well
They could make some food tomorrow
- And bring it to the live stream?
- Let's do that!
- That's mean!
- Let's give them this homework!
So they need to make whatever they want for breakfast and bring it
That's right
So yes, it will be like eating breakfast with everyone together
Everyone, please also prepare breakfast! While eating breakfast together with you, they gonna do tomorrow's episode
So... They are a lot of comments saying "I can't chose", "Both of you" or "Naoto"
Really!
- "Both"
- Wow, "Naoto" comes up so often
They say "Both of you"
- Everyone is so kind
- Yes, they are
In this case...
- We both win!
- Yeay!
- What matters are the feelings
- Yes!
For proposals and everything else, feelings are what matter
And with both of us winning, we would like to end today's stream
We will end this now!
With a good final feeling, the time for the end has come
- That's right! It was so short~
- Sukai
- It was your first live stream, wasn't it?
- Yes, it was
How was your first live stream?
It was fun!
I was moved because for the first time in while I felt close to everyone
It was like talking each other through the comments and such, right?
- This is nice, right?
- Yes
Did you enjoy it, dear JAM?
- Did you have fun?
- Did you?
Say "Yes~" in the comments, "Yes~"
For tomorrow, Thursday, like we said earlier
The ones in charge will be Syoya and...
- Junki
- Junki-chan
- It gonna be Junki-chan
And their homework is "Please make breakfast, bring it to the live stream and eat there!"
- Ple-Please eat it here!
Okay, so lastly since everyone is waiting for it
Should we do Conchikita?
(T/N: The Chibesuna version of Kungchikita)
- Conchikita?
- Should we?
Okay, got it!
The end has come. Thank you for watching today
- Please make sure to check out also tomorrow's Asakatsu!
- Please do so!
Okay... On three?
1, 2, 3!
Con chi ki ta! Ya!
- Bye bye!
- Bye Bye!
Thank you! You are not allowed to go back sleeping now!
Since you woke up early already!
- I will go back to sleep again
- No, you can't
- Thank you!
- Thank you very much!
There are a lot of comments saying "Saredo"
- "Saredo pokerface~"
- "Saredo pokeface~"
- Thank you very much!
- Thank you!