JUNKI:
When I see you again
Sugu mata kimi Somewhere
[Soon again you went somewhere]
KEIGO:
Sono imi ga ki ni naru yo
[I’m wondering what it meant]
KEIGO:
Mada ame ni utareteru yo
[I’m still getting rained on]
SUKAI:
Sorezore no sutairu de ima kara susume
[In our own styles, let's move forward from now]
MAME:
Kimi wa kantan ni iu sa
[You say it easily]
MAME:
Demo boku no michi wa So tough
[But my path is so tough]
REN:
Because iki ga tsumaru hodo ai wo
[Because with this love that takes my breath away]
REN:
Egaku mainichi wa kodoku de
[Everyday I envision is lonely]
SYOYA:
Can you believe me?
SHO:
Yume no tsudzuki wo miyou
[Let’s see the continuation of the dream]
SHO:
Owari wa nakutemo
[Even if there’s no end]
TAKUMI:
Oku fukaku kimi wo shiru made
[Until I know you deep down]
Zettai mou hanasanai sa
[I will definitely never let you go again]
Hey
RUKI:
Don’t run away from me
SHOSEI:
Never go back again
TAKUMI:
I’m following da da da
Du da da da
TAKUMI:
I’m following da da da
Du da da da
TAKUMI:
Yume wo tsukamu
[Grasp the dream]
SHO:
Michi no sekai e to ashi wo fumi ireyou
[Let's step into the unknown world]
JUNKI:
I’m following da da da
Du da da da
JUNKI:
Kaze ga senaka wo oshita
[The wind pushed my back]
MAME:
Bokura no jidai e to tsurete ikou
[Let’s head towards our times]
SHION:
Try & error de seichou kono uta de no guard K.O.
[We grow by trial & error, no guard from this song K.O.]
SHOSEI:
Baby slow down daijoubu
[Baby slow down it’s okay]
SHOSEI:
Soba ni ai ni iku Tonight
[I’ll meet you by your side tonight]
RUKI:
Ego ego ego suteru
[Throw away the ego ego ego]
RUKI:
Michi nara SAVAGE
[The path is savage]
SYOYA:
Nagameta keshiki wa chou Sick
[The view is so sick]
SYOYA:
Soudai ai Shawty zenbu
[Grand love shawty everything]
SHO:
Because subete wo te ni ireyou to
[Because when I try to have it all]
KEIGO:
Egaku mainichi wa kodoku de
[Everyday I envision is lonely]
SUKAI:
Can you believe me?
TAKUMI:
Yume no tsudzuki wo miyou
[Let’s see the continuation of the dream]
TAKUMI:
Shikai ga nijindemo
[Even if our vision is blurred]
MAME:
Oku fukaku kimi wo shiru made
[Until I know you deep down]
Zettai mou hanasanai sa
[I will definitely never let you go again]
Hey
SHION:
Don’t run away from me
SYOYA:
Never go back again
REN:
Nayami nante mou kieru
[My worries disappear]
REN:
Me no mae no konnan
[The difficulties before me]
JUNKI:
Tanoshime bokura wa Beast Mode
[When we are enjoying we are in beast mode]
SUKAI:
Noise darake no sekai kara
[From this world filled with noise]
SUKAI:
Nuketai no nara Follow us
[If you want to get out follow us]
MAME:
Oh oh oh get on the top
Zettai mou hanasanai sa
[I will definitely never let you go again]
Hey
SUKAI:
Don’t run away from me
TAKUMI:
Never go back again
KEIGO:
I’m following da da da
Du da da da
KEIGO:
Yume wo tsukamu
[Grasp the dream]
SHO:
Michi no sekai e to ashi wo fumi ireyou
[Let's step into the unknown world]
JUNKI:
I’m following da da da
Du da da da
JUNKI:
Kaze ga senaka wo oshita
[The wind pushed my back]
REN:
Bokura no jidai e to tsurete ikou
[Let’s head towards our times]
[Translation & romaji by Shin @cshinjam,
timing & formatting by Berry @BerryMagic_]