[Translation & timing by @cshinjam]
Go to the Top, we're JO1!
Alright, we'll being doing this project today:
Yes!
HAPPY NEWSmile YEAR Special Project!
Delivering by darts...
Um, excuse me.
Isn't your voice a little soft?
Is it?
Be more assertive.
Was it soft?
- Say the title once more.
- Okay.
Speak from your stomach.
Ouch.
Delivering by darts: Special New Year's Card!
What we'll be doing is,
with our feelings of gratitude,
JO1 will send New Year's cards
to 40,000 people in Japan.
Whoa!
- 40,000 people.
- Wow.
We'll send it to 40,000 people.
You can listen to our song "NEWSmile"
from the New Year's card.
- I see.
- Wow!
From the QR code, right?
So about where we will distribute it to...
look behind you, everyone.
Here...
It's HAPPY NEWSmile YEAR.
Here, we have a huge...
Isn't this JAPAN?
It is Japan.
- we have prepared a dart board.
- Dart board!
We will each throw a dart
at the map of Japan.
Wow!
And that's how we'll decide.
Um, hey...
What's wrong, Keigo?
What does that mean?
For example...
Where the dart hits...
The New Year's cards will
be sent to 40,000 people,
but who it will be sent to...
Will be decided by darts.
So we still don't know
who it will be sent to, right?
Yes, it will be sent to people
in that prefecture.
So 11 of us will throw a dart,
and it will be delivered
to 11 prefectures.
- Exactly.
- Good explanation.
And the New Year's cards will have numbers,
for a New Year's gift lottery
where you can win luxurious prizes.
The kind that is commonly held.
There are a limited number of New Year's cards,
so please understand that
not everyone can receive this.
Then let's start throwing the darts right away.
Well then, we have prepared the darts.
We will do it in age order.
- So we'll start with Mame-chan.
- Okay.
Then, please stand at the marker.
So where are you aiming?
Okayama prefecture, Maniwa city.
- Maniwa city!
- You're even choosing the city.
Okayama prefecture is over here.
Where?
What about Maniwa city?
Maniwa city is also around here.
The upper region.
Okay Mame, go ahead.
Okay, here I go.
It's Hyogo! It's Hyogo!
No, it's not, it's not!
It's Osaka.
It's Kyoto!
Where?
Plus it's up above,
so it's really close to Maizuru!
What? Maizuru?
It's near Maizuru.
Isn't this Amanohashidate?
I hit Kyoto.
[Kyoto]
- Shosei just needs to hit Okayama.
- Oh, true.
Next is Shion.
Shion, where are you aiming for?
Hokkaido.
He's looking down below.
Hokkaido is up here.
You're looking down below.
- Shion, go ahead.
- Okay, here I go.
[TsuRAMPAGEubo]
That was dangerous!
That was so scary!
- Sho-kun, isn't it scary over there?
- It's scary here.
- Please go ahead
- Oh he's being annoying.
Oh, Hyogo??
- Yay!
- Wow.
Aren't there too many over there?
Kyoto and Hyogo, neighboring prefectures.
[Hyogo]
There are mountains.
At this time of year,
you could totally go skiing.
Oh, that's nice.
Sukai, where are you aiming for?
I wanna aim for Osaka, but...
Aomori.
Ohh good idea.
We had a good time there.
It's pretty tough.
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
- You hit it.
- It's Hokkaido.
No, it's the sea.
Once more.
Just aim in between them.
The middle of the earlier two.
He got it!
[Aomori]
Okay, Shosei.
Kyoto has already been hit, so...
I'll aim for this general area.
That's a wide area.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
Oh! Where is that?
Where is this even??
Ibaraki.
[Ibaraki]
We have a good spread.
Syoya, where will you aim for?
Then I'll aim for my hometown, Nagoya.
Leggo!
You can do it!
That was really close!
- That's a good throw.
- That's difficult.
Oh!
- Where is that?
- Tokyo?
This is...
Gunma!
Next, the demon instructor.
[Instructor Kawanishi]
I just need one shot.
Where are you aiming?
Where should I aim?
Aim for Shikoku region.
Aim for Kagawa Prefecture.
Ohh Okayama!
Okayama!
Keigo will aim for
his beloved grandma's place...
Miyazaki.
That's so difficult!
Where is Miyazaki?
Oh, it's close!
Good throw.
- Oh!
- Ah... it's off.
It's Kagoshima.
It's Kumamoto.
Kumamon!
You're Kumamon.
I'm good at darts, so...
Ishigaki.
Ishigaki?
Oh that's difficult!
Which one is Ishigaki?
Oh, is Ishigaki over here?
Is this Miyako and Ishigaki?
It's Miyako and Ishigaki.
- Oh!
- Isn't that Nagano?
It's Nagano.
It's Nagano Prefecture.
I used to go there often to ski.
Okay, Ruki.
From Tokyo.
Where will you aim for?
Wah... this is Tokyo, you know.
It'll be cool if you make it.
[Keigo|Demon Instructor|Syoya|Shosei]
Go for it.
It's so tiny.
Here I go.
It's Fukushima.
Fukushima.
[Fukushima]
Okay, Ren, where are you aiming for?
Korea.
What the heck!
Then it's around the '24' text.
Aim for Kyushu.
I'll do that.
- Where is it?
- Huh?
Isn't it Fukuoka?
- It's Fukuoka.
- Wow!
[Fukuoka]
He's experienced in darts.
We did a good job.
- Right.
- Thank you very much.
- Sho-kun, aim here.
- Sho-kun, please hit it in my stead.
By the way, which one is Okinawa?
Kokusai-dori is around here.
- Aim for that.
- Go, go, go.
Sho-kun, where is Shuri Castle?
That's enough!
- Where's Churaumi Aquarium?
- Churaumi Aquarium is...
That's enough!
- You know it so well.
- As expected.
- Let's do it.
- Nice.
Sho-kun seems used to throwing darts.
- That's close.
- This is difficult.
Your aim is good.
Oh so close!
This is...
well, it's somewhere in Okinawa.
[Okinawa]
All right, thank you everyone!
Thank you!
We'll be sending an original New Year's card to 40,000 people,
so please look forward to it!
Right, and do you remember the serial number
I mentioned earlier?
In January, we will have a lottery
for the serial numbers on the card.
Please look forward to it.
The details are on the homepage.
Please wait with your serial numbers on hand.
So how was playing darts, everyone?
Harder than expected.
Did you go to the place you wanted?
- Yes.
- The place you wanted to get.
About half of us, right?
About 3. I think Okinawa is the most difficult.
Okinawa is the odd one out.
It was so hard.
But we got many places that
we've never been to, so I'm happy.
It's 40,000 people, so please look forward
to how it'll be delivered.
With that, thank you very much for today.
That was JO1!
Bye bye~
See you!