Translation: Kou (@yokousho), Verde (@1DERJAM)
Timing: Na (@delishriceball)
Quality Check: Na (@delishriceball), Verde (@1DERJAM)
I’m scared~
Wait!
Run, come on!
[A gift that arrived on one hot and humid summer day]
[JO1’s special trip was full of surprises, but it was fun nevertheless]
Hold on! This is not good
- Should I give you one more?
- No, thanks!
Welcome~! We have a sale~!
[A memory they’ll remember even after going back to their busy life]
[Our dazzling sparkling story]
Whelk!
[Sometimes they got intense work, they had exhausting and hard days as well]
- OK, OK. Go go go!
- Do it slowly!
[Sometimes they got intense work, they had exhausting and hard days as well]
- Slowly!
- Slowly, slowly
[Sometimes they got intense work, they had exhausting and hard days as well]
Hurry up!
First floor!
[JO1 devoted themselves to work with a smile]
- Please say it again
- Once again~
[JO1 devoted themselves to work with a smile]
It’s really delicious! Uhm- in my opinion...
[Things might not work out well]
Delicious, right?
[But because they had each other, they created a lot more happy memories]
So good!
Nice, nice
Will you come here to work or to eat?
[Our story to be written as a page in our youth]
To eat!
[And this story now will be the start of that final page]
[What more events lie ahead for JO1 today?]
- We had a lot of fun yesterday, right?
- Yes!
- Takumi and I were in the market
- Yeah
- Selling seafood
- We were selling in the market
And we got a lot of orders
Amazing
- Like a big order or shellfish… How many were those?
- About 30 abalones
[Heaps of abalones]
- So, you measured them yourself and passed it to the customer?
- Yes
Some even pay using card
[Customer buy in bulk and FLEX with their card]
Amazing!
- We worked in the market similar to yours
- Ah, right!
But, what we did was completely different
What did you do?
- We moved out about 20-30 sea squirts
- 20-30?
Yes, 20-30 of them
(Pfft~)
We took them out and clean the water tank
[Sea cucumber CLEAR] - [Sea urchin CLEAR] - [Sashimi CLEAR]
[Triple SUCCESS]
The restaurant team was...
(Laughing already LOL)
We were battling with whelks
[Of course it’s about the whelks]
The whelks
We took out the guts from inside the shell...
[100 garlic cloves CLEAR] - [600 whelks CLEAR] - [3 bundles of shallot CLEAR]
[The 3 went through such a big workload without any complaints…]
[JO1 have a lot to say about their taxing part time job]
It was like an internship
[A lot to say, but they choose not to say them]
[What awaits them on their last day today…?]
Does anyone have any idea where we are going today?
(Clueless 1) (Clueless 2) (Clueless 3)
We don’t
- I want to have a slow day today~
- We have an instruction card!
[A mysterious message card appears!]
I’m going to read it
- Everyone, good morning!
- Good morning~ // - Hello!
I’m Kangnam, the representative of HELLO PARADISE travel agent
Ohh! Kangnam-san!
- Did you enjoy your 2 day and 1 night trip?
- Yes!
This is the last day of the trip!
For the last day, we’ve prepared a tournament to test your unity!
[Sounds fun~]
Let’s do our best~
[Let's go to unity tournament~]
Go go go~!
[JO1's unity tournament]
The umbrella flower has bloomed!
[Hiding, splitting, falling over]
[JO1 bringing out their wonderful teamwork]
[Finally arrived at today’s destination]
We’ve arrived
- Good day!
- Nice to meet you~
(Good to see you~)
Hello~
Hello!
My name is U, and I’m here to assist you with your unity tournament!
[Main dancer and sub-vocalist from 6 members boy group ONF]
[Name: U
Traits: 8 years in Korea
Skill: Flexible MC skill as great as his dancing]
[A warm welcome]
Thank you so much~
CEO Kangnam said this is your the last day of your trip
That’s why we’ve been instructed to make sure you have a good time
[That’s nice]
Thank you so much!
Well then, let’s go inside!
[The unity tournament will be held here!]
Wonderful! What is this?
There are some things
[What caught their eyes first are… mysterious gift boxes?!]
Presents?
[Winning team will get gifts for each game!]
We’ve prepared several games according to
the special theme of today’s unity tournament
The main theme of the tournament is…
The 3 virtues of boy groups!
First...
Cooperation
Second...
Chemistry
And third...
Physical strength
And hereby I announce JO1's 1st unity tournament in South Korea has started!
[Team Red: Sho, Keigo, Syoya, Shosei, Sukai
Team Blue: Ren, Ruki, Junki, Takumi, Shion, Mame]
[First Game (feat. Cooperation)]
(Gesture Game Rules)
[1. The playing team will sit in a row with their backs to the keyword]
[2. Only the first player can see the keyword]
[3. Giving clues to the next player with gestures only
(Strictly no speaking allowed)]
[4. The last player will answer the keyword
(Within 10 seconds)]
Let’s start from Team Red!
The time limit for each player is 10 seconds
We'll start it!
Ready~
[First keyword: Overalls]
- Go!
- It’s easy
This is tricky
This might be harder than it seems
[Sukai ⇒ Syoya]
(Jumps)
10!
(Runs)
9!
(And jump)
(Overalls) (Ah~ This one??)
- 8! 7!
- He did something
[A great start??]
Oh, that’s nice~ They’re doing great
[I bet he will mistake it as Mario *ros LOL]
[Syoya ⇒ Shosei]
(Runs and jumps)
Somehow it feels off
(Nose and mustache)
[Definitely turning into Super Mari*]
[We’re screwed…]
- Looks good~!
- 3, 2, 1. Next!
[Somehow the overalls are gone…]
Seems like it’s going in a different direction!
Stand up...
[Getting further away from the correct answer]
3, 2, 1! Next!
[Keigo ⇒ Sho]
Last one!
[Run and run, then gets bigger]
Make sure to express it properly~ Ah, this is...
(LOL)
[Where did the overalls go?]
Finished!
[Time’s up!]
Finished! Stop! Did you get it?
[Your answer, please!]
Let's go! 1, 2, 3!
Standing long jump!
(Huh?)
Wrong!
[There’s still time to answer…]
Really?
- You still have time!
- Go, go!
[Completely convinced it’s about Mario *ros]
- 2 seconds more!
- Leader!
Last chance!
Hide and seek!
[Team Red’s first turn was a failure!]
- Incorrect!
- They failed this one
It was already wrong since the start
From what I saw, since the start it was kind of…
[The cause for their failure]
This part...
[Uh-oh~;;]
The answer is… What’s the correct answer, Sukai-kun?
The answer is… Overalls
(What?)
(Bursts out laughing)
(What did i just hear?)
What I meant was Mari*’s… clothes!
[What the…]
I did think it was Mari*
It was Super Mari*!
[Still clueless]
You didn’t need to insert the character!
[Switch players!! ×2]
Change! x4
(I'm frustrated;;;)
[Team Red is already in a crisis]
The overalls were red though!
The order of the members have been changed!
[Urgent countermeasure: Team Red’s rotation]
(Demoted)
Give us the next keyword!
[Second keyword: Fish]
[Sho the first baton getting a lot of pressure]
Next~
Let's go! x2
(Half-hearted swimming)
That's not it, you know?
(Shark?)
Do it properly!
You can do more!
- Looking good!
- Your role is crucial!
[Predicting the outcome LOL]
[Wiggle wiggle… Horn (?)]
(Chomps~)
(LOL)
Oh? Looking good!
[Additional clue: Really big]
Nice~
[A perfect portrayal of a shark so far…]
- I see~
- It looks nice!
Good, good!
[What is this now???]
[Flapping paper doll…?]
(Sorry, kids LOL)
3!
(Chomps) (Chomps)
2!
1! Next~
(Confidently approves!!)
This isn't it
[A very confident relay of a wrong answer]
[Powerful shark]
Now, please give us your answer
Shark!
(That’s it!)
Wrong answer!
[It’s wrong??]
(Collective shock;;)
- Is that not it?
- No, it is not!
It’s over!
You're kidding, right?
[A collective protest for the clues]
What was this then?
The answer is: Fish
(...... Huh?)
(LOL)
(Horn)
- He really did something like this!
- That messed up everything
(Sheepish) (Sheepish)
- You should've done the (common) fish^^
- Yeah~
(Devastated;;;)
You volunteered yet you suck at it, too!
[Team Red, Round 1: 0 points...!]
[Next is Team Blue’s turn]
- Leave it to me!
- Let’s do this non-stop! // - OK!
- It’s gonna be fun
- Non-stop!
Are you confident you will win?
[Pretty confident]
It’s a piece of cake~ x3
Can you get 0 points?
(LOL)
Let’s start with the first keyword!
[First keyword: Seagull]
[How will Mame express a seagull?]
This is kinda…
This is hard;;
(Wing flaps)
(Alright, it’s a bird)
[At the top of the head… Horn (again)?]
(Flying) (Flying)
(Hmm...;;)
3, 2, 1!
There’s nothing else to describe it!
[Calmly relaying what he saw]
He’s rather calm
Looking good!
(What is it?)
Alright! 3...
(Great!)
- 2, 1!
- Looks good
- Good, good
- 2, 1. Next!
[Horn, walks slowly...]
- If you don’t get it...
- Stomp, stomp, stomp
Flaps flaps~
[Adding a powerful bite (?)...]
[Is this… What I think it is?]
[Not that one…]
This is bad! x3
[A very confident demonstration!] [Got it!]
- Nice, nice!
- OK
[Takumi has fallen to the conviction]
It’s getting messy
(Rooster comb)
[A perfect change from seagull to chicken]
[A perfect chicken…]
I see!
(Bursts out laughing)
[Biting off a chicken leg as the perfect last touch]
I knew it'd become like that
Chicken!
Wrong!
Huh? Uhm- That one. Pigeon!
[It’s wrong?]
HUH?!
(It was certainly like this, right?)
Last guess!
(Getting dizzy)
What is it exactly?
(Confused)
- So close!
- You can do it! x2
(Confused) (Confused)
- 3, 2, 1!
- Hold on! I really have no idea!
[Time’s up!]
It’s over!
Let’s announce the correct answer!
The answer is: Seagull
Seagull!
- So hard!
- Seagull, huh?
How did you demonstrate it, Mame?
- Can you understand this?
- That’s kinda hard to get…
I also thought it was a chicken
[A very confident relay of a wrong answer]
Next keyword, please!
[Second keyword: Shrimp]
(Relaxed laugh)
This one...
This will be easy
- You can do this! x2
- Isn't this nice?
He is...
(Jumps)
Ohh, nice!
(Jumps) (Jumps)
(So good)
That’s really nice
It’s really scary, though
- I heard a lot of noise
- Next!
[Did Ren get the correct answer?]
I heard a lot of noise
- I feel like the footsteps are getting close
- Scary
(Super flexible)
Really, um- huh?
(Kinda ambiguous;;)
- You can do it! x3
- That’s not it!
[Take the shrimp] [Peel it]
- Doing good!
- Like that!
[And eat~]
[Great!]
Next!
We’re gonna win this!
[Confident gesture]
[And eat again]
He ate it~
[This time eating cutely~]
Huh? I can’t tell what it is
[Shrimp party!]
Okay, stop! Next!
[Lying down imitating Ruki]
- Just gotta copy when you have no idea
- Nice, nice~
[Full power mukbang effect]
(Let's see)
Please shout the answer!
- Shrimp!
- Wah! Correct!
[Team Blue, Round 1: gets 1 point!]
[Round 1 Result]
(Team Red: 0 VS Team Blue: 1)
- Amazing!
- Well played~
[Gesture Game: Round 2]
Well, then!
Let’s start with Team Red again!
The first theme is: Emotions
[What kind of keyword will show up?]
It is emotion
Good luck!
[First keyword: Panic]
This is easy
[Looking at the watch... And panic...]
[Please help Syoya~;;]
Nice~
Looking good~!
(Oh~ OK!)
[Will they really get it correct this fast?]
They’re going fast
[Looking at the watch first]
So fast~
[Then panic]
(In a hurry)
(LOL)
[Endless running]
Was there such gesture? It changed
(First of all, OK)
[+ Expression, increasing the sense of urgency]
Well, it’s not bad~
[Gesturing to Sukai the last baton]
Last one~
[+ Adding lively expressions]
You got this!
[I got this]
Will they get it right?
In a hurry!
In a hurry. It’s close~
[In a hurry gesture?]
Uhm, in a... in a hurry?
[It’s not that?]
It's Heiwajima*
(*T/N: A hot spring in Tokyo. Junki made a connection
cause Sukai said "ase" (sweat) repeatedly)
- Close to that!
- Got no time!
- In a hurry. Uhm...
- 3!
- 2, 1!
- Nervous... Being late (?)! Sadness!
[Time’s up!]
Game over!
- The answer is: Panic!
- Ah~ I see! // - That's right
The second theme is: Animals
I got it
[Second keyword: Sloth]
It’s going to be difficult
- It’s going to be difficult
- It is
[Getting straight to gesturing]
(This could possibly be…?)
(Sluggish) (Sluggish)
[“Syoyanimal” gesturing with his whole body]
[“Syoyanimal” walks too slow then lies down]
Excellent!
[You get it, right?]
Well done!
It’s exactly like the answer! Next!
[I guess I’ll relay it first]
Great!
[Right to the next player]
[Full demonstration of being sluggish]
Oh? Okay, okay
He got it
- Way to go!
- Go, go!
(Sluggish) (Sluggish)
- Look at that!
- Shosei, look at it!
(I think I know) (Or maybe not)
3!
[The gesture has changed to a turtle]
2, 1! Next!
It might be heading to the wrong direction!
It's kind of dangerous
- An animal // - Please...
- This is dangerous
(Surprised Sukai)
It’s a bit different, isn’t it?
(LOL)
[Oho... What is this gesture?]
[Oh? This is?!]
[Innovative]
Amazing!
- Time’s almost up!
- Sloth! // - Correct!
[Finally Team Red gets 1 point!]
- Correct!
- Wonderful!
Really?
[Great game, Shosei!]
Nice one, Shosei!
- I took a risk and gave it a shot
- Wonderful!
[Scoring their first point with Shosei’s great effort]
That was really great, Shosei!
[Team Red moves on to the next keyword with great momentum!]
I'm glad
[Third keyword: Elephant]
(Looong nose)
(Gets it right away)
[Long nose] [Big ears]
Sho-kun, do your best!
- Elephant!
- Correct!
[Fourth keyword: Short track race]
[Short distance, runs]
[It seems closer to a sprint than a short track race...]
100 meters race!
(Just trying to guess whatever)
Red light, green light
(Wrong!)
Time’s up!
[Fifth keyword: OO]
Oh? That’s great!
[Dear viewers, please try to guess too!]
Ah, that was nice
[Will they be able to get it right in one go?]
Please answer!
- Sumo!
- Correct!
(Acknowledges the opponent’s strength)
We did it!
[Team Red, Round 2: gets 3 points!]
We did it! x2
[Player change from Mame to Junki]
- It’s the last round so Junki-nim will rotate in Team Blue
- Yes!
The first theme is: Sports
Let’s start!
[First keyword: Fencing]
I'll leave it to you, guys
This is easy
[Junki starts gesturing]
[Get the correct answer!]
(I see~)
(Show me more)
Great~
(Take this!)
(Stronger!)
(So cute~)
1! Next!
[Additional detail: Protective equipment]
(Swoosh!) (Swoosh!)
(I get this~)
Alright x5
[Go get the correct answer!]
I got it
[Take this!]
That’s dangerous!
[Scared with the continuous correct answer attack]
That was dangerous!
Dangerous! x5
[You get the answer, right?]
[What a menacing look! I’ll be damned if I fail LOL]
So scary. But...!
[Excellent gesturing skill]
I get it! x2
[Takumi continues the correct answer attack]
I see~
[Smiles brightly from the well explained gestures]
- Fencing // - Correct!
- We did it!
[A great kick-starter for Team Blue]
Nice nice!
The second theme is: Emotions
Let’s start!
[Second keyword: Excited]
Fighting!
[The unexpected raise in difficulty level is causing headache]
- I beg you, please
- Wah! This...
This is difficult;;
(Found something!)
(Ay~ Nice~)
(What is that...?)
[Expressing excitement in his best effort]
This sounds wrong
[What’s happening? What is this ominous feeling...]
I can’t see where this is going
[I don’t get what it is, but it seems fun]
3, 2, 1!
(It’s good, though?)
Next!
(Discovers x2)
(Happy x∞)
(Super happy)
[She is dying from laughter]
(What is this LOL)
(LOL)
Amazing!
[Can’t be more excited than this]
- Great! x2
- He is dancing x2
- You’re doing too much!
- 2, 1!
(Sighs)
Next!
Will he be relaying all that?
[Firstly, start gesturing]
[Take this!] [Excitement!]
(Confused...)
[It’s hilarious LOL]
It feels kind of wrong!
[Super high tension...]
It is kind of wrong!
[Eventhough his gesture looks so happy]
[Suddenly switches to a straight face… Let's do well~]
(Confused) (Scared)
So scary. Since earlier...
[Logging out from the enthusiastic gesturing]
He's doing it again
Next!
[Can you see my excitement?]
[Looks excited even from behind]
(Astonished)
It's a bit off. Look!
3!
(Get the correct answer, okay?)
2, 1!
Your answer, please!
High tension?
Ah… So close!
(That was wrong…?)
3, 2!
- Drunk?
- Wrong! 1!
- It's impossible!
- It's over!
[Failed to answer!]
It was difficult
The answer is: Excited
He was properly gesturing excitement at the start
From being excited, it somehow turned into this in the process
[Who was the culprit?]
How come?
I thought it was like “I found something! Yay!”
It turned to be like this on my turn
(Embarrassed) (Embarrassed)
[Third keyword: Frilled-neck lizard]
[Gesturing a monstrous frilled-neck lizard (?)]
[Hearing the sound alone is already scary…]
- I don’t know!
- Scary!
[Junki lizard appeared the second]
(Came to his senses)
[Lizards appearing here and there]
(Sta~re)
(Came to his senses x2)
- Gecko!
- Wrong!
Salamander!
[A regrettable failure!]
Time’s up!
[Fourth keyword: Kangaroo]
Okay!
[Mama kangaroo taking care of baby kangaroo]
[Boxing champion kangaroo]
[The kangaroo itself!]
- Kangaroo!
- Kangaroo... Correct!
[Easy success as the result of perfect harmony!]
- It’s correct!
- Y’all so good at this! // - My neck...
Next keyword, please!
[Fifth keyword: Broom]
[Mame started with an intuitive gesture]
I feel like there was a lot of movements
[Gesturing continues really well]
[Suddenly wiping the floor…?]
(What’s with this gesture?)
Good, good
[Gesturing continues to drift off in an unexpected direction...]
(Wavering eyes)
He's grasping
(Sweeps) (Wipes)
I get it~ x2
Swipe, wipe, then throw away?
[The broom disappears in the process...]
This is regretful
[A vacuum cleaner appears?!]
Vacuum cleaner?
It's so wrong!
- Cleaning equipment!
- Wrong!
- Rag!
- Ah, close!
- Uhm...
- Go, go!
(Please…!)
3, 2...
1!
How would I know?
(Too bad ㅠㅠ)
The correct answer is: Broom
- Ahh… Sorry! My bad!
- You did it too much
[Round 2 Result]
(Team Red: 3 VS Team Blue: 2)
[Gesture game result: Both teams get 1 turn in encampment game]
[There are 11 gifts in total]
[The encampment game’s mission is to get the gift boxes]
(Encampment Game Rules)
[The winning team pick 3 players for the game]
[The players claim an area and get the gift
by spreading their legs as wide as possible]
[They’ll get the gift if they can keep their legs still until they are marked!]
[Which team will win more gift boxes?]
Ah, it hurts!
[Be careful that being greedy might cause a painful split!]
We’ll start the encampment game
Let’s start from Team Red
[Team Red players: Sho, Keigo, Sukai]
1, 2, 3!
[Which box is Team Red’s target?]
- Which box do you aim for?
- There are long ones
Shall we go with that?
[Team Red chooses the red box]
Do you think we can do it?
- The red one
- Of course!
Fighting!
- I feel like my pants will rip
- Yeah?
It’s okay to rip your pants
It's fine
- Then I’ll start
- Yes!
Just like that!
You have long legs!
[Utilizing his long legs, gently stretching for the box]
You have it easy!
You gotta make a proper circle
Okay, okay! Looking good! x3
We may not need to stretch so much
Last player!
They can do it easily
Are you done?
Please keep your position, I’m checking it
[The 3 have successfully connected!]
Please mark it quickly!
[It’s a success if they can hold on until the area marking is done!]
Just a bit more, a bit more
(Holding on)
[A line is drawn to mark the area...]
[Team Red gets the gift and the area]
You get 1 gift from this
[Team Red successfully gets a gift box!]
Which box will the Team Blue aim for?
[Which box is the Team Blue’s target?]
Just now...
It might be good to aim for that one
[What’s the Team Blue’s strategy?]
Seems like that one is a cake
Then, I’ll go first
- Yes, nice~
- The first player
[Ren is done splitting]
- 3 people! - // - Yeah
- Are you done?
[2nd player: Junki]
- That’s quite far // - If we expand ourselves enough...
- We can do this. We can go even further! x2
- Looking good! // - They can get 2 boxes at once
- Junki-kun, do your best!
(Help me)
More! x4
Shion! Spread (your legs) more!
He’s stiff
Just a little bit more! x5
Okay! Let’s check!
[Can they keep that position?]
- Nice!
- Keep the position!
Please be quick!
[Reaching his limit]
Please hurry up!
Junki-kun is amazing!
[Reaching their limit]
- 2 seconds till I fall
- They're about to break! Break for real
(Trembling) (Trembling)
(Please be faster ㅠㅠ)
- It's wide
- Hold on~
Yeay~
[Area marking for Team Blue done]
- Amazing!
- We did it~
(I did it!)
[Team Red and Team Blue both get 1 gift box each]
For the first round of the encampment game
Both teams won 1 gift box!
[Second Game (feat. Chemistry)]
(Member Q&A Knee Race Rules:)
[1. MC reads a question about a member]
What does Takumi-kun like...?
[2. The member who knows the answer
comes forward on their knees to answer]
Go! x4
[3. If they can answer correctly, they’ll get 1 turn in the encampment game!]
Please answer!
Since there’ll be one extra player
That player will be a "kkakdugi" (reserve player)
and be the assistant referee instead
[Welcoming volunteers]
Who’s willing to help me?
I am a "kkakdugi"
[Takumi gets to the referee position]
[Takumi / 1-day referee]
(A fair referee and a "kkakdugi")
Well then, let’s start with the first question!
What is JO1 members' favorite fruit?
- ...favorite fruit?
- Go go go!
I really have no idea
Go, Syoya go!
(Stomp stomp stomp)
Sukai is so fast!
- He's so fast!
- Go, Syoya go!
[Attack on Sukai]
So quick!
Isn't that so quick?
[Only Team Red's members are present]
- Line up properly, kids!
- Please, let us know the answer
(Curious) (Curious)
Let's answer in unison!
(You know, right?)
Answer in unison!
- One, two! Strawberry!
- Correct!
[Team Red successfully gets the first correct answer]
Nice!
[JO1's favorite fruit that was revealed in one of their contents: Strawberry]
(Source: Hi! JO1 on YouTube)
(I love strawberries)
This is so delicious
[Checking the answer: JO1 loves strawberries]
[Current Score]
(Team Red: 1 VS Team Blue: 0)
Now, Team Red just gotten 1 point!
Second question
Which member has the biggest hand? AND what's their hand measurement?
(How am I supposed to know that?)
[Ren from Team Blue swiftly charges]
Good luck, Ren-kun!
[Sho following Ren right after]
Go, go!
(He's fast!)
Wow, Ren-kun!
(Should I press?) (Should I not?)
(Buzz!)
What's the answer?
- Sho-kun, and his hand size is... 28 cm!
- Isn't that too big? // - You're wrong!
- Please go back
- Let's go~
[Sho's turn to answer]
Alright, what's the answer?
- I'm the one with the biggest hand... And it's 21cm!
- Correct!
[Continuously getting correct answers, Team Red is off with a great start!]
Leader! Leader! x2
Let's try comparing Sho-kun's hands with Junki-kun's
[Spontaneous inspection time]
With Sho-kun's?
[Comparing hand sizes]
Huge!
So big~
[WOW]
Let's move on~
Let's go!
Back when Junki-kun was in elementary school
What did he do to receive an award?
I dunno
Well then, let's start!
This is difficult…
Yeay!
[Ruki moves forward]
- Huh? I don't even know it myself!
- Ruki knows?
(Ruki), good luck!
(Buzz!)
Your answer, please!
[What will Ruki's answer be?]
- Wearing short sleeves all year long
- Correct!
[The person in question was surprised]
- Wearing short sleeves all year long
- Correct!
(Surprised party)
(Amazing)
What? What is it again?
You mentioned that in Hi! JO1 before, right?
That you were wearing short sleeves all year long
[That's right!]
- This is wonderful!
- Splendid!!
(That deserves a round of applause)
[This was easy]
Were you wearing short sleeves for a whole year?
I had been wearing short sleeves to school all year long
And I got a "healthy student" award for that
Wow~
Let’s give him a round of applause
- Applause~
- Really?
[Checking the answer: Junki was a healthy elementary student]
How does Ren-kun’s family celebrate the new year?
(Easy peasy)
- So hard!
- This is Ren-kun's turn
So fast!
Good! Good~
What's your answer?
Jumping!
That's what I usually do!
(LOL)
[They're going at it again]
What's that?
[Banging with his forehead]
And the answer is?
Eating homemade soba
Who makes the soba?
- His grandfather!
- Correct!
[Current Score]
(Team Red: 2 VS Team Blue: 2)
What’s Takumi-kun’s favorite season?
[Junki’s guess]
- Junki knows!
- What’s the answer?
- Winter!
- Correct!
[Current Score]
(Team Red: 2 VS Team Blue: 3)
What does Syoya-kun always eat on the New Year?
[Syoya VS Ruki]
Go go go!
(Thud!)
[Close combat]
[The agile Syoya got to answer first]
What’s the answer?
- Amazake*!
- Correct!
(*T/N: Sweet low-alcohol Japanese drink from fermented rice)
[Current Score]
(Team Red: 3 VS Team Blue: 3)
What is Mame-kun’s star sign?
(It’s about me)
[The person in question takes the chance]
Mame, go get it!
Gemini!
- It is correct!
- Really?
- What is Junki’s usual bath temperature?
- It's yours!
[A chaos LOL]
(Crawls)
(Intense fight)
[Shosei pressed the button first by a close margin!]
- Team Red!
- 43 degree!
Correct!
[Absentminded]
[Current Score]
(Team Red: 4 VS Team Blue: 4)
Now, the last!
Then, for the last question!
- What does Ruki’s…
- Bring it on!
- Let's go! // - Leggo!
- There are a lot of questions
- What does Ruki’s family do on New Year?
- Wait, I dunno!
[Not Ruki but Ruki’s family]
His family?
Not what Ruki does, but his family
Ruki’s family?
I don’t even know it myself ㅠㅠ
(Uncertain) (Uncertain)
[What was it...]
New Year?
He just went ahead first, can he even answer?
[Sho takes a shot]
What’s the answer?
Going to the grandma’s house
Wrong! They don’t~
[Ren gives it a try!]
Cleaning the castle!
Cleaning the castle is incorrect!
[Cleaning the castle seems plausible for Prince Ruki]
That’s close
[Keigo gives it a shot!]
Riding a horse!
- Yes?
- Riding a horse!
Correct!
Yaay~
No way! Really?
He did say that
That’s what a real prince does~
Now with this, Team Red…
- They get 5 turns for the encampment game!
- 5 turns?
It’s a bit unfortunate for Team Blue
[Team Blue gets 4 turns for the encampment game!]
But they get 4 turns!
(That ain’t bad~)
That much is enough
[The winner for Members' Q&A Knee Race is Team Red]
[Encampment game, Round 2]
[The current area marked by each team]
(Top: Team Blue's zone) (Bottom: Team Red's zone)
Let’s start the 2nd round of the encampment game!
We’ll start from Team Red who won the Q&A quiz
And from there, they will do rock-paper-scissors to determine the turns
[Team Red’s players: Keigo, Shosei, Syoya]
- Let’s go!
- Let's start from there
This will be good, don’t you think?
[This is impossible]
That sounds hard!
[Choosing a strategy to expand existing area]
- Let’s start from me
- Oh, I see
- OK!
- Just a little bit more
Oh, now the length is...!
Okay, stop!
Looking good!
[Shosei the last player has finished, too]
[This time they’re not pushing themselves for the area]
OK! Please, check it!
[Team Red’s area has expanded…]
[The number of gift boxes they’ve gotten so far]
(Team Red: 2 VS Team Blue: 1)
[RPS to determine the next turn]
- Let’s do this~
- Alright
Rock, paper, scissors!
(Win)  (Lose)
[Team Red gets the next turn to play again!]
(Gloomy;;)
Shion, you are the best~
Since Team Red won the RPS, please go for another turn!
[The tall trio strikes again!]
Oh, you’ve reached the box. Now, stay still!
[The strategy to continuously expand their area upwards]
- It’s connected!
- This is easy
- Yay!
- This way...
[The number of gift boxes they’ve gotten so far]
(Team Red: 3 VS Team Blue: 1)
- Team Red gets another box!
- Thank you!
Rock paper scissors! x2
[Takumi wins!]
Please send out 3 members from Team Blue
- How about this?
- Yup
[Team Blue’s target gift box]
- Can we reach this?
- How are we gonna reach that?
Let’s do it the same way with before
Ah, but I guess it’s impossible?
You can do it! x3
- It’s impossible
- No. It's possible x2
Will they fail for their greed?
Or will they succeed in getting 2 boxes at once?
Alright, then. Ready?
If we can’t, we’ll just go for one
[100% sure to succeed]
No, we’ll definitely nail this
- Ready?
- Yes
[Aiming for 2 boxes to turn the tide]
This will be hard getting in one go
[Ruki’s solid determination to get 2 boxes]
- Awesome!
- Good luck! You got this! x2
Hold on!
The hand is touching (the ground)! x3
Dangerous! x4
It's dangerous!
[Speeding up due to Ruki’s crisis]
Faster, faster
Nice!
[Mame the 2nd player reaching far with his legs, too]
Looking good!
Okay. Next, next!
[Nice, our team!]
Next, next!
(Distress)
(Joy)
[Quickly marking the area]
Amazing!
[Perfectly connected legs]
You got this! Hang on there!
(Shudder) (Shudder)
[But the pain grows as the time passes]
- Takumi is amazing // - He is
Please be faster!
It has become this wide
[Team Blue getting 2 boxes in one swoop!]
- Ah, it's heavy x2
- Good game!
[Who will win the next RPS? Team Blue wins]
- Rock, paper, scissors!
- Yayy!
[Once again! Team Blue aims for 2 boxes!]
- Awesome~
- How could they do that?
How do we do this?
[Just a little bit more to get the big box…!]
[Oh~ That worked]
It’s mostly just his butt there
[Gasping in awe at Team Blue's high level skills (?)]
Please check them!
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Team Red’s turn to catch up and surpass the other team]
Here I go~
[Keigo & Sho the long-legged duo up for the challenge]
It’s still not enough!
- Nice, nice!
- Very nice~
(Gets 2 gift boxes)]
[Only 1 gift box left]
Let’s do another RPS!
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Team Blue wins!]
Alright~
It’s fine!
Oh my~
[Team Blue moving for the last box]
- We'll win this
- Yes!
Honestly, I think we can do this with just 2 people
(Okay) (Got it)
[Ren reaches with his legs first]
[Takumi the next player comes in]
They’ll get it like this
Do your best, Takumi!
[Will they succeed with just 2 people…?]
Please check it!
[Please, save my team members!]
Please!
Junki, go support Takumi!
[Hurry up in checking!]
[For some reason it feels like time moves so slowly]
Please hurry up!
He’s dying! He’s gonna break!
One gift box successfully captured~
[Finally, Team Blue successfully got the last gift box]
[Acknowledges the game]
- Nice!
- Great game!
[Team Blue is the winner of the encampment game]
Fighting, fighting!
Team Blue got 6 boxes, and Team Red got 5 boxes!
With this, the winner of the encampment game is Team Blue!
[You’ve done well~]
[Final Score]
(Team Blue: 6 VS Team Red: 5)
[Coming soon]
Where~ are you?
Where~ are you~
So scary.. ㅠㅠ
I'm scared
No one's here
This box?
[Hide well, JO1]
Or this box?
Where are they? x2
[A game beyond your imagination]
Camera! There's a camera!
[A game to decide attack or defense position for the final game]
- The Umbrella Flower Has Bloomed -
[1. Various shapes of umbrellas are laid out at the starting line]
[2. Choose an umbrella by its handle (Some are better than others)]
[3. Pass the finish line without being discovered by the taggers]
The umbrella flower has bloomed!
[The team with most members past the finish line wins]
Get ready!
[It's getting physical even before the game starts]
Hey!
Set, go!
[Umbrella lucky draw, START]
1, 2!
[Intense brawling LOL]
[Everyone choosing an umbrella they like]
3, 4!
5, 6!
[Got a long umbrella!]
- This is too small
- 7!
[Evident misfortune concluded from the size]
Did everyone get one?
[Umbrella lucky draw complete]
Well then, open your umbrellas!
[Syoya pulled a cute, yellow umbrella!]
[Junki and Shosei got fitting umbrellas]
[Keigo - Fancy umbrella] [Sukai - Big umbrella]
So small
[All eyes on me, I am Shion]
- Cute!
- Huh?!
(Huh? Something's not right)
[Got a torn-up umbrella!]
This doesn't stay open!
(LOL)
Takumi!
[Takumi is perplexed]
What's that?
Then shall I close mine? I won't open mine either
[How will Team Blue's fate play out with the misfortunate pulls?]
Taggers, are you ready?
[Preparation completed]
We are ready!
[Without being discovered by the other team's tagger]
[Pass the finish line!]
(It's hopeless...)
- I'm...
- Ready?
Go!
The umbrella flowers has-
[Fast advance while hiding their bodies]
(Careful) (Careful)
(Stealthy) (Stealthy)
♪ The umbrella flower has bloomed ♪
Okay!
(LOL)
[Hide well, JO1]
[Iron wall]
[They are making the best out of it~]
[What are those umbrellas LOL]
Please do RPS!
Rock, paper, scissors!
(Lost) (Won)
[Team Blue's tagger Ren will choose first]
[It's not easy regardless of the order]
[Not even a strand of hair is visible]
[Rainbow umbrella with awkward position]
(Oof-)
(Slumps)
[The red vest is exposed]
The rainbow umbrella is, Keigo!
(Unsure) (Uncertain)
The rainbow umbrella, Keigo-kun. Will that be correct?
If it is, please reveal yourself!
[Correct!]
[King of intuition, Ren]
Yes!!
(Bummer)
- It was right
- Awesome!
[Team Red's Keigo, out!]
Out, Keigo is out
[Team Red's Sho's turn to choose]
Next, it's Team Red's turn
'Kay! Uhm...
All or nothing!
The blue (striped umbrella) is... Mame!
The blue is Mame! If it's correct, please come out!
[Correct!]
[The class of the leader]
[Team Blue's Mame is out!]
- You got the right answer
- Wonderful! // - This way...
Each team has gotten one point
[Current Survivors]
(Team Red: 3  - Team Blue: 3)
Let's continue right away
Please turn around
Let's start the second round
Get set, go!
The umbrella flower has-
[Sprinting umbrellas]
[Frantic rush]
(Flops)
-bloomed!
(LOL)
The umbrella flower has bloomed!
(Fall flat;;)
[Throwing their body to hide]
[I'm doomed LOL]
[Dying from laughter]
Please do RPS
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Team Red's Sho will choose first]
Okay, Team Red
(Doing the best they could)
The rabbit umbrella is Shion
If the rabbit umbrella is Shion, please step forward
(Darn it!)
[Team Blue's Shion is out!]
- Correct!
- It was impossible
(LOL)
Team Red got one point. Now, Team Blue!
[Team Blue's tagger Ren's turn!]
[The finish line is not far away]
[He must find a Team Red's member!]
[Team Red is nervous]
Eiffel Tower? The red umbrella
(Oh no... I'm in your team)
No, no...
(The red umbrella is) Sukai!
Is the red umbrella Sukai-kun?
(Silent~)
Oh, it's not!
You got it wrong
[What have I done?]
[Current Survivors]
(Team Red: 3 VS Team Blue: 2)
Let's move onto the next round. Please turn your back
(Look over there)
It's too revealing
[Strong will to survive]
Get set, go!
The umbrella flower has bloomed!
[Everyone is about to pass the finish line]
Are they in? Is that an in?
No, not yet!
You have to be out of the zone
[Has to completely go over the green line]
Then, please play RPS
Rock, paper, scissors!
(Won) (Lost)
- Aigo!
- Okay, Team Blue!
The red umbrella was not Sukai earlier, right?
[Choice that carries the fate of Team Blue]
(Still alive)
- Yellow umbrella-
- The yellow umbrella!
It's Syoya!
Is the yellow umbrella Syoya? Three-
Two, one!
[Correct!]
[Syoya got picked]
You got it right~
[Team Red's Syoya is out!]
That means Team Blue has taken one point
Team Red!
- Eiffel Tower
- The Eiffel Tower!
- It's Junki
- Junki-kun
[Correct!]
[Team Blue's Junki is out!]
- How did you know?
- Team Red took one point
I can't believe it
He is about to pass
But nobody is past the finish line yet
- So, we'll play another round
- Okay
[Current Survivors]
(Team Red: 2 VS Team Blue: 1)
Get set, go!
(Team Red Takumi, IN)  (Team Blue Shosei, IN)
The umbrella flower has bloomed!
[Sukai passed the finish line as well!]
Oh, my legs...
Goal x4
[Final Result]
Team Red: 2 persons, Team Blue: 1 person
Team Red will get to choose whether to attack or defense first!
[The long-awaited final game]
[Gigantic cardboard box]
[Mysterious boxes that will be used at the final game]
[What kind of game are they preparing?]
Finally, today's highlight!
We'll start "A Box Flower Has Bloomed"
[Ta-da!]
- Members, take a look at this!
- Oh, wow~!
[Today's competition's highlight]
[Among the numerous boxes]
[Find JO1 who's hiding!]
(Guess where am I?)
A Box Flower Has Bloomed
(a.k.a A Hibiscus Flower Has Bloomed)
[The game stage is divided into Zone A, B, and C]
[1. The pursuer team counts down from 10]
[2. The fugitive team hides inside the boxes
(Can advance to one zone per round)]
[3. The pursuer team opens boxes once
per person and finds the fugitive team]
[Pursuit fails if there's no fugitive inside the box]
[Pursuit is successful if there's a fugitive inside the box]
[The team with the most members past the finish line wins]
- Are you ready?
- Yes!!
Team Blue will attack first. Fighting!
[Burning passion]
[Real game STARTS!]
[Team Red chose to hide (defense) first]
Hello. It's itchy (?)
- Everyone, let's do our best!
- Yeah!
[Fighting!]
- We'll do our best
- Our best!
[First Round - Hide within Zone A only]
(Rushes)
[The cameras are shaking uncontrollably]
[Deception skill: He moves other boxes]
[Finished hiding within 10 seconds!]
(The heart is pounding)
(Nervous)
[The fugitive team, shush~]
[They hide just as the countdown was finishing!]
Okay, let's go!
10 seconds are up. Please go find them!
[First round pursuit starts!]
(Zone A - Zone B - Zone C)
[To Zone A where the fugitive team is hiding~]
- They'll be in Zone A // - They are only in A now, right?
[You just wait]
Where are you?
[It's time to choose a box per person]
[Sho is in here]
(Sniffs sniffs)
(I can smell something suspicious)
Are you here~?
[Even breathing needs to be cautious inside the box]
Where are you?
[Takumi & Shion do not have a clue yet]
- Maybe two people are hiding inside one box
- That's a possibility
[Will they succeed in finding the fugitive team?]
I feel like someone might be in here
This one moved a lot
[Suspicious locations no matter how you look]
(Covers his mouth)
Someone pushed these aside
Really?
- And went inside one of these
- Yeah, I think somebody is in here
- Really?
- Probably... It looks like it moved a little
- This one looks easy to get in
- Well- It does look easy
[This is a sure thing]
Somebody's definitely in here. This is the most definite
They went like this
[Simulation of the fugitive team's possible route]
- Then here
- Yup! Somebody's definitely in here!
Definitely!
We are catching you!
- They couldn't have hidden in here, right?
- Yeah, it looks hard to get in
(Phew... They are going away)
(Relaxed) (Nervous)
Could it be this?
Could it be this? x2
Could it be this? x3
Could it be this? x4
Could it be this? x5
This one is suspicious, too! It's crumpled
[Tries to hear the breathing, examines the boxes]
[This is quite a mystery...]
Now, please stand in front of the box of your choice
[Time to choose a box]
- What about this? Someone could be in here?
- Have you decided?
- Let's go!
- Are you ready?
It's time to reveal the inside of your box
- We'll start with Issei-kun
- Okay! Leggo!
Let's see whether there's a person inside the box or not!
[Impending box opening]
One!
[What will be the fate of the fugitive team?]
Two!
Three!
[The pursuer team's Mame opens the box]
Open!
[The first result for the fugitive team is?!]
- Ah~ It's empty;;
- It's empty!
(Relieved;;)
It was empty
- Ah~ It's empty;;
- It's empty!
(We survived!)
It was empty
Open!
[Empty box-]
- Ah~ It's empty!
- It's empty!
(What a shame)
The first box was empty. Next up is-
[Ren's turn to open]
Ren-kun! Let's open a box
(Thinking) (Thinking)
Now, until the box open...
Three!
Two!
This one moved a lot
[The box that was on his mind]
[Ren's choice will be?]
(Please...!)
Until the box open... Three! Two!
[Ren agonized until the very last minute]
One! Open!
It's empty!
[Empty box-]
It's empty~
No one's here
It's empty!
[The pursuer team is not even near the fugitive team]
- It's empty~
- This is harder than we thought // - No one's here
[All members survived!]
- Two people have failed
- Amazing! x2
Open!
[Shion & Ruki failed at choosing the right boxes as well!]
- Open! // - Empty
- For real? // - There was no one inside!
No way!
This is not good
[4 out of 5 members have failed]
No one's here
- No way!
- This is not good
We chose wrong ones
(This is going good)
To find Team Red members-
[The pursuer team's last chance in the first round]
There's one more chance. Please be aware~
Junki-kun!
[The pursuer team is feeling pressured due to the consecutive mistakes]
[Currently all of the fugitive team have survived]
Junki-kun, let's pick a box! The last choice of the first round
[Last person to choose! Junki's choice is?]
One, two, three!
[Junki opens!]
Open!
[The result is...]
Three! Open!
(Yes!!!)
Open!
(I've got you)
(Darn...)
Sukai!
(We found him!)
(Yay!)
He's cute
(Then I shall runaway..)
[First elimination, Sukai!]
Nice, Junki-kun!
(That was close-)
(Sukai... Goodbye...)
[Playzone extends to Zone B]
(Zone A - Zone B - Zone C)
(Syoya's Camera)
(Sho's Camera)
(Keigo's Camera)
(Shosei's Camera)
[He advances with amazing speed at the beep]
(Syoya's Camera)
[The fugitive team has to hide within the time limit]
Go, go, go!
(Stomps~) (Fumbles~) (Bumps~)
Do your best! x4
(What's happening...? LOL)
Go, go, go!
(Peeks?)
(Slides-)
(BEEP-)
Then, please go find them!
[Second round pursuit starts!]
- It's Zone B, right?
- They can hide in both B and A, right?
[The play area is expanded to Zone B]
- They may be in B, or can be in A as well
- They can be in A, too
Ah, I see
[The pursuer team looks for movements of the boxes]
I have a feeling they are in B
[The fugitive team has settled in Zone A]
[A lonely box in a random place]
I have a feeling they are in B
- Wait, the boxes are messed up
- Really
[Trying to calm his breath]
They've moved a lot
Something must have happened here
[One can tell by the looks of it, what harrowing incident took the place]
- This is suspicious
- It is
But it may be a trap
May be a trap~
But that means they must be around here
- Yeah, they must have hit the boxes here
- That's true
They won't go to the far side after making a mess here
This makes sense
[Meticulous investigation]
[The fugitive team is only suspecting Zone B]
I'm gonna choose this
[What will be the result of round 2?]
- Please choose one box per person
- I'm gonna choose this
I'll feel bad if I don't pick this
- This...
- That's true
[At the risk of being fooled, Ruki chooses the suspicious box]
- No good, I have a bad feeling
- Boo!!
I'm having a bad feeling
[The pursuer team is done deciding]
- Okay?
- Shion!
[Mame will open the first box]
Let's open the boxes one by one
Three!
[Empty box-]
Oh, no one's there
The first box was empty
(This is not going well;;)
We'll move onto the second box
Open!!
[Empty box-]
No one's here
[This is bad;;]
There's no one
- They are good!
- None has been found yet
- Nice~
- This is difficult
(Relieved) (Relieved)
It means Team Red is good at hiding
Heart throbbing
[Hearing the good news that each other is alive]
[Third box, Ren's turn to open]
Let's check the next box
Open!
Empty!
Another empty box! It was empty
No one has been found yet
[Team Blue continuously fails to catch]
- It was empty
- This is difficult
- Next up is...
- Junki!
They are still in there
[It's the pursuit team's Junki's turn]
Let's open a new box
- Someone might be in there, Junki
- There's heat. I can feel the heat
(You can feel the heat? LOL)
He said there's heat coming from the box
[Wrong!]
[The box is empty this time as well]
It's empty~
[Every pursuit team member failed to catch so far]
- This is difficult
- I really want to catch // - They are not in here...
- Then, shall we go, Ruki-kun?
- Yes!
We would like to catch one now
Until the box open... 3, 2, 1!
(Please) (Expectant)
Open~
[The fugitive team is holding their breath]
Until the box open... 3, 2, 1!
Open!
[Keigo is found from the mysterious box!]
[Thank God]
[Spot on~!]
One person is found!
Was I that far away?
Very!
[How did Keigo end up here...]
[Rewind to before the 2nd round started]
Do your best! x5
(Keigo)
Go! x3
(Keigo is passing~)
(My perfect plan...)
[A theoretically perfect plan by Keigo...]
(All by himself)
(Happy cheers)
You were there!
One person is found!
[Too bad, Keigo is eliminated!]
(Shosei plans on staying)
[Sho & Syoya move to Zone B]
(Pushes- hits)
[Syoya employs deception strategy]
[The remaining three of the fugitive team finished hiding!]
[The pursuit team begins their investigation!]
It's easy to tell
[Guessing the routes by the movements of the boxes]
- They were here and then they came out
- They came out and-
- I think they came out from there and went into either of these two
- I do think they have come from that way to here
What do you think? Do you think they are there? Or not? Mame-kun
- I think they are here!
- He is very sure
Three!
[Help me, please~]
(LOL)
- Someone's definitely in here
- Why? Why?
(LOL)
(Pulls-)
I wonder why?
[Nice to meet you LOL]
[Thanks to Mame, fugitive Syoya is arrested]
I knew it...
[Three eliminations during three rounds]
[The remaining members are only two!]
[Run with all your might!]
[Shosei runs to Zone C in one breath]
(Slow) (Slow)
(Haste) (Haste)
[The fugitive team finished hiding!]
[The pursuer team turns around right away]
(Wiggle) (Wiggle)
[Knock, knock, knock... Hello..?]
(LOL)
Oh, come on~
[The pursuer team heads to the scene]
Oh my god! Oh my god!
[What in the world happened?]
[What... happened to you... Sho?]
[Sho had a shaky start]
(Urges extremely)
[While he was hurrying to get in, he got caught by the box]
[That's what happened.. LOL]
[Those who laugh in hard times are of the highest standing -Sho Box-]
[Takumi is speechless (?) after witnessing the accident scene]
[Spectators (?) are starting to gather~]
[Ruki covers up the accident LOL]
Good!
Let's go find!
(We know nothing)
- We didn't see anything x2
- Let's find them!
[Take a rest for now LOL]
[They are keeping Sho for now and leave to find Shosei]
- There was a sound around here
- Judging by the footsteps
- There was one around here too
- We got two people to find
Two people
[The pursuer team focusing on Zone C where the sound came from]
- This is difficult // - One person around here
- These- // - Around here or...
[Shosei sprinted from Zone A to Zone C in one breath]
[Currently, Shosei is located somewhere in Zone C]
- Judging by the sound I think it was around here
- Right
This one is suspicious, too
These two
We only have two people, so we can attack all of these boxes
All four people?
- Can four people go out?
- That's a bold movement if we can do that
- If we don't get it he'll pass the line
- Yes, we'll lose in the next round
The middle would be too narrow
[The first to open is Junki]
So, Junki-kun
I feel like... Someone could be in here
(Just hurry up and open it...)
- It was moving a lot
- We tried to look over
(Just hurry up and open it...)
- Should I open it?
- Well, then
Open!
(Embarrased-)
[Sho is here]
That was fast!
- Hello!
- Hello?
- Please tell us how it was
- How it was?
Moving through... It was very difficult
(LOL)
Ah, is that so?
Moving through is VERY difficult
[Moving was very difficult to fugitive Sho ㅠㅠ]
- Then 10 seconds are too short?
- Moving in 10 seconds...
[Moving was very difficult to fugitive Sho ㅠㅠ]
It is very difficult
[Sho who had issues with moving through, eliminated]
(Too bad...)
One person is out
The person who is in this area must be nervous
The next box will be opened by Mame-chan
(Resolute-)
- Let's go!
- Yes~
One!
[Pursuers: 4  VS  Fugitives: 1]
Two, three! Open!
[Empty box-]
Empty
[Shosei is still alive in Zone C]
- It's empty
- No one
[Shosei is still alive in Zone C]
Then we'll open the next box right away
Three, open!
[Shosei has avoided third opening as well]
Nobody
No one
[Getting anxious]
He hasn't been found yet. There's only one more to find
[The pursuer team's fourth chance]
Let's open the next box
Open!
(Peeks-)
[The fugitive team's last hope, Shosei's fate is...?]
- I can't believe this
- This is not good // - No one, no one
Open!
[Empty box-]
- I can't believe this
- This is not good // - No one, no one
[Everyone is baffled]
The one person has not been found yet
[The pursuer team has only Ruki left as well]
- Ruki is the last. Ruki! You're the last!
- The last chance, let's go!
If I don't get this, it's over?
Correct!
One, two, three!
Open!
[The result of the battle between the two teams is...?]
[Wide open]
[Shosei got caught at the very last]
Yeay!!
[Ruki succesfully made the final catch!]
[Utterly devastated]
- That was amazing
- Awesome!
Nice~
Nice!
[The pursuer team wins!]
Amazing
[Position Change]
(Fugitives: Team Blue  VS  Team Red: Pursuers)
[Team Blue as fugitives]
[Shion & Takumi are making strategies]
- Let's rampage this part first
- Okay
(Burning resolution)
[The pursuit team is determined]
- I won't let you reach Zone C
- I accidently looked behind, I'm sorry
[Sprinting with all his might]
[Takumi & Ruki decide to hide at the starting line]
[Shion & Mame push the boxes askew]
[The fugitive team finished hiding!]
[The pursuer team STARTS]
- The boxes moved a lot
- They moved a lot
Isn't it too easy to tell?
[It's the pursuer team's win if they catch 5 out of 6 fugitives]
That might be on purpose
[They can hide in Zone A only in the first round]
Good luck to you
Isn't it too obvious?
They are definitely around here
(Bet you are scared~)
This is awesome
Where are they? Where are they?
[The pursuer's voice is right in front of him]
At least one person's gotta be here
[For now... lights OUT...]
Where~ are you?
[Junki is trembling]
- Where~ are you~?
- I wonder where they are?
I have no idea. Finding them is kind of fun
[The pursuer team investigates based on their experience]
(Wild Sukai)
[Cautious about even the tiniest breath..]
We'll open the boxes one by one from now on
Open!
[The fugitive team's first fate is?]
It's empty ㅠㅠ
(Relieved) (Relieved)
Three, open!
It's empty~
- Empty!
- It was empty
- No one's here
- Really?
[First box opening, failed]
- Aigo~
- As we thought, it's hard to catch at the first try
[Syoya opens the second box]
Until the second box opening... 3, 2, 1! Open!
[Empty-]
- It's empty
- Empty!
(Confused)
- It was empty
- No one..
[All of the fugitive team remain alive!]
- It's empty // - Empty!
- It was empty // - No one..
Whoa~ Huh! Really?
(This is not good;;)
(Thinking) (Thinking)
I'm opening it~
(Abruptly)
- One- // - Oops!
- At one
[Empty box-]
It's empty
[The pursuer team failed three times in a row]
- It was empty
- It was
[The fugitive team survived three times]
- It's empty
- It was empty // - It was
(Glad) (Glad)
Aahh!!!!
[Keigo succeeds in surprise arrest of a fugitive]
[The fugitive team strategically messed up the boxes at the start]
I can see their route
[Shosei perfectly saw through their ploy]
(Trick) (Trick)
- They are gathered around here
- At least one person's gotta be here, right?
[Keigo & Shosei became certain after seeing Sukai's opening]
[Someone's gotta be here!!!]
[They caught fugitive Ren!]
[Round of applause]
That was amazing
(Even the enemy acknowledges~)
[First elimination, Ren is out!]
- The fact that we found Ren is kinda big
- It is // - This is regrettable
(This is.. not too bad)
(Phew.. I'm relieved)
Open!
[Unfortunately Shosei failed]
- Empty?
- Empty
[1st Round: 1 fugitive apprehended, 4 remaining]
- Aigo~
- It was empty
Let's go back! x2
[The pursuer team toughen their will once again]
- For real?
- I can't believe it. We let them go to B
[Memorizing the location of the boxes]
- Let's memorize
- Are those all?
[Advancement to Zone B is allowed in the 2nd round]
(Careful) (Careful)
[Except Shion everyone remains in Zone A]
[Second pursuit starts!]
They came to the right side
[The pursuer team heads to the most suspicious boxes]
- Please choose five boxes
- They came to this side. They definitely did
- The three over here
- Isn't it too neat?
[This is suspicious]
Was it this out of place before?
[I'll go with this!]
- This is suspicious
- That is suspicious
[Shosei is confident]
I'm going to choose this one!
(Nervous-)
First one
Were they this jumbled up before? This chaotic?
[Sho suspects the disarrayed Zone A]
- Gotta mean they were there before?
- This is too much
Three, two, one! Open!
Awesome!
[Shion who were in Zone B alone, eliminated!]
Is there someone?
Open!
[Fail 1]
- Empty!
- It's empty
Open!
[Fail 2]
- It's empty~
- No one
Three. Open!
[Fail 3]
[The pursuer team went all-in on Zone B]
It's empty~
[The pursuer team went all-in on the B zone]
- This is not good! x2
- No on was inside the box
Three!
It's empty~
[Sho fails to catch due to miscalculation]
- Huh? Ninja?
- In this round-
- We have one elimination
- Do we have ninjas here?
[2nd Round: 2 eliminations, 3 survivors + 1 (extra)]
[The fugitive team has three lives remaining]
[They sprint with all their might]
[Mame displays a deception tactic]
[They evenly distributed compared to the previous round]
[The fugitive team finished hiding]
(Takumi ready) (Mame ready)
(Junki ready) (????)
[Where is Ruki?]
(Ruki???)
(Slips-)
[10 seconds ago, when the round started]
(Ruki was not able to get out of box quickly)
(Ruki was flustered)
(While hurrying, the camera got caught on the box;;)
Stay at your position!
(While hurrying, the camera got caught at the box;;)
Everyone, stop now! (Pursuer team), please go find!
(Goodbye ㅠㅠ)
[Ruki was not able to hide properly]
[Team Red starts the pursuit!]
Please go find!
Huh? There's something-
[They sensed something out of place right away]
Camera! x3
Camera! There's camera!
[They found the camera that's left alone]
There's camera!
[The pursuit team gathers at the accident (?) scene]
There has been an accident
But where could he be?
There's camera, but which box? We don't know
[There is nobody?]
- We don't know
- This is quite an incident
Here- Wait! This-
But the fact that it fell here
Either he did it like this or did it like this from here
- Shouldn't it be this one?
- That's likely
We'll leave this up to you
[They retreat leaving the Ruki's case to Sho]
If it were me-
- I think we better go with that area
- I think so, too
[The pursuit team resumes finding the fugitives]
- There were a lot of sounds
- There were sounds from right and left
[They suspect all the remaining fugitives will be in Zone C]
- In order to pass the goal line
- It'll be impossible to pass the line unless you are in C
They must have targeted C
Okay! We are good to go
- Are you ready to choose?
- Okay
Are you guys confident?
Yes. Well, the camera- It's the same situation as mine
Until the box open... Three, two, one!
Open!
(Hello Ruki)
- Wait he only has the light! LOL
- Ruki is in there!
One elimination!
(Feels empathetic?)
Good, good
[Fugitive Ruki, eliminated together with the camera]
- Ruki, make sure to take your camera
- Yay!
[The fugitive team has two chances remaining]
Shosei-kun, let's open a box~
[Shosei will open the second box]
Box opening in-
One, two, three!
[This time?]
(Peek-a-boo)
(Takumi is here~)
Takumi-kun!
Oii!!
It was you!
It was slanted
I did it!
Nice, Shosei!
Let's keep this going!
You came this far.. Amazing~
Let's continute to the next box. Syoya-kun!
- Yes!
- Let's go
One, two, three!
[Third box open]
- Open!
- I'll do it
[Fail]
Not good, not good
[This is not good]
- There's no one
- It's empty
[This is not good]
- No one was in there
- Could it be over there?
[The fugitive team has one life remaining]
- It's empty
- No one was in there
[The pursuer team has two chances still]
[4th player is Keigo]
- Keigo-kun!
- Keigo! // - Let's go
[The game is over if one of them gets caught]
Open!
[Keigo did it again]
[In despair]
Junki~
Junki is here~
Junki where did you come from?
I came from A
[Junki ran from Zone A to Zone C in one go]
[Taking the last life of the fugitive team]
Keigo, nice!
[The pursuer team wins!]
(Where is Mame?)
Mame-chan~
- Where are you?
- Mame-chan!
(Shots up-)
(Our youngest~ LOL)
Mame! Go, go!
Run! x2
Mame, go! x2
Go, go!
[The result of "A Box Flower Has Bloomed": Peacefully tied~]
[After the exciting unity competition]
The last special game ended with a draw
[Good work, everyone]
How do you feel about ending the competition with a tie?
- We could confirm everyone's unity
- The power of unity
Hence we specially will give these prizes to both teams
Thank you!
It's Hello Paradise Tour's
Restaurant gift certificate
(Fully) (Satisfied)
Also we'll give you these presents in front of us
[JO1 chooses a gift one by one peacefully]
- It's light!
- No, no, no. This one-
[JO1 chooses a gift one by one peacefully]
- This is the closest to me // - Really?
- This is the middle
Here
[Gifts the members chose for each other during free time]
[Hopefully the caring thoughts reach each other..]
(LOL)
- Cute! // - What is that?
- It's moving // - Awesome!
(Cute) (Cute)
[Closing with cute Ruki~]
How was the last 3 days 2 nights trip?
It was a self-sufficient tour
So, it was tough and I was almost discouraged
But, the pleasure of working? I was able to learn that
And we, JO1, were able to travel Korea together as 11. It was very fun
I can only be grateful for this precious experience in Korea
And we'll continue to be JO1 who strives hard. For the last three days!
- Thank you so much!
- Thank you so much~
There are animals
[Korea tour for 3 days and 2 nights.
Priceless memories thanks to special experiences]
[Through the self-sufficient experience,
they came to learn each other's new side]
- Stop for a moment
- Good, good! x2
[Through the self-sufficient experience,
they came to learn each other's new side]
Buy this king crab~ It's really delicious~
[Which made their trip all the more exciting]
One, two!
Why don't we say the final greetings together?
One, two, three!
See you again~
- Thank you~
- Bye bye
#Only_for_Jams #Don't_go_JO1
[JO1's_Hello_Tour_unreleased.zip]
One, two, three
(RenGo)
Leggo!
[JO1_Korean school.mov]
(Puppy wants pork belly)
- I want to eat pork belly // - Okay, then. Let's go
[JO1_Korean school.mov]
(Oppa? Hyung!)
- Really, oppa (older bro for girls) // - Oppa?
[JO1_Korean school.mov]
(Oppa? Hyung!)
Oppa- Ah, hyung! x3 (older bro for boys)
[JO1_Korean school.mov]
(Is Shosei a genius? - Kinda)
Sir, we are out of paper bags
[JO1_Korean school.mov]
(Is Shosei a genius? - Kinda)
- You are? // - Yeah, the paper bags
[JO1_Korean school.mov]
(Tsundere sassy cat Shion)
Eat slowly, I tell you!
[JO1_Korean school.mov]
(K5's charm is 1.. 1.. no, 100)
One~ Two~ One hundred. It's one hundred
[JO1_Korean school.mov]
(Baby angel Sukai's legendary insightfullness)
Hyung has an allergy. So, I- I eat a lot, yeah
[JO1_Korean school.mov]
(Preschool Re*ls & Tikt*k experts)
[JO1_Pro_Idol.mov]
(Winner of "Unlock The Face ID Cutely")
(Close-up on beautiful, delicate hands)
It's fun
[JO1_Pro_Idol.mov]
(Can I be a ninja too? Syoya can?)
(How is a person so puppy-kitty >3<v)
[JO1_Pro_Idol.mov]
(Yona-oppa's surfing is the BEST >_<♥)
(We decided to call this "Too into the role")
- I will grant this to you // - Hello! I'm a straw-hat revolutionist, Yutabon (A Youtuber)!
[JO1_Pro_Idol.mov]
One, two, three
[This song is...?]
Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious
[Please give lots of support to JO1 who will expand
to the world and their new song 'SuperCali']
[Thank you for your love for JO1's Hello Tour]