Translation: Verde (@1DERJAM)
Timing: Na (@delishriceball)
Quality Check: Na (@delishriceball), Verde (@1DERJAM)
[Previously in HELL?O TOUR, Day2]
[The traditional seafood market located in Sorae Port, Incheon]
[Plenty of fresh seafood]
[Challenging the fishing village! JO1 is here~]
Hello~ Isn't it amazing?
[Nice to meet you]
[Team A will be working at 'JM' Seafood Shop]
- Market team?
- Sho and Takumi
[Team A will be working at 'JM' Seafood Shop]
Hurry up inside~
You gotta start working right away!
(It's busy;;)
Okay! Please take good care of me!
Get a king crab~ 1 kg for 60,000 won
[At seafood market, they sell king crabs and abalones too]
Six, seven... Wow!
[We are selling a lot ^____^v]
Many, many!
[+Customer management. I won't be negligent^^]
- Bonus, bonus
- Thank you
[Task level:★★★ Bring 5 kg of live shrimps]
- Please bring 5 kg of shrimps using the bucket
- 5 kg!
(Get back soon^^)
Hurry back~
[We are going on an errand!]
- Hope you succeed! Good luck!
- We will~
[At the same time same location, Team B at 'DH' Sashimi Center]
Alright, let's do it!
[Getting ready to open! Cleaning the sea squirt tank!]
(Sukai wipes~) (Ruki scoops~)
I see, I gotta do it like this
[Practicing promotion of the store]
Welcome~ Sea squirts are very delicious~
It’s really delicious! Uhm... in my opinion...
[Everything is going smoothly for Team B]
[Meanwhile, Team C that is working at the restaurant]
[While they were preparing ingredients after done cleaning...]
[They got handed over a mysterious(?) basket...]
[Auntie... What is this...?]
What's this?
Whelks (for 20200304 people)
Whelks!
[The members look moved by the generous gift from the owner]
[Remove x1]
Like this~
[Remove x2]
[Remove x3]
[The amount of whelks does not seem to go down]
[Where's the end of prepping ingredients for the restaurant team?]
[And this place is?]
These are the water tanks where we breed shrimps
[In more than 100 water tanks]
[They breed shrimps using eco-friendly technology]
These are the water tanks where we breed shrimps
- Shrimp! x2
- The shrimp flew
[Checking the health of 2-months-old babies!]
- I think there's a lot around me
- Raise the net up!
(Very healthy)
(Brown = Healthy shrimp)
[Feeding the shrimps, CLEARED]
- Now we need to feed them
- They are eating!
Eat a lot~
[JO1's Tale of Toil at Fishing Village... To be continued]
[Filmed in accordance with the guideline of COVID regulations]
[Cleaning the sea cucumber tank after the sea squirt's]
(Plop~) (Plop~)
- "Namako"*
- "Nameko?"
(*T/N: Sea cucumber in Japanese)
"Haesam*!"
(*T/N: Sea cucumber in Korean)
[Returning the sea cucumbers into the clean tank]
(Proud)
Done!
[Finished cleaning the sea squirt & sea cucumber tanks~]
These are wild-caught spotty-belly greenlings, famous in Sorae Port
(Fresh)
- Since you worked hard, why don't you slice yourself and try it?
- We can try it?
(We... we are doing it ourselves?)
For real?
(Thump!!)
Is this real?!
What do I do?
[The owner's confident and skillful cutting and slicing]
I don't think... I can do that
(Sukai is getting used to it)
(Sparkle) (Sparkle)
Who would like to try first?
[Sukai works up a courage!]
- I'll teach you. Like this, like this
- Here? This?
(The owner did the initial preparation for him)
Oh~ You are good!
[Despite the concern, he's doing a clean job]
You're doing good. Cut all the way up!
Am I doing well?
(He removed the skin nicely without cutting off the meat)
Oh~ Nice, very nice
(Yes! I did it!)
You did very good
[It's Ruki's turn]
Yes! Please teach me
(Slice, slice~)
This is difficult;;
Do you have to tug at the skin while slicing?
You have to tilt the blade a little
Oh, like this
Wait, I left too much meat on the skin
(Too much meat left)
[The owner takes over the mound!]
- This...
- Thank you
[Hold the tail and then in one swift motion!]
The meat is very delicious
[PER-FECT]
[You are the best~]
But Ruki did a good job too
[Ruki is the best~]
Good job!
(Bump!)
(Ouch;;)
Good, good~
[Time to remove moisture from the meat]
(Towel that has been in the freezer)
You have to freeze the towels before using them
You need to spread them wide
Who would like to go first?
Me
[Sukai steps up this time as well]
[Roll up the towel and put pressure on it]
(Press) (Press)
[Power Crush]
[Next, Ruki's turn]
[This is not a sushi roll]
Squeeze, squeeze out the water. Roll it!
Okay!
[If you unwrap carefully, fish meat minus the moisture is ready]
There is no water
Hyung*, you are good!
(*T/N: Older brother in Korean)
[Ruki does the final slicing~]
You're good!
Should I cut it bigger?
[His soul is in each and every piece]
Applause! You did great
[Slicing sashimi, finished!]
[Ruki & Sukai's first ever sashimi slices are a success!]
[Time to taste]
- Well then, should we try it?
- We should!
- It looks so good. Since it's fresh
- Very fresh
They were in the tank just minutes ago
(With a dab of spicy sauce)
It's wonderful
It was really a precious experience we wouldn't have had in Japan
(Swallow~)
How is it?
[Truthful eyebrows say it all]
OMG~!
- It's so good
- It's really good
(Food taste better when shared)
- Let's call Keita!
- Yeah!
I really want Keita to taste this, too. Let's eat it together!
Keita~ Keita~
[Reply, Keita]
- Keita-san~
Yes~ x4
Thanks for your work
Thank you for your work, too~
We just sliced sashimi by ourselves
[We want to eat together with you~]
And we would like to share that with you
I'll run to you right away
Take care on your way here
We'll be waiting for you~
He's here
[Keita happened to be already on his way with gifts]
Wow, bouncy!
[Welcome back]
[Keita is here~]
Thank you~
[Cold drinks for the hard-working customers]
- I brought you cold drinks
- Thank you so much
Thank you!
Thank you, Keita-san!
Did you... cut this?
[This is the sashimi?!]
We took it out from the tank about 5 minutes ago and...
[THUD!]
- Is it okay if I eat it?
- Please! Keita-san
We sliced it with knife ourselves
By the way, what kind of fish is it?
Spotty-belly greenling!
(Nom-)
How is it?
It's rea~lly good!
[Feels happy]
(Next stall's owner)
I'd like to eat that too~
- You are eating alone?
- It's really good
[Sukai will deliver it to you~]
Ma'am~ Would you like one?
[Open your mouth~]
[It's the best~!]
That's so sweet~
- Is it good?
- It's good!
[Sukai's warmth fills the stalls]
- We got a very good scene
- That was amazing
(Slashing the fish) just like this
[Thanks to Su-weet Sukai the market team is full of happiness]
- Ow ow, it's heavy. Keita, please take this
- Ah~ Thanks
[Meanwhile, the restaurant team is?]
[They are preparing vegetables peacefully]
Shion, which part of this do I peel? From here?
You need to peel more
- Hm?
- Peel more
(Look over there!)
[Deadly serious about peeling garlics]
He's a professional!
(Cut cut)
[I'm a solitary professional]
[I'll peel each and every one of these!!!!!]
(Last one)
- Done
- Yo!
[Shion & Keigo are done preparing the green onions]
(Triumphant)
[50 servings of whelks and 5 bundles of green onions, finished]
[1 bag of garlics, soon to be finished]
Auntie~ We are done
Oh my, you did a very good job! Very good!
(Pat pat)
- I know it was tough
- Thank you
(M A S S A G E)
- You worked hard
- Thank you
[Gotta wash the hard working hands~]
[Precious break time after work]
- Good work!
- Good work~
I'm very hungry
I made you something delicious
[Special dish from the owner for the restaurant team]
[Sushi and seasoned whelks!]
- Thank you!
- Shrimp!
- This is what you unshelled earlier
- Ah, the whelks!
- The whelks, yes
- Whelks!
[The fruit of today's labor]
(Moved)
- Thank you for the meal
- Yeay!
What was it called again?
- The result of our work
- Yes. The whelks
[Ingredients prepared by themselves, how would it taste?]
- "Tsubugai" (Whelk in Japanese)
- "Golbaengi" (Whelk in Korean). Bon appetit!
Mmm~
- It's really good
- Whelk!
Let me dig in!
[Licks the sauce that got on his hand]
- Delicious!
- Bon appetit!
(My turn)
It's so good!
[Nods moved by the taste]
Yummy!
[Double thumbs up~]
I'm glad we did our best
[More into my mouth~]
[Satisfactory special dish]
This is the fruit of our hard work
Yay!!
The delivery is here~~~~
[Keita is busy taking care of his customers]
Thank you so much!
It's 10,000 won
(Excuse me?)
(LOL)
[Keita's drink service for the hard-working restaurant team]
- So good~
- This is it!
[I'm revived~]
It's tasty!
How was working here?
- It was... I feel like we worked pretty a lot
- A lot, huh?
(Shoulder massage)
- It was... I feel like we worked pretty a lot
- A lot, huh?
(LOL)
[How are Sho and Takumi doing?]
The sauna is supposed to be there...
Sauna...
[They are on the errand of bringing back 5 kg of shrimps]
Here?
- The one over there?
- No, no. It's not that one
[They are on the errand of bringing back 5 kg of shrimps]
- Looks like... this one definitely is not it
- Definitely not
[It's not sauna from any angle]
- Hello~
- Since it's gotta be a sauna
I think it's that way, but I'm not sure...
Oh, but "second floor" is written over there
[It's on the first floor of the building that says sauna! First floor!]
First floor
[Past Sho heard it clearly]
[However he seems to have forgotten it LOL]
(Sigh!~)
[He is getting antsy]
- Let's speed up a little!
- Should we?
[Starting to feel anxious..]
They are drying a lot of fishes
Hello~
[The restaurant that the restaurant team is working at]
There's Keita!
[They found Keita who's in the restaurant!]
- Let's ask for help!
- Let's ask!
[Keita, please help!]
- Hello
- Hi
We've missed you! A lot!
- You missed me?
- Yes!
What happened?
So this-
We'd like to go here
(★ Shrimps' location) - (Sho & Takumi's location)
- What's the name of this sauna?
- What's written here?
(★ Shrimps' location) - (Sho & Takumi's location)
- Yoo-il Seafood~
- Yoo-il Seafood!
And Haesoo Sauna is-
[The sauna you are looking for is...]
(O~ver there)
- Oh, it's that one?!
- It's that building
[Finally found the sauna!]
- That one?
- You'll get there if you go straight this way
[To think it was this easy to find...]
- Should we try going inside?
- Ah, I see
- Oh, it's inside
- So, it was inside of this sauna building
Is it okay to just walk in like this? It was pretty close by...
Don't worry, it's okay...
- If it was just us we'd never have found it
- Yeah, never
[They trust in Keita and tail behind]
[Crossroads appeared]
- Oh!
- Is it wrong?
(Hmm...)
Ah, but this way...
[It thought it was around here...]
- But it does look like it'd be around here
- Could it be this?
(Confused;;;)
[Walking straight for now]
[There's a fish market in a place like this?]
[His brain is about to explode...]
[No matter how you look at it this is a restaurant...]
I don't think this is it;;;
[Quick U-turn]
Let's go back for now
(Scratches)
So, it wasn't here
It was on the other side
No wonder we couldn't find it
[Brain engine on the maximum power]
- It's the other side x3
- I see
[Will we find it this time?]
(Yoo-il Seafood)
[Once they stepped outside, it came into the vision!]
Oh, it's here
(Yoo-il Seafood)
[Once they stepped outside, it came into the vision!]
[We finally found it!!]
[Everyone is overjoyed]
- Thank you!
- Thanks, too
(Sigh. I'm relieved)
- We are here! // - We are here~
- Let's go inside
- Hello~
- Hello, Sir~
[Not only shrimps but also various other seafood is sold]
[Jump, jump! Fresh shrimps are here~]
What's the order?
[The owner is checking the order list]
Ordering itself should be simple
- Please give us (the shrimps), thank you
- Thank you
Your Korean is too good
- You can catch the shrimps with the net and take them out
- Okay, okay
Takumi-kun is catching the shrimps himself~
[Keita CAM]
- So cool!
- Good luck!
[Takumi, good luck!]
Good luck!
(Full of shrimps)
(Heavy)
Good, good
[Moving them into the bucket]
Oh my!
[He did it all by himself]
You need to measure the weight
[Current weight: 2kg. They need 5kg in total]
- Alright!
- You can do it!
[Let's fill up a little more~]
Huh?
- You're so cool, Takumi
- He is, really
(I acknowledge)
[ - Let's appreciate his working face - ]
More, more
(Fu-ll)
You can do it!
[Even his frown looks cool]
[Total: 5 kg. It finally reached the goal!]
- Yes!
- Wow~!
[The owner moves the bucket full of shrimps for them]
Oh my!
[Thank you, Sir]
- Thank you very much!
- Thank you!
[Now they need to return asap]
[The shrimps are on the way~]
I need to pay attention
Shrimp- Oops, shrimps!
Slowly, slowly~
But gotta hurry up at the same time, too
Slowly but quickly
[Surprised]
What will happen if we drop this...?
[I don't want to imagine...]
I won't let that happen!!!
Ah, thank you!
- Since I've helped you... (My job is done here)
- Thank you so much!
Best of luck to you!
I'll do my best!
- Let's do our best!
- See you later!
I'll see you later~~
See you later!
[Sho & Takumi return to the workplace]
I think we can find our way back from here
- We can just trace back, right?
- Yup
[We are used to this street now]
- Slowl- Slowly
- Slowly
Slowly but quickly
Hot!
- Auntie might scold us
- She may scold us
[In heart we are moving fast]
She'll scold us, let's hurry back!
- The seagulls!
- They are after the shrimps!
The seagulls are eyeing our shrimps!
[I won't let you take my shrimps]
This is not good, she'll definitely get mad at us
I don't want to be yelled at in a foreign country
[Bring... the shrimps... quickly!!!!!!]
[Finally arrived at the market entrance]
- Hello~
- Hello~ Slowly, slowly
I'm tired
[Finally arrived at the market entrance]
[Delivering shrimps without a break]
- You came from far and working at a place like this
- Thank you // - Hi
- Oh my, you are having it hard
- Hello
- Oh my!!
- Oh my~
[Oh my...? What does that mean?]
- What did he say?
- Hello
- This is where we were before
- Yeah x3
- Hello
- Hi~
Long time no see
- I'm tired!
- Tired
[They are getting used to the work and the language]
- I'm tired!
- Tired
- It's really hot
- It really is
[They are getting used to the work and the language]
Fighting, fighting!
This situation is so funny LOL
[Going over the curb with all of their remaining strength]
Phew~ I'm dead tired
So tired
The numbers!
- Oh, right! Each stall has a number
- That's right!
Did you remember the number?
I didn't LOL
But I remember approximately where it was
- We can tell by the surroundings. There are indicators
- Yes
(Follow me)
[Follow the alley lined up with stalls]
(Found it!)
[They have finally returned]
It's here! This is it
We are back
Good job~
Shrimps!
- Please put them in here
- Here?
Let's go!
Leggo!
[Pour them in-]
Oops! x2
[They are carefully carried into the tank]
[Replenishing shrimps, finished!]
Very good job~
- Thank you for your work
- Yeay!!
[We did it!]
(Congrats1) / (Congrats2) / (Congrats3)
[Shrimp errand was perfectly carried out]
Thank you
Since you worked hard, I'll treat you to cold drinks
[Two orders of cold and sweet rice drinks~]
Thank you~
Cheers! We worked hard
(Gulp gulp)
- Sweet!
- Is it rice?
It is rice. It's really good
[They are falling in love with the rice drink]
Very delicious
I peel likum rehive?*
(*T/N: Sho forgot the phrase)
I. Feel. Like. I'm. Revived
[It's good to hear you are revived]
I feel like I'm revived
How was the work today?
- Was it hard?
- Uhm...
It was- difficult
But!!!
- It was! A lot of fun
- It was fun?
Will you come back someday?
(Of course)
[Give us a call anytime~]
- Yes, yes
Are you going to come back to work or to eat?
We'll come to eat
Did we do a good job today?
You did a good job
[You did very well~ ★★★★★]
- A very good job
- Thank you
[You did very well~ ★★★★★]
[Meanwhile, the shrimp fishery team?]
Now, here...
We'll be catching shrimps and ship them out
You remember the 2-months old babies?
[Previously they checked baby shrimps' health]
[This time they will catch and pack 4-months old shrimps]
(Plump)
We need to take out all the oxygen generators outside. Like this
And we'll tie up the ones in the middle
Let's catch and taste some shrimps
Really?
[He is looking for shrimps harder than any time]
It's different
Oh, it's not soy sauce
[Found shrimps!]
(I'm eating this here right now?)
Now?
- Now?
- For real?
Show us please!
- Try smelling
- Really?
- I doesn't smell
- No smell
- It's alive! x2
- Awesome!
It's moving! x2
[He is making shrimp sashimi on the spot]
(Gulps)
He is rinsing it properly
[Dipping sauce choice: Both Korean and Japanese style are available~]
Korean style...
(Japanese style) (Korean style)
- Or Japanese style sauce?
- Japanese style!
- Please give me a lot of wasabi
- A lot?
(A lot of wasabi)
This is definitely a luxury
(In one bite)
It's meaty
(Eyes wide open)
It's delicious!
[Syoya's reaction makes them want to try]
- It doesn't smell and is delicious, right?
- Yup!
- Is it number one?
- It's good!
- Is it the best you've ever had?
- It's tasty! The best!
I'd like to try it too, then!
I want to try too!
[Strongly recommend]
- You want to try?
- Yes!
[Please feed our youngest Mame]
Mame-chan, I like you. A lot of wasabi?
The wasabi wasn't that spicy
(Junki peeks)
(Swallows)
So delicious!
(He's eating well)
It's good!
[Mame is now shrimp-holic...]
It's yummy!
I want the Korean style sauce!!
Korean style this time
(Dab of spicy sauce)
Thank you for the shrimp~
(Synchronized devour)
[Sweet and spicy taste spreads in mouth]
Delicious!!!
[Strongly recommend]
- It's very plump
- It's crazy!
Now, let's get back to work! We need to hurry
[Power up!]
- Okay!
- Power!
[Let's work~]
Go, go!
[Today's goal: Packing 30 kg of shrimps]
[Catching live shrimps starts]
- Let's go!
- We'll start!
Hurry, hurry up!
Hurry up!
[Swift 4-months-old shrimps]
[Syoya and Mame catch the shrimps]
Mame, pull!
[Shosei and Junki put and carry them in boxes]
Oh my! Oh my!
[Full of healthy shrimps]
On the scale
Alright!
- Go!
- Go to the truck
[Heavy box is not a problem]
- Thanks, Shosei
- Alright!
[Powerful Shosei]
This is interesting
Should I put this on here?
[Safely delivered it to the truck]
Okay!
Don't you want to eat more shrimps, you dummies?
[The magic words "pali pali*"]
(*T/N: Hurry up)
It's hot!
One, two~
(Heave~)
Shosei, did you see? x2
[Perfect teamwork]
- 8.2 still
- Let's go!
Okay!
[It's better to speed up when it's heavy]
This is too heavy
[The net team is doing their best too]
One, two!
[They pull up the nets with all their strength]
Here we go!
[Energetic shrimps~]
- Let's go!
- Oops! Sorry
[Speed UP]
[Today's last batch: 5 kg!]
5 kg!
Many many!
Here
Is that 5 kg already?
Slightly over, but okay!
- Okay
- Go!
(Rushes)
Alright, it's over!
The last one!
[With Shosei's last box]
The last! This is the last one
[The fishery team's job came to an end!]
It's done
Good work~
[The power of labor division]
[The tank team did a good job too]
- Nice work!
- Nice work to you, too
Everyone is so cool
- It's hot
- You must be
- Since the water is very deep
- Sweat!
[The value of sweated labor...]
- Since the water is very deep
- Sweat!
[The value of sweated labor...]
OK. Thank you for your work!
[The team came out to send off the truck]
- You worked really hard
- This is the last!
The last! The last!
One, two!
There!
[They finish the day's work by closing the truck's tailgate]
All's good. You can leave
- Goodbye~
- You were delicious~
- Edible shrimps, let's meet again~
- Bye bye~
- Thank you for your hard work
- Thank you
- Please give lots of love to shrimps
- We will. I love them
[Meanwhile, where is the market team?]
Hello~
[They are visiting the restaurant to dine]
[Welcome to the store]
Welcome~
(Give us food~)
I'm very hungry
[Waiter mode ON]
- This way please~
- Here? Got it
[Smoothly guiding to the table]
- Here?
- Please take a seat here
I'm so hungry
[Side dishes are here~]
- Welcome~
- Awesome
[Side dishes are here~]
[Perfect customer service]
Welcome~
[Applauses burst out]
Wow! Awesome
It's okay, it's okay
Please enjoy!
Thank you~
[Prepared with heart for the members]
[The table is getting full]
- That too, over there
- What about this?
This is cold raw fish soup
(Heaping amount)
- What's that?
- Please mix it before you eat
- Oh, right!
- Yes?
[Another main of the table, whelks]
The whelks!
The whelks~
[If we are to talk about these whelks...]
It's "tsubugai" (in Japanese)
- We unshelled about 500 of these
- That's right
- That was a lot of work
- Good work
And we are having about 20 of your hard work
Enjoy the food!
One, two!
Thank you for the food!
You all worked really hard
Let me dig in
[Meal after hard work is sweeter than honey]
- Does anybody need green onions?
- Looks delicious
[Meal after hard work is sweeter than honey]
The whelks are seriously delicious
- Are they?
- Yes. They really are
They look sweet
(How is it?)
(It's good!)
- Is it good?
- Yeah!
[Cannot hide his smile]
So tasty!
What kind of work did the market team do?
- We divided into two teams, right?
- Yup
Depending on which shop you were in, the works were totally different
For me and Takumi, as soon as we stepped in
We were told to grab an octopus
- An octopus?!
- Yes
After that...
Shrimps!
We had to bring shrimps
- 5kg (of shrimps)
- It was pretty far
(LOL)
It was quite far, wasn't it?
And then we sold things like crabs
Abalones and scallops, too
Did you sell a lot?
- We sold a lot, didn't we?
- We did. Customers bought a lot
We- was it abalone?
We sold 30 abalones
- It was a lot of fun
- It was
What about Ruki's?
We did... water tank cleaning!
- Water tank cleaning?
- Yes
After that...
- They taught us how to cut sashimi
- Really?!
How to cut sashimi?
And then we ate it
- Then you know how to cut sashimi now?
- Oh, but...
I was... pretty bad at it
(It's difficult~)
Were you unshelling the whelks the entire time?
We prepped vegetables and cleaned the space, too
Did you learn any new words?
"Golbaengi*"
(*T/N: Whelks)
Shrimp team?
I just got a news about them
(Picture acquired)
They sent a picture
We, the market team wore aprons
But they were wearing something like overalls and in chest-deep water
Amazing
- Looks like the got a hard job
- That must be hard
- But those four wanted to go there~
- They did
Let's enjoy our food ^^
- Let's eat the shrimp team's share, too
- Let's!
I'm sorry, shrimp team
I got to watch you work today
Everyone worked so hard
And underwent hardship
So we've prepared FLEX time in pool
(Sounds fun)
- I appreciate your hard work. Thank you
- Thank you!
[Today's FLEX location!]
[Various activities in cool artificial waves]
[You can enjoy surfing as well!]
[JO1 has appeared at the water park!]
[JO1 entering the water park. Welcome!]
Nice~
(Excited)
- There's pool!
- We can go in, right?
[A special vacation place in the middle of the city]
- I'd like to go in
- It looks like sea!
We've arrived!
[A place where you can recharge energy through relaxation and activities]
[Let's go have fun!]
[Six members are heading somewhere first]
Hi~
I'll do my best. Fighting!
Oh, I see
We go down by the zipline
[Zipline that waiting for the members?]
[First member who will challenge the zipline?]
Let's do rock, paper and scissors
Let's do RPS!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Paper!
- You two
- I'm not
(Shosei lost!)
- Why me?
- One, two- Rock, paper, scissors!
Okay, I'm first
[First player, Shosei]
First, second, third...
Third?
How do I- What do I do?
- You have to sit down
- Sit down. Okay, I got it
- Sit down. Go down straight
- Yes
And at the end just let it go
[Five members are cheering from the front row seats(?)]
Shosei, do your best~!
Shosei! Do it with one hand!
Shout "hakuna matata"!
Okay, go!
[Shosei takes off!]
Let's go!
(Aakk~)
Quite uncool
(This is fun~)
[They are excited too]
He looks a little bit uncool
[Shosei advances cutting the wind]
(Rotates) (Spins)
[Fell into water with splendid spin!]
(LOL)
[Huge laughter thanks to the extraordinary performance]
That's gotta hurt
So funny
[Technical score: 8 points] [Comedy score: 6 points]
[Applause to the sacrificing performance]
He fell
(Cooly returns)
- Nice!
- It's too funny
(You are the best)
Nice~
[Second player, Sukai]
He might do something acrobatic
Kinjo Sukai, go!
[Gentler start compared to Shosei?]
Kinjo Sukai
[He's starting to bounce]
Go!
[Huge expectation]
Amazing!
[While he was coming down smoothly]
(What was that LOL)
[With calm facial expression and not-as-much posture]
[Cool splash!!]
[Technical score: 5 points] [Comedy score: 8 points]
[Which member will challenge the zipline next?]
Go! Fighting!
[Mame the youngest takes off!]
(Excited) (Excited)
[Other members followed with unique poses]
Takumi!
[Takumi drops!!]
[Mame drops!!]
[Front row seat for the view]
[Keigo falls hard LOL]
[This is so much fun]
[Ren departs~]
(Perfect posture)
So cool!
(He is good LOL)
Potato* pose! x3
(*T/N: French fries)
[His drop down is per-fect!]
Nice pose!
Nice potato!
[Rapper Syoya departs~]
[With flawless posture]
[He goes down smoothly]
[And then drops with high-level technique]
(LOL)
[Profuse applause]
[Technical score: 8 points] [Comedy score: 9 points]
- Eight!
- That was amazing
[Technical score: 8 points] [Comedy score: 9 points]
Yeah! Eight!
[It's hilarious. 8 points!]
- Nice!
- That was so funny!
[Ruki & Junki & Sho take off!]
[Diving 1 combo]
[Diving 2 combo]
[Diving 3 combo]
- This has to be 1 point
- He'd break!
One point!
[Last player, Shion]
We'll wait here
[Do it funnily!]
Make us laugh!
- Leggo!
- I'm expecting something fun and cool!
Hurry up!
[Shion departs]
[I'll show you what zipline is about~]
[Members suddenly burst out laughing?!]
[Hanging helplessly]
[Oh, come on~~~]
(Struggles) (Struggles)
[Man who can walk on the water]
[Floundering with his entire body]
[With intense kicking]
- 7 points? 7 points!
- It was funny
[Applause to Shion who gave big laughs until the end...]
Was it funny?
[JO1 summer FLEX main event]
[Solidarity UP - Water Basketball Match]
Team Blue: Keigo, Sukai, Takumi, Mame, Shosei
Team Red: Sho, Junki, Ren, Syoya, Ruki, Shion
One, two, three!
[6-point match, START]
We can't use legs
[Ren takes the first chance to attack]
I'm gonna protect!
(Hesitates) (Hesitates)
- If you don't catch, it won't end
- Correct!
Over here!
(Here~)
(Team Red's goal)
Me, Junki-kun~
[Seeking weak spot while passing around the ball]
Dangerous! We can't use legs
[Junki's ambush shot!]
(Goal!)
[A long-shot goal]
[Smooth score]
- I see, now
- Nice!
[Current Score]
Team Blue: 0　-　Team Red: 1
(Sneaky laugh)
(Squeeze~)
[Everyone, be ready!]
He's awakening! x2
[He moves in closer to the goal]
Alright. Shion, go!
[Rapid pass in triangle formation]
Do your best!
[Unguarded goal chance]
[Will they score?]
(No!)
[The ball bounced off of the hoop]
(What a shame...)
We can still do it! x2
- Shosei!
- Ruki, Ruki!
[Iron-wall block]
[Good job, Takumi!]
[He passes to Keigo past Shion!]
[Keigo charges toward the goal]
[Passes to Shosei]
No! x4
[He pretends to pass, then shoots]
Attack, attack!
[Shosei's one-hand mid-range shot]
[Current Score]
Team Blue: 1　-　Team Red: 1
- Go back, go back!
- To the other side!
[Shion invades the empty space]
This makes me sweat!
(Exchanges eye contact)
[Passes to Shion]
(Slips)
[It fell too far]
That's ours
[The ball is in the hands of Team Blue]
I hate this
Let me hit the ball!
Go this way!
[Pass to Takumi on the left]
Takumi! x2
[Commence operation]
I hate this!
[Pass missed]
Nice!
[Chance for Ruki!]
Ruki! x2
Aahh...
(What a luck?!)
[Powerful shot]
[Sukai is superbly receiving Takumi's shot]
[Goal!!!]　[In!!!]
[Another point thanks to Takumi & Sukai!]
(Chance to attack)
[The swiftly passes while Team Blue let their guard down]
Mame! x2
[Easy goal!]
Nice!
(Nice!)
[Current Score]
Team Blue: 2　-　Team Red: 2
[Keigo starts a counterattack]
- It's too deep
- Too deep
[Goal Sukai is gonna come meet you]
- Go, go!
- He's coming!
[Keigo's shot!]
Nice!
[Junki's super blocking!]
(Good job, Junki)
[Junki blocks one more time!]
[Mame's shot!]
[Don't you dare!]
Ren-kun! x2
[Iron-wall Spiderman Junki]
Ren-kun! x3
[Team Red quickly changes from defense to attack!]
[Easy goal!]
[Thanks to Spiderman Junki, Team Red leads 3:2]
Nice~
[Team Blue's player change]
[Physical King Sukai is IN]
[Game resumes]
(Checking the point to pass)
(Fire!)
[Sukai's perfect long pass]
[And subsequent goal!]
[Successful super assist!]
(Roar!)
[Current Score]
Team Blue: 3　-　Team Red: 3
[Team Red has excellent speed and clean passes]
(You can't get it)
(You won't get it)
Protect it! Protect it!
(LOL)
[Sudden shot]
Move fast!
[Will they score...?]
[Don't you dare!]
[Rocket speed~]
[Rocket pass]
Dangerous!
[Keigo scores!]
[Sukai's consecutive assist]
[Team Blue is winning 4:3 thanks to Sukai's excellent play]
[Ren's long~ pass]
[Sukai blocks]
[Sukai is the best]
Nice! Go!!
[Here I come~]
Stop him! x2
[He intends to push his way through to the goal]
Stop him!
(Flung out)
[Attacker Sukai charges]
[The opponents fall one by one]
[Go, Sukai-mon*!]
(*T/N: Pokemon reference)
[He looks like he would chew off everything]
(Dunk!!!)
Here!
[Sukai scored against three players using his strength alone]
[The! Best!]
[Team Blue is winning 5:3]
We'll do our best!
[Team Red is gearing up]
[Syoya's long pass]
[Easy score!]
[Team Red gained +1 point]
[Water basketball is heating up]
[Ren's super long shot]
[Team Red gained +1 point]
[The neck-to-neck battle continues]
Nice~
[Current Score]
Team Blue: 5　-　Team Red 5
(One more point until the victory)
[Team Red's attack]
[Junki's ambush shot!]
[Did it... go in?!]
[I won't let that happen]
Nice!
[The game resumes]
Let's do this together!
[The last one point is the most important]
It's the last one!
(Sukai, take it!)
[Sukai forces his way in with his power]
(Just then!)
[The ball is stolen while he was distracted]
Nice! x2
[Ruki did it]
[Chance goes to Team Red]
[Neck-to-neck]
Go, go, Syoya!
Go! x5
[Team Red's ferocious teamwork]
- My ball!
- Go! x3
[Perfect chance to score]
[Ruki's shot!]
(Oh, no~)
[Sukai's rebound]
OK!
[Team Red hurries back to their positions]
[Sukai charges]
Let's go!
(Hurry;;) (Hurry;;)
(Raises~)
[Takumi, take it!]
(Soars)
(Intense battle)
[Perfect chance to the unguarded goal?]
(Throws~)
[Goal!]
Yeah!
Yes~
[Shot followed by splendid technique]
[Dramatic score]
[The victory goes to Team Blue]
[Team Red did their best until the end]
[Everyone became one and enjoyed the time]
(It was the best)
[Water Basketball Match]
Team Blue wins 6:5!
[While they were laughing and having fun, The Sun has started to set]
I can hear the sound of the waves
I want to go in!
They are the coaches
[Coach Kim Minsu]　-　[Coach Lee Hanseung]
Nice to meet you!
Please take a good care of us~
Hello!
[The last course of Pool FLEX: Surfing lesson, start!]
When you lie down...
Leave a size of a hand from the tail of the board
[STEP 1: Lying down on board]
Good! This is the basic position
Now, in this position...
[STEP 1: Lying down on board]
Raise your chest up about a fist size above the board
[STEP 2: Raise chest above the board]
Paddle along the lane. One, two!
[STEP 3: Paddle using both arms]
One, two!
(One, two!)
[JO1 copy pretty fast]
One, two!
Now, push up
[STEP 4: Push up the chest]
Put your hands underneath your chest! Straight up! Push!
[STEP 5: Stand on the board]
Right foot! Left foot!
Okay, good!
If you are stiff you will fall. So, try loosening up
[Relax the body in order not to fall]
[Everyone together, relax〜]
Relax. Okay~
[That's overly relaxing LOL]
Now, let's connect the positions faster! Push! Up!
[Start with paddling]
- Next, paddling~
- One, two!
One, two! One, two!
- Push... Up!
- Ouch!
(It hurts)
- Good. Nice~
- Up!
Okay, that's good
[From now on... It's show time]
Now, we'll go into the water
(Great~)
So fast!
Please take good care of me
- Let's go in! Take your boards
- Yes!
[Let's sail towards the waves!]
Heavy!
[Expectation rises up with the surge of the waves]
- There are waves
- It's dangerous!
[How will JO1's surfing skill be?]
- I'm soaked!
- Awesome!
[It's as refreshing as being in real waves]
[JO1 in the water, it's time to start real surfing]
Okay, good. Paddling!
[His paddling is good! Now, push up!]
[Shosei disappeared like magic...?]
[Take-off failed]
[Keigo challenges!]
[He couldn't balance and fell over]
Paddle! x3
[Takumi starts!]
[After paddling he stood up smoothly...!]
[But, falls into water!]
(LOL)
Okay, paddle!
Paddle! x3
[Sukai & Ruki paddle forward at the same time!]
Up!
[Double flip-over]
[The youngest is going, too~!]
[Mame's amazing water show(?)]
Wonderful!
[Members are busy falling down here and there]
[But it's a lot of fun ^_^]
[Junki goes!]
Go! Paddle!
(Sigh~ It's difficult;;)
[Real surfing is different from practice on land]
- Surfing? Relax!
- Relax
- Push~ up and down. OK?
- Okay!
[The coach teaches one more time step by step]
We can do it! x2
Isn't the wave too big?
This is too insane, isn't it?
It's coming, it's coming!
The wave is here!
It's too big!
The wave is huge!
[Gigantic wave appeared]
[They are nervous in front of the big wave]
- It's almost here!
- It came! x3
(Yakety-yak)
It arrived!
[Members who are ready go first!]
(Splash)
[Sukai fell before even standing up]
(Starts paddling)
[Push~ up!]
Wow~
[Successful take-off]
[Solid success]
Ren-kun is good!
[Mame follows!]
I almost did it, right?
[Narrowly succeeded!]
Mame did it, awesome!
[Smooth take-off from Ruki as well]
Wow! Awesome! x3
(Jealous)
[Smooth take-off from Ruki as well]
[Shosei's turn]
(Shaky) (Shaky)
Let's go! Shosei!
[Shosei succeeded as well]
[Make a way for Shion!]
[Push~ up!]
(Splash~!)
[Save Shion...]
This is too difficult!
[Meanwhile Syoya spectacularly succeeded as well]
So cool~!
(Yay~)
[Next member, Junki is ready too]
[I'll show you this time~]
(Slips~)
[Fell in water within 0.1 second after the push-up LOL]
(OK~ I got the hang of it)
[Powerful start from Takumi!]
[Will he succeed just like this?]
(Shaky)  (Shaky)
(Splash!)
[Keigo challenges!]
[His awesomeness is exploding!]
[Best feeling ever!]
Did you catch that?
＃surfing_genius
＃surfing_was_the_easiest
#marine_boy_Keigo
[After two days of work at the farm and fishing villages]
This is impossible! x2
[They got to taste sweet FLEX tour]
All together?
[Everyone fell in love with surfing]
[Next episode]
[For JO1 who have worked hard so far]
- It's hot!
- It's hard
[Hello Tour prepared]
Whelks!
[Arranged only for JO1]
Let's start JO1 Unity Competition!
[JO1 Unity Competition]
[We have prepared presents for JO1]
There are gifts as well
[This part is for JAMs!]
[Best scenes from the unity competition.zip]
(Present for you LOL)
[Playing gesture game]
You guys are talking too much
[Got it! Circus!]
(Of course not)
[He is really speaking with his body]
(The end)
[Shocked]
(Cannot even guess)
[They are this serious about the competition...?]
I'm gonna go! I'm gonna go first!
(Make a way!)
[They are this serious about the competition...?]
I'm gonna go! I'm gonna go first!
[HAPPY]
[FYI there is no cash prize]
(Invincible fingertips)
Red light, green light!
[There may be odd moments...]
[Please focus on many cute scenes]
[AND]
Scary~ I'm scared
[Finally]
I'm scared
[The long-awaited]
What do you think about this?
[Highlight of the competition]
[A game with about 100 boxes]
(Let me pass~)
(Breath-holding)
(Suspense)
(Oh, shoot... LOL)
(LOL)
(Embarrassed;;)
[There was someone...? LOL]
We didn't see anything
[Two nights and three days itinerary full of fun]
[A special competition finale to commemorate the tour]
Correct!
[It's more fun with everyone together >.<]
No way!
We did it!
[Hello Tour is full of laughter until the very last]
(Claps)
[You won't be disappointed]
Let's meet again next week~