Mountain and sea travel programs
[From Produce 101 Japan]
[11 boys who made the debut they dreamed of]
[They are already into their third year]
[Welcome to Korea]
(Pit-a-pat)
[JO1 came to visit Korea 0_<]
(Heart-fluttering)
[At a farm and fishing village]
Welcome~!
It's on sale~!
[They work for their own trip]
[JO1's self-sufficient tour]
Please enjoy
[Handsome = universal
(His face is) working hard]
(Travel expenses +10 earned)
[Handsome = universal
(His face is) working hard]
Ah! This. Very. Delicious~?
[This]
(Travel expenses +10 earned)
[What? ...Why are you good at this]
(Travel expense +10 +20 earned)
Get your king crab~
It's really delicious~
(Travel expense +10 +20 +50 earned)
[Experiencing Korea is sweet^^]
[Is it?]
(Current temperature: 35°C)
I'm tired. Aahh.. TT
[It's not easy to make money]
It's hot-.-;;
Aah, this! Help my face... Smelly!
[It's not easy to make money]
It smells -.-;;
- Oh my~ What should I do~
- Hello~
Oh my~
Thank you for your hard work today
This is the result
[Get your day's pay]
[This is what we worked for]
[Since we got money, at night...]
We came to Hongdae~
[Those who worked hard, play hard.
-JO1-]
- Can I get the receipt?
- Yes
[Those who worked hard, play hard.
-JO1-]
[Hip and cool right here. I earn I spend, JO1 style]
[Tough life experience during the day]
Hello!
[Hip flexing at night]
[JO1’s Hell? No]
Right foot~ left foot~ One more time!
[JO1's Hello Tour]
Starts now
[On one fine day for a trip]
- We are here!
- We have arrived!
[Good bye reality. Hello Tour! Find your dream and adventure!]
[This is where JO1's first tour will be planned]
[Industry's best wealth of data]
[Guides catered to customers’ taste]
[Welcome to Hello tour!]
Hello~
(Stops)
[What's with this strange entrance?]
(This place) ..is it alright?
Yes, this way please
[We won't hurt you, please come in]
(Automatic deep bow;;)
(Call me later~)
(LOL)
You are not being filmed
Come in, everyone
Hello~
Please wait for a second
I'm looking forward to this
President~
I'm excited~
[Why is JO1 visiting the travel agency?]
[JO1 filled out To Do List for their time in Korea]
[An itinerary that reflects JO1’s preference will be created based on the questionnaires]
It’s our first time to travel all together
That's true
What do you want to do?
Since we are in Korea...
Travel to Jeju Island?
(Tempted)
I'd like to go there
Anywhere else?
Forest?
Somewhere like forest
We can go to forest in Japan too
I'm curios if Korea's forest is different
Like, things that are there
[JO1 members have thought of places they’d like to visit]
Oii!
(Surprised)
Hello!
[Name: Kangnam
Title: CEO of HELLO Paradise
JO1’s K-Tour Special Guide]
(Loud) (Loud)
Hello!
(LOL)
Hi, everyone!
I’m Kangnam, the CEO of Hello Paradise
Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you~
We are Hello Paradise Tour
I came today because I heard you want to travel
Has anyone traveled to Korea before?
- Not yet
- You haven't?
If that's so
I’ve prepared some travel options to recommend
(Thank you so much)
Awesome!
By the way, how much Korean can you speak?
Shion... A little bit...
- You can speak a little?
- Yes!
You sound very good
- You can tell just from that?
- Yeah, just from that
Your intonation of “yes” was good
Then you are not that advanced in Korean
Okay, I got it. Maybe just the greetings
So, for you...
I brought something from Planet Namek (feat. Dragon Ball)
(Translation device)
Take one for each
Thank you
[JO1 puts on the device for smooth communication]
Waah, awesome!
Everyone can hear me well?
Yes~  ❛⁠ε❛⁠ ♪
[Why is JO1 here?]
What is the reason you are here?
We want to travel!
- Because you want to travel
- Yes
So I will show you the PPT we've prepared
[PPT Targeting JO1's Preference]
Round of applause to Yujin-chan
[Youngest staff: In charge of PPT]
[K-Tour PPT for JO1, Start]
[A Course: Ambient, healing trip in a forest]
[Member who’d like a holiday in forest?]
Hands up if this is your thing?
(Ruki)
[Member who’d like a holiday in forest?]
Yes~ It's me
Why? Are you stressed these days?
Not that I'm stressed
How should I put it...
There are times when I want to be in nature
That means you are stressed!
(Stress) (Stress)
(LOL)
You must be stressed a lot
Then, moving on!
[A light walk to Cheonwang Peak, Jiri Mountain. Elevation 1,915m]
Waah, great!
Cheonwang Peak; 1,915m
[Relaxing time at Jiri Mountain with quality air and water]
This is Jiri Mountain. A light walk to Cheonwang Peak
We will be going 1,915m upward
[Hiking Jiri Mountain to 1,915m high summit]
- Really?
- Yes
[Hiking Jiri Mountain to 1,915m high summit]
It’ll take 5 hours to the peak from here
Including the time we get to the foot of the mountain
(5 hours...?)
Because it’s exhausting and loathsome...!
You will forget the stress
[Miraculous logic that you can forget stress with another stress]
- You get rid of the stress with a stress
- Right!
[Miraculous logic that you can forget stress with another stress]
Has anyone done hiking before?
[Which member has hiked before?]
I've done it before
You have? In Tokyo?
I've climbed Fuji Mountain
Fuji Mountain?
That's pretty high
Mount Fuji's...
Did you reach the top?
- Yes, I went to the top
- Then this may be easy for you
(Elevation 3,776m)
- Yes, I went to the top
- Then this may be easy for you
[JO1’s hidden hiking professional, Ruki]
B Course!
B Course: A luxurious holiday trip at the sea!
Enjoy the vast ocean
This is the kind of place we’ll be going to
[Healing time at heaven on earth where endless horizon unrolls]
For your intimate time
We’ve planned 6 nights 7 days
(6 nights 7 days…?)
For real?
(LOL)
You will have to dig your own toilet
Get into this part and dig
[Handle your own business & food procurement]
And catch fish at night to feed yourself
6 nights 7 days…
Once you go in you can’t come out
(Horrified)
At the mountain if you feel too tired you can go back
But from the island, you can’t
[No way back from the island]
It's for your solidarity!
You will have unprecedented bond!
[The solidarity will tighten]
Give us the next slide~
12-Dish Korean Traditional Cuisine & Hanwoo
[The entire course meal will be the finest Korean table d’hote]
Hanwoo is expensive Korean beef
[Best part of travel?]
What is travel about? Relieving your stress through food
[Mukbang!]
That's why we prepared something like this too
[Which member eats the most?]
Who likes eating the most here?
(Syoya)
Oh! Do you eat a lot?
Kimata Syoya
I love food
- You tend to eat a lot?
- Yes, I eat a lot
Then let's leave him out~
Because it's expensive!
[In order to save the expenses, Syoya’s sacrifice(?) is required]
So these are the options we have prepared
And then... Travel expenses!
Now, the most important part. We need to talk about money
[The most important time has come - Payment]
With all the discounts and benefits we can provide...
With every cut we can make~
It's 1 million won per person!
[Necessary budget per person: 1 million won]
1 million won??
Including all the discounts, it’s 1 million won
[1 million x 11 people
Total amount = 11,000,000 won]
[No way]
This is wrong
- For one day...?
- 10,000 yen for one day?
For one day?!
Aigoo~
(LOL)
No aigo, no aigo
Let’s not cheap out
Cough up 1 million
[Give me 1 million!]
(He’s showing his true color..;;)
He’s dangerous! Scary! Scary!
- We don't have time. We don't have money
- You got no money?
We have no salary
You don't have salary?
(Clicks tongue)
(LOL)
[Emergency meeting due to unexpected situation]
Let's take a sidebar. I thought they'd have some money
Please wait for a bit while we discuss
[Emergency meeting for all the employees]
It’s impossible
1 million won is impossible
[Customer complaints bursting out at the insane price]
- It’s for one day, right?
- One day, per person
[Customer complaints bursting out at the insane price]
It’s a rip-off!
(LOL)
This company is suspicious
Shion, how do I say “expensive” in Korean?
"Bi-ssa-da"
"Bissayo"
Very "bissayo"!
[Learning real life Korean through experience]
They are coming out
[CEO Kangnam looks serious]
(Nervous)
Just for you... At the end of a long discussion, we came up with a new tour plan
[A new tour plan specifically designed for JO1]
Thank you
[Voilà, Self-sufficient Tour]
Shelf.. suf-?
Chef...surf...$#&??
"Jikyū jisoku" tour = "Jageub jajok" (Self-sufficient tour)
Ah-ha~ Understood
The first course is a sheep ranch in a farm village
[Wide green meadow surrounded by Mother Nature]
[Where you are welcomed by freely romping sheep]
Second course is fishing village!
[A seafood market with lively atmosphere]
[Fresh seafood party every day]
(That’s my style~)
Next one...
Third course is city!
[Enjoying the night street. City’s nights are more beautiful than it’s days]
Work during the day, play at night
[Self-sufficient tour, what do you think?]
Are you okay with this? How do you feel about this?
We like it!
For me, I’d rather pay 1 million and go on tours like these
(LOL)
[In a farm & fishing village]
It's so fun
We'll work hard!
[In a farm & fishing village]
Slowly, slowly
[Made only for JO1. Self-sufficient tour, coming soon]
I'm sure it's alright
- In about an hour, meet me at the front of the building after you are prepared
- Alright!
Yujin-chan! Please give them an encouraging word
(Suddenly?;;)
(LOL)
[Big laughs thanks to her]
JO1 do your best, ganbare~
(Tight fist)
Then I’ll see you in an hour!
Then, let’s go!
(See you later~^^)
(Thump)
[One hour later, time for departure]
We are leaving!
Leggo leggo!
[Members are excited about their first K-tour]
We are going~
[Full of expectation and excitement, JO1's self-sufficient tour]
[Departing to the first destination now~]
We are going to Gapyeong
It’s JO1’s first time to travel all together, right?
First trip as OT11!
[Korea became their first travel destination…]
Yeah and it’s in Korea
[Let’s not lose this momentum... and have fun!]
Since we are all together, let’s enjoy this!
If we had more money we could have gone to the A or B course…
(LOL)
[JO1’s self-sufficient tour will be filled with new experiences]
[We are leaving with a heart full of expectation & excitement]
[Greeted by warm sunshine and cool breeze]
- Welcome!
- Thank you
[Welcome to Gapyeong]
Kono! Thanks for coming this far
This is a place called Gapyeong
It seems to be getting more popular among tourists these days
[You can feed the sheep by yourself]
[And meet the sheep freely running around]
[A place where you can enjoy nature closer]
You can see animals over there
Is this a donkey?
[Donkey and alpacas are also here~]
There is also alpaca
[Being in wide open nature makes the mood goes up]
Amazing!
It's beautiful
Wonderful!
[This is a sheep ranch, where JO1 will be working for the day~]
For now, you can go see alpacas, or eat something
Have some free time!
[15 minutes free time!]
Look around as you please! It's a free time
[After free time they will divide chores]
- I can already see them
- Amazing!
(Mehhhh~)
- They cry "mehhh"
- I heard "mehhh"! It's my first time actually hearing it
They actually cry "mehhh"!
[These four are going to see the sheep]
I almost thought a person was making that noise
Pretty~ Pretty~
(Cute)
Pretty?
Bon appetit
Nom nom nom nom nom
[Cuties in front of cuties]
Cute~
The sound from their teeth is kinda amazing
Yeah they make a lot of sound
Wah! Cute~
You have teeth?
That sheep is staring at us hard
(Come hither a bit~)
You are staring too much
It is so big!
(Stares)
- You stare too much
- Huge!
(Stares)
(Yum yum)
I can see the teeth
It's as if the sheep is saying “give me something to eat”
(Meehh~~~) (Mehh~)
(Meehhh~~~)
Whoa! Amazing!
[Cannot understand but they are talking and talking]
(Amazed)
(Passionate conductor)
[Sheepchestra trio reverberating in Gapyeong]
They are separated by musical scale
The further you go, the lower they are
(Mehh→↘__)
(Bursts out laughing)
Isn't that too low?
(Mehh→↘__)
(LOL)
He must be a veteran
He's a boss. Boss!
(Salute)
It's a nice weather today~
It looks like my hometown
- Is it that rural?
- Maybe not this much
[Taking a walk together]
- Is it that rural?
- Maybe not this much
But if you go further in, then it’s kind of like this
[While walking, something stole their attention]
Awesome!
It is tiny. Cute~
What is this in Korean?
- It is "yang"
- Yang!
"Yang"!
Cute "yang"!
[Let's go see the sheep]
- Hello
- Wow!
It's cute
[I'm hungry, meh~]
I don't have food
(Then bye~)
(LOL)
Well then, let's go
(Meeeh~)
They cry like, "Eu~aangg~"
Wasn't I similar?
Now that I think about it, in Japan they cry "meh~"
But here it's a little different
"U~~waa~~nnggg~"
That's not even a cry of an animal
That's screaming
U~~waa~~nnggg~!!
If you see the sun you become like that*
(*T/N: Speaking nonsense)
[Sweet break is over]
[JO1 and Kangnam reunited in one place]
How was it?
Good~
What was good for you?
- The atmosphere (was good)!
- You liked the atmosphere!
(Agrees)
The atmosphere... That's nice
So now... There’s an important purpose to this trip
We are going to make you work
(It’s finally here)
Because you said you don’t have money
We’ve prepared this for you
Thank you
There are going to be team A, B and C
What Team A will be doing is...
《Team A's To Do》
✅ Cleaning sheep sheds
"Nyang... chuksha... chomseo...? Yancha nakseo*?"
(*T/N: Doodling in Korean)
(LOL)
"Yang chuksa cheongso"
"Yang~ chukkusha cheongso..."
Shuksha~ Syoji...;;
Together!
Cleaning sheep sheds
Also, handing out hay to visitors at the hay exchange center
《Team A's To Do》
✅ Cleaning sheep sheds
✅ Handing out hay
Also, handing out hay to visitors at the hay exchange center
《Team A's To Do》
✅ Cleaning sheep sheds
✅ Handing out hay
And then Team B
《Team B's To Do》
✅ Preparing ice cups and serving at cafe
✅ Decorating desserts
(Mouth-watering)
《Team B's To Do》
✅ Preparing ice cups and serving at cafe
✅ Decorating desserts
[That sounds fun!]
And making dough at the bakery
(Sparkle) (Sparkle)
As for Team C~
《Team C's To Do》
✅ Walking and feeding the animals
From now on, we will choose the team leaders using this bottle
[Choosing leaders of each team by spin the bottle!]
The leaders will pick their team members one by one
We’ll start with Team A's leader
[Who will be the leader of the cleaning & hay team?]
(Nervous)
(Don't let it be me)
[Thank God]
[Syoya is selected as Team A's leader]
(Congrats)
Congratulations!
Okay, moving onto the next
We will choose Team B's leader
[Sweetest job, cafe team's leader?]
Team B will decorate desserts
[The easiest job that all the members strongly want]
(Wishing to be chosen 1)
(Wishing to be chosen 2)
(Wishing to be chosen 3)
(Please) (Please) (Please) (Please) (Please) (Please) (Please)
[Who will be the leader of Team B?]
[The direction… is not clear]
[Junki won]
Okay, Kono-kun!
(Really~?)
(It was close~)
[Junki is the Team B's leader!]
- Kono!
Please say a word towards the camera
I’m Junki. Nice to meet you
[Sweet job, here I come~]
Let's start!
(Junki~ I’m envious)
[Lastly, Team C. Leader of the walking & feeding sheep team?]
Now let’s select C Team’s leader. 1, 2!
(Spin) (Spin)
Kono one more time, Kono one more time!
[Ren is chosen as the Team's leader!]
Ren-chan~ Ren-chan!
[Team B's leader: JUNKI - Team C's leader: REN - Team A's leader: SYOYA]
Leaders, please stand up
[They will decide the teammates with rock, paper and scissors]
- With RPS?
- Yes
[They will decide the teammates with rock, paper and scissors]
- With RPS?
- Yes
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
[Team B's leader, Junki won!]
(Let’s see)
(Stares)
Leader!
[There’s no question about it, Sho the leader of JO1 is chosen!]
- He likes coffee
- I love coffee
[Sho who loves coffee is perfect for Team B]
[Team B's cafe job goes to Sho]
Thank you very much
[It’s turn for Team A and C's leaders to choose]
Then, let's do RPS one more time again
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
[Team A's leader, Syoya won!]
I’d like to choose who wants to be in my team...
Tsurubo Shion!
(It's okay... It's okay)
[Automatically it’s Team C's leader, Ren’s turn]
Ren-chan, who will you pick?
Well, enthusiasm is important, so-
[Ren chooses Sukai who has the biggest heart]
Congrats!
(I wanted to go to the cafe though)
[Speeding up the rest of the game]
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
(Syoya lost)
[Team C's leader, Ren won!]
Ruki!
[Ruki is chosen by walking the sheep team]
[One more round!]
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
[Team A's leader Syoya won!]
I’d like to work with someone who is eager
(Gained one more worker to clean the sheds +1)
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
(Ren lost)
[Team B's leader, Junki won!]
Capacity: 4 people  -  3 people  -  4 people
[There’s only one more spot left in cafe team]
Who are you going to choose, Junki?
Who wants to go to the cafe?
Me, Keigo!
(Shooting up the hand)
(He’s fast LOL)
(Desperate) (Desperate)
Please!!! Junki!!!
(LOL)
So, who is it?
- Keigo, you wanna go?
- I wanna go!
[Has Junki decided on to take Keigo?]
You really wanna go?
(Yup nope)
Mame!
[He chose Mame]
(Oh, come on!)
I knew it
(Sorry) (Sorry)
[Team B: JUNKI SHO MAME]
Then, maknae* Issei. Issei, Mame-chan. Mame-chan, congrats!
(*T/N: Youngest one)
[The greenery deepened after rain]
It’s been raining a lot recently, but today is sunny
It's really raining a lot lately
[Team A + C are leaving to meet the sheep]
We bring the sun out
- We are the sun bringers
- Certainly
Hello
(Meeh~ )
Hello. Please take good care of us
(Welcome)
How old are these guys?
They are three months old
(3 months old babies)
(Meeh~)
Why are they crying?
Because they don’t like us?
Whenever people pass, they cry asking for food
- They are crying because they want food
- I see
Now, shall we get to work?
Let’s take the sheep out and have them go for a walk. Let's go!
[It’s time to pasture the sheep]
Sheep are coming out!
(It’s time for a walk~)
Come here!
(This way)
Come this way!
(Sheep in the 4th shed are coming out first~)
Here!
Oh, they are out! They are out
(Trots)
You, you guys...
(Sheep in the 3rd shed are slightly scared)
(Hesitates)
(This way)
[Going for a walk is fun~]
(Scaredy sheep)
You should go too!
(It's okay) Come here~
This way!
Here here here!
[On the verge of going, then U turn]
Over here! Ah, this guy
Leggo leggo leggo!
[Meanwhile, sheep from 4th and 5th sheds head to the pasture]
(Let’s play in the large ranch~)
(I want to play too~)
(Slips)
(Oops;;)
[Finally The Fussy escaped the shed, too]
It came out!
Ah! It came!
(Halts)
(Meeh~ )
(Runs)
(Jumps)
- It's fast
- Woaah!
(I fly)
It flew!
Cute~
So energetic
Come here! Get in
[Remaining sheep went in as well!]
They are strong
Ren Team, please go on a walk with them!
[Walking and feeding the sheep, start!]
I'm scared~
Wait, wait
(Cheerful~)
(I'm excited)
Will I be scolded if I give this much to one sheep?
(Shush- It's a secret!)
Awesome!
[Cutie next to a cutie.jpg]
You are cute~
(Jumps) (Jumps)
[Follow Sukai~!]
Ah, this is fun
It is so fun now
[While Team C is having fun, what’s Team A doing?]
They are very friendly
What are they doing?
Are they even working?
Looks like they are having fun
[They are even more excited than the sheep!]
[Keigo and Shosei are separating hay]
Is the other team gonna buy the hay?
We need to grab this much in one go
How is it?
Isn't that small?
Is it?
(Putting in to the fullest)
(Perfect at one go)
Oh~ You are good
Well done~
Come to the store! It's on sale~
We are on sale?
It's 200 yen but is on sale?
It's on sale~!
"On sale", he said
After I became JO1...
I never imagined I'd be filling hay like this
It's fun~ ♪
- This is...
- A life experience
- Exactly
Ah, it smells...!
[Shion and Syoya are cleaning the sheds]
It’s hard to sweep the poops
This is no joke
(Working hard)
What should we do with the water?
Let’s stop here for a bit~
Why don’t you go to the hay shop, grab hays and give them to the babies?
[Get hay from Keigo & Shosei]
- What’s wrong?
- There’s a bug
Do it one more time!
(Flaps) (Flaps)
One more time
[Sudden performance in the shed]
Nice! Very nice
[Talents who can even turn shed into stage]
Nice~ Wooh!
Ice hockey-!
(Time to stop~)
Now, let's go
[To the hay, GO]
(Working hard)
Welcome~
Welcome!
Please give us two
Two?
I need two as well
Thank you so much
Please enjoy~(?)
Please enjoy
- Hi~
-Hello
[Back to the shed after getting the hay]
[Right into the sheep's mouth]
One more time... Wah! Oh!
(Fierce mukbang)
(Nom nom)
You have amazing eyes
Yeah, they got great eyes
(Eating well~)
They are small
Look! They are so small
[Kindly taking care of baby lambs as well]
They are so cute
Eat a lot~
(Half-eaten hays)
Let's clean up here too
[Sweeping from top to bottom]
From the top!
(Sweeps)
This reminds me of my school days
Look at him!
How do you say "glutton" in Korean?
- "Mukbo!"
- "Mukbo..."
Mukbo! Do you want to eat this?
It’s been dropped on the ground
We’ll give you something better
[They are busy persuading the baby sheep]
We really can't give these to them though?
- I guess it's dirty
- Yeah
Let's feed them delicious ones
(I'm hungry!)
Whoa~! Please calm down
- Calm down
- Please calm down
(I'm hungry, meeh~)
- Calm down
- Please calm down
(With cameras to their backs) (Working hard)
[Meanwhile, what is Team B doing at the cafe?]
[Working hard under the cool air from air conditioner]
What do I do when I clean this?
[Sho turned into a one-day barista]
This, levelling, tamping, grinder and then espresso machine...
[He is diligently learning how to make coffee]
[*Filmed in accordance with the guidelines of health authorities*]
This, levelling, tamping, grinder and then espresso machine...
That's okay, too?
This is caramel sauce
Caramel sauce!
We use this for caramel macchiato
- What is this one?
- This is vanilla syrup. For vanilla latte
What do I say when the drink is ready?
"Iced americano nawasseumnida~"
"Nawasseumnida~"
(Got it!)
It's ready. Please enjoy~
- It's fun~
- Are you having fun?
I love coffee
(Agrees)
Kono-kun is working hard
[Passion MAX]
Junki is very cool
[He is doing photoshoot while working]
#sheep_farm                        #handsome_part_timer
(Wipes)
Junki is working hard. So, I’d like to make him an iced americano
- Is that okay?
- Of course
Thank you
[Barista Sho's time]
One iced americano
(Rattling)
It has to be 20g
(Tamping hard)
[Doing well as he learned]
I love this
I'm done!
[Junki is back after done cleaning the cafe]
Okay!
(Eager to work)
What's next?
This is for soft ice cream
[Time to try making soft ice cream]
(Soft ice cream machine)
Have you ever used this?
I’ve used it once, when I was a kid
Will I be able to do it?
(Careful) (Careful)
Put in the ice... And then water up to here?
[When the ice cup is ready, pour the espresso over]
[Barista Sho’s iced americano is done!]
It looks really tasty!
[Junki’s ice cream is done too!]
(Tada-!)
(Better than expected)
Please enjoy
(Found the ice cream)
Awesome. You are good!
(Proud) (Proud)
[A gift for Junki who's working hard]
An iced americano for Junki who’s been working hard
- Really~?
- Yes
Then for Sho who's also been working hard
[A gift for Sho who's working hard]
Ah! Thank you
May I?
Let me dig in~
(A big sip)
(Yum)
It's delicious
- It's really good
- It is
It's better than the ones from Sho's room
This one is no joke either
Try it
[Heartwarming cafe team_MOV]
[At the same time, at the bakery?]
(Putting on bakery uniform)
[Done getting ready]
(Baking teacher) (Baking teacher)
Please take a good care of me!
I'm in your care
[After the lively greeting...]
(Awkward silence)
(Do something...)
Um... Have you ever baked bread before?
No, I have not
What kind of bread do you like...?
The kind of bread I like... I like croissant
(LOL)
[Putting the awkwardness behind, baking bread START]
There are a lot of breads
They all look delicious
[First batch is Mame’s favorite, croissants~]
[Cut fresh bread in half, then generously fill up with cream
(Give it a go!)
Will I be able to do it?
[JO1’s maknae’s first try at piping cream!]
(Focus) (Focus)
How is it?
I think I did a good job?
Yes. You did
I can't tell at all
Do you mean it?
[It's an empty talk, right?]
You are humoring me
I don't think I've seen breads like this, with blueberry
Doesn’t Japan has this too, cream croissant?
Are there? I don’t think I’ve seen it
[If you top it up with blueberries, it’s done!]
I don’t normally get much chance to bake breads
So this is a valuable experience
Thank you
They look so delicious
[2 hours since the work has begun]
This way
Welcome!
[Team A's Ren & Takumi are visiting the hay exchange center]
You two will grab hay stacks and bring them to alpacas
Give us some hay, please
(Stacks of hay)
Please take it from them, it must be heavy
[They make a good team]
- Nice!
- It's heavy
[They make a good team]
- Nice!
- It's heavy
(It's huge;;;)
[One more coming~]
It looks heavy
1, 2!
(Massive)
Okay, let's go
To the alpacas!
Fighting!
- You can do it!
- Let's do this!
(Playing hooky?)
(I got you!)
You should do it too!
It looks heavy
- Good, good
- He needs support from the side
- You gotta support from the side and go together
- Fighting!
Let's go to the alpacas!
You can do it
[You have to be back and forth four times]
Let's go
(Gaaaaargh~)
Oh, no!
[It's pretty far to where the alpacas are]
Alpaca! Please come to us
It's farther than it looks
Ah, wait! It’s a little...
[Danger] [Danger]
What is it? Take turn?
[Change players]
1, 2!
[Alpacas, here we come]
Let's go to the alpacas!
- Heavy!
- Is it?
- Would you like one more?
- NO!!!
Okay. Leggo leggo!
[Almost there!]
- Alpaca!
The road is a bit narrow here
Why don't we change the roles again?
[Change players]
Alright alright!
Pump it up and go
- It's an uphill!
He noticed it was an uphill and changed with you
We are almost there
[They entered the uphill]
Alright alright!
The alpacas are waiting for you
[Finally arrived at the alpaca ranch!]
Their necks are skinny!
Why are their necks so long?
(Thanks for coming)
Thank you for the hard work
[This was just the beginning, real work starts now!]
Now we need to spread the hay
Please cover the patch of dirt over there with hay
(Right over here!)
Aren’t they staring at us too much?
I. Am. Watching. You.
They do stare hard
Hi~
[Polite greeting to alpacas first]
- Hi~
- Hello
[Works up a courage and gets close]
- Hi~
- Hello
[Works up a courage and gets close]
[FAILED]
1, 2!
Ah, this! You can do it!
Alright alright!
1, 2!
Okay! Good good!
Let's hurry up
Get it quick! One more time!
(+1 hay stack)
1, 2! Alright alright!
[No time to rest, leaving again for the hay refill]
(Haah... It's exhausting)
[Ren starts on arranging the hay]
It's like sprinkle toppings
It smells like tatami*
(*T/N: A type of Japanese traditional flooring mat)
Nice~ Do it like sprinkle toppings
(Scatter) (Scatter)
"It's sprinkle toppings~" Try saying it
It’s sprinkle toppings~
[Full of sprinkles]
It's heartfelt sprinkle toppings
(Sudden interests from the alpacas)
Oh! They eat those
(Let me taste it)
He must have been hungry
Are you hungry?
(Silence~)
[Will they be able to acquaint?]
Oh! He's getting closer
(Turns)
He wants to get close
Ah~ You should have stayed still
He wants to get close! Ah~ You should have stayed still
[Let's give it some time~]
It's sprinkle toppings~
[Meanwhile, how's cafe team doing?]
After this, one iced americano and one vanilla latte
[Busy! Orders are pouring in]
Iced americano is ready
Thank you. Please enjoy~
[No need to teach him twice]
Yes~ Thank you
This was the number 3
Enjoy your drinks~ Thank you
[Handing over the orders is easy breezy too]
Woahh!
[Bread King Mame has come]
It is bread
[So proud of our maknae]
- It's from bakery
- Bakery?
- Yes
- Awesome
(Let's see)
Did Mame make these?
Yes, this, here
If I may explain... These ones are anko butter breads
[Red bean paste & butter combination]
[Sweet & savoury, irresistible anko butter bread]
- They look delicious
- Of course
I made them
You've got to take a look at this
[Entrance of the second breads baked by maknae~]
It looks really good
What is that black thing?
That’s squid ink
The black part is squid ink
[Salty sausage & cheese and flavorful squid ink!]
This looks so good
[You are the best!]
This is really good
- There seems to be one more?
- Yes, one more
Where is it?
This is something that you all love
Cream croissants
There we go
[Brimming cream and blueberries on freshly baked bread~ Cream croissant]
[Our maknae did a good job~]
Mame, you did great
Yeah, I made these
Wonderful!
I heard you were working hard making the coffees
So, I did my best too
- The outfit suits you
- Amazing
(Maknae is the best)
- The outfit suits you
- Amazing
(Maknae is the best)
[Three kinds of breads baked by Mame, finished~!]
[Three hours since they have begun]
Let’s herd the sheep and bring them back to the sheds
Alright?
Team A and C will work together to herd the sheep
Please gather up the sheep over there!
Let’s gather them up!
They are over here too!
Let’s make a round!
Gather them up, please!
Gather them up here!
[Guys, let's go home~!]
Bring them over here please
Run, run!
Sukai-chan, run!
[Sheep are lining up and returning home]
That's good, take them. There are two more at the far end
Atta, girl~
[Sheep are lining up and returning home]
[Herding is going smoothly]
[Sheep at the 4th shed arrived home safely]
[Keigo is on to catch the escapees(?)!]
[Escorting with his entire body]
[Sheep at the 3rd shed arrived]
[We’ll take care of sheep who got strayed~]
[Last sheep arrived home safely as well]
We worked really hard
Mission, complete!
Thank you for your work!
[One day part time at sheep farm ends]
[SELF-SUFFICIENT TOUR ITINERARY]
Time - Plan - Place
✅ 13:00 - Farm Experience - Gapyeong Sheep Ranch
🟩 18:00 - Dinner - Restaurant (Menu: Spicy stir-fried chicken, chicken soup)
🟩 21:00 - Flex - Hongdae (Street of youth and culture)
✅ 18:00 - Dinner - Restaurant (Menu: Spicy stir-fried chicken, chicken soup)
[Where are JO1 members headed to after the work?]
The sound of the river is refreshing
(A restaurant by a small valley)
You did a good job today
And now... This is the result of your day
[After an exhausting day, time to balance today's payment!]
(Expectation rises)
This is the same as grade announcement
[Payment for Team A, shed cleaning + hay distribution]
- Who was Team A's leader?
- Here!
[Team A's leader, Syoya]
- Here you go
- Thank you
(Good job~)
Thank you
(Thick)
How much is it?
It's 150,000 won!
[Team A’s pay is 150,000 won!]
[Team members are satisfied]
We are Team 'A', you know?
[Next, how much did Team B (cafe + bakery) earn?]
(Let's see...)
[They are nervous together]
- How much will it be?
- Aigoo aigoo
[They are nervous together]
(A lot thinner than expected)
(Taken aback)
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
[Team B's pay is 50,000 won]
(Slight disappointment)
[Lastly, Team C(walking+feeding)'s earning is?]
It's heavy!
Really?
(Expanding wishful thinking to maximum)
- Is it really?
- It must be a lie
[NO WAY]
[Now, it's party!]
(Unbelievable)
[Team C's pay is 300,000 won]
Congrats, congrats~
Team C, you got the hardest job right?
Yes...
[If we are to talk about Team C...]
[They moved cart full of hays under the hot sun]
[And knuckled under to the demanding physical labor]
- They were sweating like crazy
- We were
(That's right)
I see no differences from before we started filming
[What about Team B who worked indoor?]
[They are still dry and clean]
I see no differences from before we started filming
(We admit)
[This amount is just right]
We understand and accept the amount
(LOL)
- Anyways, congratulations to Team C
- Thank you very much
[Congratulations to Team C on getting the 1st place]
- Anyways, congratulations to Team C
- Thank you very much
[Congratulations to Team C on getting the 1st place]
Congrats!
However!
[It's not over yet!]
You need to flex at the end of this trip
[The tour’s highlight, ‘FLEX’]
In order to flex, you need 500,000 won
[500,000 won is required for 5 people to flex]
It has to be 500,000 won
(Intrigued)
And the maximum capacity is 5 people
Team C 300,000 won; Team B 50,000 won; Team A 150,000 won
If you add them all, it's 500,000 won
(Don't tell me...)
[A game through which winner gets all]
We're going to play a game
And the winnder gets all the money
[Joy and despair cross]
Team C’s 1st place has lost its meaning
This is no good...
Last place Team B has nothing but to gain
[The game is flicking bottle cap to the farthest]
The game is about making the longest shot
Who is Team A's representative player?
Someone who's strong at this kind of game should go
- Shosei, why don’t you go?
- Shosei, let's go
[Team A’s Shosei will compete!]
[Team B who is dreaming of a plot twist?]
Maknae! Maknae will go
[Team B’s maknae Mame will compete!]
[Team C who can’t afford to lose]
Let's go, Sukai
[Team C's Sukai will compete!]
[Rock paper scissors to determine the turn]
Do RPS!
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
[Team C's Sukai lost]
[Team A's Shosei won]
Um... I'll go last
(Not bad~)
He chose the last
[Team B chooses to go first]
The first!
[Team C automatically will play the second]
- Okay, let's go
- Alright!
[Team C automatically will play the second]
- Well then, Mame!
- Yes
[First player is Team B's Mame]
Everyone remembers, right?
I'll do it!
(Leggo!) (Leggo!)
His hand is shaking
[The tension is palpable]
Way to go!
(Perfect landing)
(Is this possible?)
[Our maknae is the best]
(Oh my God...)
Push it out!
[Pressure x100, Team C's Sukai's turn!]
OK OK!
(Sukai do your best!)
Let's go!
- Team C, your turn!
- Do your best
An angle shot from the corner, nice
[Finger of 300,000 won, ready]
Angle shot from the corner
(I'm going!)
(The direction is wrong;;)
[Sukai sent it to totally wrong direction]
Well well well
(Embarrased)
Isn't that amazing?
It is amazing... But the direction...
[Lastly, Team A's Shosei is on!]
I'll go!
Make is a close-run
[Lastly, Team A's Shosei is on!]
(The goal is to push this out)
Please hit it, please hit it
I'm going!
(Initial direction is good)
(It's over...)
It's okay! You did your best
Who was in Team B?
[Cap flicking game, Team B's victory!]
Team B has three people?
Because there are only 3 people, you can pick 2 more
[Team B can choose two members to go with on the FLEX tour]
You can bring two people more
Up to five people can go
[Face brightens at the good news]
Then please decide through a discussion
I understand
(Shameless appealing)
Good work today
[The real boss of this area, maknae]
(Look at this guy)
Kinjo Sukai...
[I can do anything for FLEX tour!]
Mame is so cute!
He is overdoing it
(Darn...)
(Our maknae is good)
Takumi, why don't you try appealing too?
Appeal...
I'll do my best
(I like that)
[Final decision is left to Team B's leader Junki...]
Leader! Junki, please make your decision
[Junki's choice is...?]
(Desperate)
I want to go to Hongdae~
(Please~)
[KINJO SUKAI!]
[Strong desire does come true]
(LOL)
Well, he did work hard
Next is Keigo!
[Winners of FLEX Tour]
Five of you will go to Hongdae!
The rest will go back to the lodge!
[Everyone, good job today]
Thank you so much for today
[Today's work is over]
[It's time to enjoy delicious meal!]
[Today's menu is spicy stir-fried chicken]
[The hunger had been forgotten by the day's hard work]
I'm so hungry
I'm hungry, very hungry
(Give us food already~)
Aren't you hungry?
(Fixed stare)
[The visual that makes you drool just by looking at it]
[Can't help but sing!]
♪ Pirate pirate We are pirates ♪*
(*T/N: I'm a Pirate, kids song by Otake Ryu)
Then, let's put hands together
1, 2!
Thank you for the meal~!
Please give me a lot~
Oh~ Nice, Sukai
Is this spicy?
It is spicy
This is spicy
[Beware of the spiciness!]
Ah!!! So hot
[Beware of the hot plate too!]
(LOL)
[Second menu is here!]
[The food that keeps your energy up during summer, 'white chicken soup']
[Beautiful silhouette inside white soup]
This! x3 I vouch, it's so good
(A bite for the older brother first~)
[Older brother handing over his serving plate]
Sukai~
Oh, yes of course
[Yielding the biggest piece to Sho leader!]
[Both are surprised at the size of the chicken LOL]
Thanks
[Syoya is biting into rice cake first]
(Amazed)
Delicious?
[Takumi is attacking the meat]
(It's good~)
[Shion who served Keigo first is finally helping himself too]
[Dinner is right up everyone's alley]
Tasty!
It's been a while since we've eaten together like this
Not many places have tables where 11 of us can sit together
Many places don't
We haven't gone eating outside
Everyone, good job in this hot weather
Meeh~ (Good job everyone)
Stop
Meh~ (Me too~)
[All the members gathered in one place, laughing and chatting]
[It looks like one more precious memory will be born]
Next week
[FLEX Tour finally starts]
[Popular spot which is the epitome of youth]
[This is Hongdae]
[Flex Team came to Hongdae]
We've finally arrived in Hongdae!
[Let's go~ V]
[Those who worked hard, flex as you want]
That looks cool
(Thanks^^)
Good work~
[Members enjoy as hard as they worked]
So delicious!
(True feeling 729%)
Why is this so delicious?!
[Meanwhile, the lodge team is...?]
I'm hungry~ I'm really hungry~
[What is flex...?]
Can we get some food..? (poor thing)
You got money?
[They don't look like they do]
[We did]
[But these people took it]
[So we prepared this]
[Cottage industry 3 sets]
[Folding paper cranes... Making bracelets...]
It's smelly
[Picking anchovy poops]
[BEST-O1 does everything they are asked to do]
[Picking anchovy poops] [BEST-O1 does everything they are asked to do]
How is this?
Gotta fill it more (meanie)
[This self-sufficient tour never ends!]
You are strict!
AH...
[Will lodge team...]
[Be able to eat late night snacks...?]
[Second day, fishing village tour]
JO1's self-sufficient tour in fishing village
- Hello~
- Fighting fighting!
JO1's self-sufficient tour in fishing village
(Whelk)
Slowly~
JO1's self-sufficient tour in fishing village
Slow-ly~
(Working hard)
Get this king crab~ It's really delicious~
(Continued mistakes)
(Aakk >.<)
(Very surprised)
[If you're curious about JO1's special day?]
Delicious! Hm~
Be "With Us" next week too~