Translation: Verde (@1DERJAM), Kou (@yokousho)
Timing: Na (@delishriceball)
Quality Check: Na (@delishriceball), Verde (@1DERJAM)
[JO1 Welcome to Korea]
[In the previous episode]
[JO1 visited Hello Tour for a memorable trip in Korea]
- Oii! Hello!!
- Hello!
[JO1 visited Hello Tour for a memorable trip in Korea]
[Tailor-made tour for JO1]
[Work hard during the day and earn money]
It's hot
I'm tired!
[Work hard during the day and earn money]
[Flex in vogue at night]
- We are in Hongdae!
- Hongdae!
[Flex in vogue at night]
Good job today, everyone
[Self-sufficient tour - YES or NO?]
Are you okay with this? How do you feel about this?
(Love it)
[Welcome to HELL(?) TOUR]
Wait, wait!
[Nobody told us it was going to be this hard;]
[In charge of walking and feeding the sheep]
Ahh~ Wait, this is hard!
Welcome~ It's on sale~
[In charge of hay and the sheds]
Are you okay?
(I'm not)
[In charge of hay and the sheds]
Aah, my face! Smelly!
It smells -.-;;
Thank you. Please enjoy
[In charge of cafe]
(Focus) (Focus)
We worked so much today
Mission, complete!
[Time to receive the paycheck!]
Thank you for your work today. This is the result
[Payment was given out based on the difficulty of the tasks]
(300,000 won!!)
One, two, three... (50,000 won;)
[Payment was given out based on the difficulty of the tasks]
150,000 won!
[Now the only thing left to do is flexing...]
[500,000 won is required in order to flex!!]
[There can only be one winning team for FLEX Tour!]
Everyone remembers, right?
(Nervous)
[There can only be one winning team for FLEX Tour!]
I'm going!
Leggo leggo!
His hand is shaking
[The outcome is...?]
[Bestowed by the goddess of fortune, the winner of 500,000 won is the cafe team!]
Kinjo Sukai!
[Sukai and Keigo are additionally selected!]
Keigo!
[The five winners of FLEX Tour]
[Brimming with youth and idyll]
[Popular place among Millenials and Gen Z, Hongdae]
[The winner team has arrived at Hongdae]
Hello~
We finally came to Hongdae!
I'm in Hongdae!!!
- Because we are the winning team
- Yes
We are carrying one camera per person
Do we need this many (cameras)? Is this necessary?
We do! We do!
How's Hongdae?
- I've come few times. About twice. Alone
- Oh, nice~
- What do you want to buy?
- What are we gonna buy?
Why don't we go to clothing stores?
(Good idea!)
It's my first time coming to Hongdae at night
I'm getting excited
- There is a lot of people
- There really are
Hello, we are JO1!
[LOL]
Hello~
- Even if you say that, I don't think people know us
- Hello we are Japanese artists, JO1. Notice us!
[Found a clothing store]
Cool!
Hello~
Awesome~ There are a lot of clothes
Everyone, please gather up here for a moment
We are finally here
Do you remember we have 500,000 won?
[During the bottle cap curling match earlier today]
- I'll do it!
- Leggo leggo!
[Mame's team won the winner-takes-all and obtained 500,000 won]
I have them right here
- Everyone will get the equal amount of 100,000 won
- Ah, I see
You can spend it on shopping for yourself
Or buying presents for the other members!
I'll hand out 100,000 won now
I understand!
[Yes! Got 100,000 won!]
Well then, get ready- start!
[On your mark. Get, set~~ Start shopping!]
Well, then. Get ready- Start!
[Meanwhile... The lodge team]
I'm hungry
Is there anything (to eat)?
[Glutton Syoya, heads straight to the fridge]
There's nothing;;
(SHOCK)
What about the other one?
(Empty-)
The yellow one!
There is really nothing
(Empty-)
Seriously, nothing?
[This is not happening]
- What do we do?
- That one too?
[The kitchen is bare]
I am, SO hungry!
[What are we going to do now...;;]
Do you have any food?
Choose anything you want from the menu!
(It's a gift)
Suddenly a menu appeared
[Appearance of a questionable menu]
(*T/N: 1. Rice cake, 2. Seaweed soup, 3. Grilled meat)
Looks delicious!
- But we have to pay money though
- Oh, really?
30... 30,000 won?
So expensive
[Too expensive;;]
That's expensive!
We don't have money
(We got one more)
(List of Chores)
Prepping dried anchovies
(*T/N: Removing the guts a/o heads)
[What is this]
- Prepping, what...?
- Anchovies, huh?
[What is this]
Prepping- It's written over here
[List of Chores]
1. Prepping dried anchovies - 5,000 won per one full ziplock pouch
5,000 won
Secondly-
[List of Chores]
2. Making beads bracelets - 10,000 won each
3. Folding paper cranes - 50,000 won per a full glass jar
(Awesome)
It doesn't matter how many paper cranes are in the jar (as long as it's full)?
That must be it
By the way, can anyone fold a crane?
- I'm very good at it, honestly
- We'll rely on you then
[Materials for the work]
Give them to us~
Thank you
Look at the anchovies
[A lot of work to do]
[List of Chores]
Why don't we divide the chores for now?
[Part-time factory is open]
Ah, I see! This way is better
(Folding paper cranes) - (Prepping dried anchovies) - (Making beads bracelets)
[I will satisfy my hunger by any means]
(Anchovies that will turn into money)
(Graceful posture)
This! This!
Isn't this too much work?
This, in South Korea...
Is this a trend (in Korea)?
In Korea, prepping anchovies is a common thing!
It's big!
Uwah! This is Little Shark
That's not a shark LOL
There are only big ones here
(Strategy: Do only the big ones)
Pick the big ones
Make the bag look fuller
How is this?
There is a lot
[Half air, half anchovies;;]
Taku-chan, we can totally finish this soon
(Are we good?)
You have to fill it up. It has to be full
"Ppang Ppang?"
[Example of "ppang ppang".jpg]
(Mewls) (Strict!)
I think we chose the wrong task
(Making beads bracelets)
(Becoming one with the beads)
(One by one) (Carefully)
I did as far as Junki, so...
[Tada~]
Sho, Ren, Ruki, Junki, Takumi.. Ah, wrong! Keigo, Takumi,
Syoya, Shosei, Sukai, Shion, Mame!
[His detailed work, stringing by members' colors]
I strung in that order
- Fold this triangular part once like this
- Here?
Leave a crease and unfold again
(His first time) (Folding crane professional)
[Folding paper crane tutoring session]
Open, and then?
(His first time) (Folding crane professional)
[Folding paper crane tutoring session]
Open, and like this, and then like this
(50,000 won, wait for me)
Shion, you know how to do this!
He knows how to fold
We are gonna be fast
- He is fast?
- Yup! He is. I haven't even taught him and he is folding them
(Pampering Shion~)
- He is fast?
- Yup! He is. I haven't even taught him and he is folding them
We got the hardest job!
Removing the guts?
It's not progressing at all
It's fun
[Meanwhile... Hongdae team is having fun shopping]
It's pretty
It's 10,000 won
What should I do?
Did you find something, Mame?
Not yet
For Shosei...
[They are choosing caps as gifts for the members]
- Isn't this color cute?
- It is
Should I buy?
Did you decide?
- There's Mame
- Wah, there's Mame!
There is Mame! Mame is here
[Found a Shiba dog that looks like Mame]
Well, it is me, but...
Should I gift this for Mame?
It's 20,000 won
Got it!
I've decided
I've decided on this, too
[They are done shopping one by one]
Then should we go pay...
Where is Sukai?
This is it
[I'm the hipster of the area]
Good!
- Should we line up (to pay)?
- We should
Thank you
Bags.. How do I say "bags"?
"Bongtu! Bongtu!"
- I need... "Bongtu"
- Please give us a bag
[They are paying in order]
Please give me a receipt
I'm in need... of a bag
I bought a gift for Ohira Shosei. It's a cap
[Satisfying shopping spree finished~]
Thank you~
[30 minutes into the domestic manual labor]
Are these edible?
(Nom nom, OK?)
Is it okay?
It's delicious
Really?
[It's my first time with Korean anchovies]
(Putting one in mouth)
(Curious)
(Chews) (Chews)
- Really?
- It's good
Really, really
Try it
- Are you sure?
- Yup!
- No, thanks
I'm fine
- I tell you, it's good
- I'm okay
All Koreans eat these
- Really?
- Yes
- Still. No, thanks
[LOL]
You are touching them this much, but don't have any interest?
(Almost done)
(Focused) (Focused)
(Drops;;)
(I'm going to cry ㅠㅠ)
Ruki!
Ruki...
This is not good
[Scattered beads]
[Scattered '10,000 won']
[Time is passing... At this rate I'm going to starve... ㅠ]
I did my best and was going to give this (to the members)
(It was in vain;;)
This won't do. It's going to take time
(Two cranes in 30 minutes;;)
How many paper cranes do you think we can make?
The origami papers are smaller than I thought;;
[We cannot starve like this!!!]
[Anchovies that carries the fate of the lodge team]
Maybe I gutted anchovies for living in my previous life
Well, possibly
How is this?
Oh... Oh~
(What's with the reaction?)
Please please please!
(Good enough?)
[Pass!]
Okay
[First successful income from the anchovy team]
Finally!
50,000 won
- Nice! x3. Work more!
- More more!
[You are trying to ride our coattail...]
- There are still lots in front of you, right?
- Oii!!
We are gonna stay up all night (if you don't work too)!
(It's so hard not to joke around LOL)
Seriously, this is difficult!
You can do it!
We are gonna see the sunrise
(Gained 5,000 won)
(Total: 5,000 won)
[Meanwhile... the beads bracelets team,
Overcame the failure and is on the brink of a completion...]
(Maximum concentration)
(Cut-)
Done!
[Completed a beads bracelet!]
Oh! Really?
(Gained 10,000 won)
(Total: 15,000 won)
(I'm proud of everyone~)
Wonderful!
Nice!
Can you do 25,000 won for half the bottle?
(It's supposed to be 50,000 won per full bottle)
(Desperate)
[Please say yes]
(If we can do well...) Then maybe we can even go for bulgogi
We'll accept beads rings too
[Because it's too slow we'll add this as well~]
Rings are okay, too
Whoa, really?
(Thank you~)
[Sorry, Lodge Team. Hongdae Team will have dinner first~]
(Clink)
Good job today
[Drink up]
Aigo~
- This is so delicious!
- This is no joke!
- This...
- It's really delicious!
[Shockingly delicious lemonade]
Is it that good?
[This is not a PR]
- Lemonade!
- Can I try a little bit?
Is it that good?
I've tried lemonades from various places, but-
This is it...! This is what I've been looking for
[Today's main menu - Margherita pizza]
[With various toppings]
[Baked it in a brick oven]
[Gorgeous pizza, complete!]
Crispy and crunch, huh?
[The main menu is here]
It's here!
- Awesome!
- It's big
[The visual is exploding~]
[Cut the burrata cheese in half-]
(Let's dig in~)
Whoa, the cheese...
(Chomp)
- Is it spicy?
- No~
Delicious!
(Cut then nom-)
This is too delicious!
Why... Why is it delicious?
Huh?
[Communication error]
[We baked it in a brick oven with the best ingredients]
[FLEX Team's happy dinner time~]
When the next pizza comes, let's ask them to take a picture of us doing that pose
The lemonade is delicious
[Sukai's unwavering love towards the lemonade]
(LOL)
[It was a satisfying dinner]
[1 hour and 30 minutes since the factory started~]
[Has the time stopped over here?]
I'm full with anchovies
Because you've been eating them
But that's good
(The bottle is filling up)
Could it be that there's a Korean way of folding these?
- Probably
- An easier way...
Do you think this size is okay?
[The bracelet team has changed their lane to rings]
We did it
Two rings are done
Amazing~
Now, I just need to tie up this one
Yaass!!!
[At the same time, finally they filled up a half of a bottle!]
(Amazing~)
25,000 won
(Rings are done too!)
Ring~
[Half-filled bottle of paper cranes and two beads rings are done!]
We did it! x3
Payment, please~
- Should we get paid now?
- Payment~ Payment~
(Total: 80,000 won)
[Earned 80,000 won for cooking ingredients]
(Proud)
Amazing!
[Earned 80,000 won for cooking ingredients]
We've earned 80,000 won
That's amazing
Look at this
It took more than an hour
(Proof of hard work)
That's crazy
While we're working this hard, what's Hongdae Team up to?
(You got a call)
[A call with Hongdae Team]
- It's connected
- Wait!
Now...
What are you guys doing now?
Pizza party~
Pizza?!
[Wow! Cool]
We are having a pizza party, yay~
(Bragging)
Big Tabasco~
(Cannot lose)
Here, you know...
Anchovy party~
Eh, what's that?
- Huh? Frogs?
- What is that?
Very very healthy!
[LOL]
[The lodge team is flexing health]
It's so very healthy~
"Healthy," he said
Wait, are you in a rural area? When we are-
[That peeves me!]
He's annoying!
- Bye bye~
- The connection is a bit bad
(I'm jealous~)
That looks fun
I want to eat pizza
[But we can't get weary just yet!]
Alright, shall we start cooking now?
[Ok~ Let's start cooking]
- Let's cook~!
- Let's start
[End of the hard work
Time to prepare dinner]
[80,000 won worth of ample ingredients
gained through shedding blood(?), sweet and tears]
So...
[Syoya / JO1's main chef]
There isn't seem to be recipes
[Just from the pictures... I guess we can do this]
- We can do it!
- We can!
[Just from the pictures... I guess we can do this]
(I'll put my trust in and follow you!)
Then I'll hold this for you
You are in charge of the cue card
[TODAY'S CHALLENGE MENU]
[Tteokbokki - Bulgogi]
[BUT, without recipes. There are only the pictures!]
[First, let's wash the hands]
That's for dishwashing
[Main Chef Syoya is assignining works]
It's... that, right?
[Main Chef Syoya is assigning works]
(Chop) (Chop)
[Members bustle at main chef Syoya's lead]
- About this?
- Something like that
[Members bustle at main chef Syoya's lead]
- Amazing! Shosei is good at that
- Nice, Shosei~
[Members bustle at main chef Syoya's lead]
(Thin) (Thin)
[Chopping as directed]
(Oh my eyes...)
[Main chef is happy at the sight of the bustling kitchen]
- Can you cheer for us?
- Alright!
(Baffling cheer...)
Go go go go go go!
Syoya!!
[Finally main chef Syoya makes an entrance]
[I'll show you the class of the main chef]
Do we have salt?
(Giving it a taste)
Yeah, it's salt
Please cook the bulgogi quickly~
[Beef bulgogi à la Syoya, START]
[STEP 1: Salt the water and boil it]
[STEP 2: Put glass noodles into the seasoned water]
(They are rinsed in cold water to keep them from sticking together)
[STEP 3: Put sesame oil in the pan and stir-fry marinated meat
(Stir) (Stir)
Whoa! Smells good
(We are hungry~)
The aroma of beef~
[Beef bulgogi à la Syoya, coming soon-!]
[Meanwhile, the tteokbokki team?]
[1. Put in the rice cakes even before the water starts to boil]
[2. Put in the fishcake for now too]
- Shion, is it okay to put everything in?
- Let's put them all
[3. Put in sausages as well as all other ingredients you can find]
It's all in
[4. Only a tinsy bit of pepper paste since it's spicy...]
Pepper paste!
- Shion! x3
- Yes! x3
Can you taste this for me?
[Already...?]
(Nothing has been done except putting in the ingredients)
- It looks good already
- Right? It looks like tteokbokki, right?
What else did you put in?
Just the pepper paste... for now
(Bland) (Bland)
[Tasting in just a minute after the stove was lit...]
(Dumbstruck main chef)
I think it's okay to put in more. The color is okay, but...
Isn't tteokbokki thicker?
- It's salty enough, but we need more sweetness
- Sugar?
- It's gotta be sugar, right?
- Yeah
It's not as spicy as I expected
(Sugar power) [Chaotic Tteokbokki Team]
- Is that sugar?
- Yup
(Sugar power) [Chaotic Tteokbokki Team]
[It won't have proper taste unless it's boiled longer...]
We put in quite a lot
I think we should add more
(I don't know anymore~ LOL)
(Mugen-sugar)
If you ask me what's lacking... The whole is lacking
- Then, let's put this in too
- Yeah
[Furious sesoning bombs]
[At this rate they'll put in all the seasonings in the kitchen]
- Well
- How will it turn out
[At this rate they'll put in all the seasonings in the kitchen]
[Finishing touch with honey]
How will it be?
That's right!
(Third time's charm)
- Is it good?
- Yup
(Takumi who happened to be passing)
It's done, then
(Strongly agree)
It tasted like tteokbokki
[The pepper paste was only auxiliary,
A miraculous birth of tteokbokki]
Well! That's how it's done
[The pepper paste was only auxiliary,
A miraculous birth of tteokbokki]
(Bulgogi is almost done too)
[Anticipated tastes of the two dishes!]
[Quite a spread(?)] [Dinner banquet]
(+ Ramen à la Shion)
1, 2!
Bon appetit!
- The original pictures-!
- Look at the pictures
- Don't they look just like the pictures?
- We did it!
Tteokbokki!
[Matching 1000%]
The quality is high. Wonderful~
The rice cake is important
[Beware of how good it is]
So delicious~!
(Proud) (Proud)
It's good!
- (How?) It's good~
- It's so good
- Shall we try the bulgogi too?
- Let's try it!
- The amount is quite-
- The visual is very bulgogi
[Succefully made bulgogi, just by looking at the picture]
It's really bulgogi!
I'm worried about the depth of the flavor
But the quality is amazing
(Nervous) (Nervous)
It was your first time cooking this...
[First swallow of the bulgogi!]
The meat, right? The "gogi" (meat)
(Mmmm~)
What is "gogi"?
(Curious)
Yummy~
Delicious!
This gives me a flash back to school meals
[Sweet taste of bulgogi that brings back the memory of school meals]
Tasty!
I keep going in
I'm glad
Everyone, how was today?
It was really tough
Physically tough work is not unusual (for idols)
But today was exceptional
From morning to night
We were able to experience things we won't normally get to do
(Right) (Right)
And we even cooked dinner together for the first time
(Yes) (Yes)
You can't buy something like this with money
The tour will continue tomorrow
Let's have fun tomorrow, too!
[Meanwhile... Hongdae Team after their dinner?]
I really enjoyed the meal
- I felt bad for the other team
- It was delicious
- But we got them presents
- That's true
- I hope that makes them feel better
- Yeah
- I'm worried about tomorrow
- If we are not careful, it'll be the opposite for us tomorrow
[LOL]
Since we have to work tomorrow, too
Let's go back, take a good rest
- And look forward to tomorrow's tour
- Okay!
[A fun day filled with unusual experiences]
[What kind of day will be waiting for JO1 tomorrow?]
[Second day]
([WEB Message] Hello Tour Paradise bus + your guide have arrived at your accomodation. Please gather in front of the lodge~)
Everyone! Looks like Hello Paradise's bus has arrived
- Let's clean up!
- Okay~
[What kind of self-sufficient tour will unfold today?]
[A mysterious guide holding the tour company's flag]
[Who is the new guide for the second-day Hello Tour?]
- Waah, hello~
- Hello~
Hello!
[Ciipher's lead rapper & lead dancer]
[Name: Keita
Special feature: 4th year in Korea
Hobby: Expert on K-restaurants and trends]
I'm Keita, your new guide who'll be travelling with you today. Nice to meet you~
Nice to meet you
If you work hard during the day, you'll be able to flex at night
Shall we say fighting together?
One, two, three, fighting-!
[Self-sufficient trip, fighting!]
Well then, please get on the bus
Please take good care of me
[Here is to new self-sufficient experience~]
- I'm from Japan~
- I'm from Japan, too~
[Bus is running straight along the road]
[To the second destination, GO!]
So, we have departed
Does anyone know where we'll be going today?
I don't know!
We don't know!
Today, we'll be going to a seafood market and a shrimp fishery
[A traditional seafood market located in Sorae Port]
[Plenty of fresh seafood]
[Lively place that's always busy with crowds]
[And the other place is?]
[A shrimp fishery located in Daebu Island]
[Greetings from the energetic shrimps]
Waah, sounds really good
(Expectation up)
I like shrimps
And at the restaurant...
[Things you can do at a traditional fish market?]
《The Seafood Market Team's To Do》
✅ Cleaning the restaurant and preparing side dishes
(Pricks up ears)
And then, at the market...
《The Seafood Market Team's To Do》
✅ Cleaning the restaurant and preparing side dishes
✅ Helping the stalls in the market
《The Shrimp Fishery Team's To Do》
✅ Feeding the shrimps
✅ Catching and packaging the shrimps
At the shrimp fishery, you'll be feeding and catching the shrimps
You'll also be packing those shrimps
(Full of anticipation)
- Cool! Yeay!
- I see
That sounds good
《Job Status》
[Restaurant: 3 people] - [Market: 4 people] - [Shrimp Fishery: 4 people]
We'll divide you into teams now
We'll start with the shrimp fishery
This will be the most popular. It's impossible
[Volunteers, put up hands please]
1, 2!
(Shots up hand)
[Total: 7 people]
Then why don't we decide by charm appeal?
(Charm appeal??)
[Stage is open for the bewitching charmers]
This it too tough
[Syoya volunteers first]
Which way should I be looking? This way?
This way, please
It may not be funny but I'll give it a shot
I! Love shrimp!
(Parrot)
Love shrimp
SO much!
I wanna go!!!
(Parrot 22)
Wanna go
(No matter what) Wanna go!!!
(Uhm...)
[Keita's verdict is...?]
Well, this is...
I could tell how much you'd like to go
I tried hard with my insufficient Korean
I could see the desire from your eyes
That was good
I'll hold my decision until after the last person
Who's next?
Which people wanted to go again?
It's suddenly hot in here
[It's hard to step up the charm appeal]
(Peeks)
Any volunteers?
[It's hard to step up the charm appeal]
Shosei...
(Hesitates...)
Shosei will do it!
Shosei keeps hitting his thigh
Hold on! This is too difficult
New rule. Let's do acrostic poem with SHRIMP!
[Forget the charm appeal, make a two-line poem with "SHRIMP"]
If you pull this off, you might score high points
(This won't be easy)
A poem with SHRIMP. This is difficult
Shrimp?
(Junki's hand is UP!)
(Surprised;;)
- I got it!
- You are loud!
Ebi's energy is biribiri biribiri*
(*T/N: Ebi = shrimp, biribiri: electric)
I'm cold for real
Impossible
Electric!
[That was an unusual poem]
[I want to go to the shrimp fishery]
[Junki's acrostic poem that left strong aftertaste]
(I'm still safe...)
By the way, what kind of electric was that?
(I should not hesitate..;;)
Ebi's! Energy is! Electric!
(Younger bro, help me out)
(Help me TT)
Electric!
(Energy received)
[Shrimp]
Shrimp!
(LOL)
- He earned the point
- Mame, yours is the best
(Our youngest is the best!)
Sorry, I cannot help to stay still
Issei passed!
[Mame got accepted into the shrimp fishery]
(Wait for me, shrimps!)
No doubt
Friend! Friend!
Shrimp friend!
- Shrimp friend...
- I'll think about that
[The result of the audition is?]
[Eager Syoya] - [Electric Junki] - [Shrimp Mame] - [CF Shosei]
[Shrimp Fishery Team]
《Final Team Selection》
[Shrimp Fishery] - [Restaurant] - [Market Stalls]
[Namdong District, Incheon]
[First destination - A wide traditional seafood market next to sea]
[Seafood Market Team arrived]
(Smile)
Please line up this way~
We have arrived
We arrived at the market!
Now, we will head to the store you'll be working at
[A place where you can taste fresh seafood all seasons]
[The favored seafood market located in Sorae Port, Incheon]
Shall we go in?
[To the lively market- GO]
A marketplace, huh?
Right, this is Korean marketplace
- Wah, awesome!
- Hello
[Crispy yellow roasted mackerel]
Hello~
[Various market snacks that hold your feet]
- Whoa, mandu!
- There's mandu, too~
[Various market snacks that hold your feet]
That looks delicious
I don't understand, I don't understand
- Awesome
- I don't get it
(Mmm nice~)
There are a lot of things
- We are JO1. JO1!
- Huh?
[He never forgets to introduce them! LOL]
We'll be going this way~
[Filmed in accordance with the guidelines of health authorities]
If you head this way there's another alley here
Hello~
[Spread of fresh seafood in front of the eyes!]
They are interesting, right?
- Hello~
- Sashimi!
Hello~
[They arrived to their first workplace!]
- Nice to meet you
(Dropped them off succesfully! V]
It's my first time seeing this kind of Horsea (Pokemon)
This is the first place you will be working at
[Plenty of seafood such as abalones, sea squirts, and more]
[Even fresh life fishes!]
['DH' Sashimi Center]
Ruki-kun and Sukai-kun, this is where you'll be working
- Good luck~!
- Please take a good care of us
[Ruki & Sukai assigned to the 1st workplace]
Let's go! Let's move along!
- See you~
- Leave it to us
Let's do this!
[Entering a new workplace with support from other members!]
[Hipsters of this area]
Hello~
Let's walk this way
- Good day, ma'am
- Hello
[Arriving at the 2nd workplace!]
- Good day, ma'am
- Hello
Let's see, who were the remaining store group?
Sho and Takumi!
[2nd workplace for Sho & Takumi]
These two will help you out today
Hello~
Pleased to work with you
Hurry up inside~
Come in and start working right away!
(LOL)
Yes! We are in your care
(Scurries)
Way to go!
Inside here?
Good luck guys~!
Good luck!
(Sho, Takumi, do your best!)
- Your name is?
- I'm Sho
[Introduction is the first step of business]
- Your name is?
- I'm Sho
- I'm Takumi
- Sho, Takumi. Okay~
[Introduction is the first step of business]
- I'm Takumi
- Sho, Takumi. Okay~
[Sho and Takumi's workplace of the day]
First, let's get you changed into work clothes!
[Great deal of freshly-caught seafood]
[The alley is always jam-packed with people]
['JM' Seafood Shop]
I think they are singers from Japan~
[Handsome youths at the center of the attention]
We are not (singers)!
- You are not?
- He says they aren't, he speaks Korean
(Joking) (Joking)
[JO1, the popular stars of the fish market]
I gotta look them up later
[Questions from all sides pouring in]
- Name (of the group)?
- Name? JO1!
[Questions from all sides pouring in]
- Name (of the group)?
- Name? JO1!
- JO1?
- Yes!
(Nice to meet you~)
You can speak Korean? You are not Korean?
(Curious 222)
[Who gave birth to those attractive boys~?]
[Confused by the overflowing attention]
Alright, let’s go!
[Meanwhile, how are Ruki and Sukai doing at the first workplace?]
[Cleaning the water tank to prepare the shop’s opening]
We'll start~ Wait, is this fish? What's this?
What is this...?
- Sea squirt!
- Sea squirt
This is hard
[Cleaning the sea squirt tank, start!]
[First, move the sea squirts aside]
Sea squirt~
(Squirts water-)
[The owner's tips on how to move sea squirts]
Squish them like this so they get harder
(Amazed) (Amazed)
It got stiffer
I got it!
[Moving the sea quirts according to the owner's tip!]
- Sea squirt are super tasty
- They are
- They’re in season right now!
- In season?
- Now?
- It's the best season
Right now? I see~
[Meanwhile Ruki has completed moving a basketful of sea squirts]
Welcome to the store~
[Practicing promotion of the store as they go]
The sea squirts are really delicious~
It’s really delicious! Uhm-- In my opinion...
"In my opinion", he said
[After finishing moving the sea squirts]
[Pour water over so they don’t get stressed]
[Swiftly cleaning the aquarium]
[Rubbing every nook and cranny!]
[Remove the remaining dirt in the water]
- You are done there
- Really? Okay
[The shop is ready to open!]
[At the same time, the remaining 3 are heading to the last workplace]
So hot~
It's hot today
This might be the hottest it’s ever been since we arrived in Korea
Oh, really?
Do you have any Korean dishes you recommend?
Korean dishes to recommend?
Have you ever tasted grilled pork belly?
[4th year in Korea]
Yes! That’s super tasty
Tasty, right~
- Korean stews are also good
- Ah, yes
- I really like beef ribs stew, too
- That one is nice as well~
This is where you'll be working
[Arrived at the restaurant team’s workplace, a little bit separated from the market team’s]
['BRD' Restaurant]
[Restaurant team's tasks:
Cleaning up & preparing ingredients
and more (a lot to do)]
They have fishes here, too!
[The restaurant's water tank caught their attention!]
(Hello~)
- They even have shrimps, too!
- There are shrimps, too!
So big!
There are crabs!
How do you say crab (in Korean)?
- "Kkokke!"
(Korean +1)  (Korean +2)
- Let’s head inside, shall we?
- Yes!
Hello~
Welcome to the store~
[Shop manager welcomes the members]
It's hot today, isn't it?
- So nice to meet you
- Hello~
These three will help you out in the restaurant
I appreciate your help, please do your best~
What's your name?
My name is Ren
- Reng?
- Ren!
- Rem!
I'm Keigo
- Kkeigo?
- Keigo
Kkeigo!
- I'm Shion
- Shion~
- I’m auntie! Please just call me auntie
- Auntie~!
The jobs here are tough, would you be able to handle it?
Yes, we can! Leave it to us!
- Please clean the place~
- Clean the place
- And wipe the tables too~
- Wipe the tables
Please give it your all!
Alright! We’ll do our best!
[Keigo: in charge of cleaning] - [Shion: moves the chairs] - [Ren: in charge of cleaning]
[Thorough cleaning START!]
[Shion pulls the chairs away]
[Then Keigo & Ren sweep the space]
[Perfect team play]
It doesn't look too dirty to me
[Done with the cleaning at Spead of Light!]
[Promptly continues to wipe the tables!]
Have you cleaned like this at your old part-times?
I did tons of it
I worked part time at a ramen restaurant before
- Ramen?
- I see I see!
I did things like wiping tables and utensils
Really?
How about Keigo-kun?
I've worked at an izakaya bar before
(Surprised)
- Izakaya?!
- Yeah!
I cooked there
Which dish were you good at?
Do you know omusoba*?
(*T/N: Stir fried noodles wrapped in omelet)
I used to make that
(Making sure no speck of dust left) (Real clean)
[Inspection complete]
OK!
Auntie~ We’re done here~!
Auntie, we're done
[Finally cleaning is done!]
Good job!
[Shop manager is impressed with their cleaning]
[Surprise gift prepared by the kitchen chief]
[What could the surprise be?]
Guess what this is~
[Today’s lunch ingredient: Whelk]
(50 servings)
[So the cleaning...]
[Was not...]
[The end...?]
[They can only laugh looking at the amount of whelks]
- Take a guess
- What is this?
- Whelks~
- Whelks!
[Quite a lot of whelks]
Looks delicious, no?
Using this scalpel
- Twist them out like this
- Like this
(Wiggle) (Wiggle)
Take it out like this. Watch me!
Look how I do it
(Slides~!)
Done!
[Perfection]
(Wide eyes)
- Jealous (of your skill)!
- Impressive. You are a pro...!
You pierce right here, grab this part, and pull. Try it!
Like this, like this~
(Slides!)
(Instructor)
- Is this alright?
- No. No
(Instructor)
Here
(Turn and turn~)
(Slides!)
(Meanwhile Shion...)
- Do I pierce out like this?
- Not like that
[PER-FECT!]
With this hand-
- Like this?
- Yes, that’s right!
- I like the big ones
- Do it gently!
- Gently~
- Roger that!
- Gently!
- Gently, yes
[Okay.. Gently]
[Work progress: 2%]
- Isn’t it tricky to poke like this?
- Yeah
It might be easier to just pull them by hand
See?
- Did you find a trick?
- Yup
This part
It’s a lot faster if you press the other side
Really
It really is a lot faster
Like this
[Remove x1]
[Remove x2]
[Remove x3]
[Remove x4]
[No matter how many they remove]
[The amount of whelks does not seem to go down]
[Will this ever end?]
(No thoughts, head empty)
[Danwon District, Ansan City]
[Shrimp Fishery Team arrived~]
[The fine weather puts them in great spirit]
We've arrived
The weather is nice
We arrived at our destination~
- Hello~
- Is this the place?
We can harvest shrimps here?
- Looks like we are inside of mountains
- I can see mountains
(Looking around)
[Where exactly are the shrimps…?]
We’re arrived at a place rich in nature
I can’t wait to see what lies ahead
Hello~ Nice to meet you~
[The CEO of the fishery welcomes the members]
Welcome to the shrimp fishery! The fishery is located over here
(Where?)
[Finally the revelation of the shrimp fishery]
[Incredibly vast shrimp fishery]
[In over 100 water tanks]
[Shrimps are farmed using environmentally friendly technology]
[In other words, there are enormous workloads~]
- Let’s do our utmost best!
- We’ll do our best!
[Determined to work hard]
- Let’s do our utmost best!
- We’ll do our best!
Let's change clothes and start right away
- This way please
- Oh, we'll change
[Change into work clothes]
- Please take good care of us
- Alright
[Arrived to work in one of the many water tanks]
- There are a lot of work to do around here~
- I see
[Filmed safely in compliance with guidelines of the health authorities]
This is the tank where the shrimps are cultivated
(+ Full of microorganisms)
We’ll start here today
First, let’s get into the water and examine the shrimps
[Entering the first water tank]
- Wow, really?
- There are a lot of shrimps
- Impressive, so deep!
- Look!
There are a lot!
- Looks dangerous
- I'll be going in
(Isn't it deep?)
Is the water warm? Or cold?
It’s cold
- Then it'll feel nice
- Good
[They relaxed and follows Shosei's step]
I can feel them squirming
They suddenly swarm around you
Oh! The shrimp, the shrimp!
The shrimp flew!
- The water pressure is crazy
- Shrimp attack!
Amazing!
So cute!
They’re bumping into me a lot
[With Junki in, finally all of them are inside!]
It’s kinda slippery
Two of you will catch the shrimps on the floor
And then check their intestine color through the back
Shrimps that are eating well will have dark brown intestine
[Let’s go check the shrimps!]
- Here I go!
- Let's go!
[Junki and Mame start!]
The shrimps...
There are lots of shrimps
[Moving carefully~]
I got them
Wonderful!
(Hello shrimps?)
- Press down to the bottom
- Understood
[Herding jumpy skippy shrimps]
- They are jumping!
- Sweep and lift it up!
[Full of shrimps]
Amazing!
[The shrimps are very energetic]
[LOL]
(Mame, are you okay?)
(Struggling with the shrimps)
- Isn't this too many?
- Too many? That's too many?
[A must-do before the shrimps escape!]
- Amazing! There are so many
- Oh, they're jumping!
- Here... After you lift, you need to check their color
- Yes!
Whether it's brown?
[Scoop them out and check]
- Is that brown?
- Looks like it
(Concentrating)
Ah, here, here!
Oh! There's a line
(If it’s brown, it's healthy!)
- You can see it's brown, right?
- Yes, yes
Are these ones healthy?
Yes, you can tell it's been eating well
So cute~
If there’s no dead shrimp, it means the water tank is working well
- We’re done checking this one so let’s move on to the next one. Let's get out~
- Okay!
[It’s time to show what we've learned!!!]
[Starts checking the second water tank!]
(All set to start)
I’m ready!
1, 2...
- Come slowly
- Slowly!
- Got it!
- Let's go~
[Shrimp hunt starts!]
At 45 degrees angle
Press down to the floor and move forward slowly
I think there are a lot around me
- Around me, too
- You can feel the vibration from them
So cute. There’s a baby shrimp! There's a baby
Loads of them got caught in my net! For real
No joke
This is getting heavy-
(Working hard)
Or is it just my feeling?
Lift them up!
[The shrimps jump around when the net is lifted]
[Full of fresh and energetic shrimps]
[Flinching because of shrimp attacks]
[The shrimps jumping around above the water]
You need to check them
[Inspects closely]
Check, check!
- Open the net slowly
- Oh, this one!
- OK!
- You need to check whether it's dead or alive
[Checking the color of shrimp’s intestine]
Please check~
Wah! This one looks good!
[Brown = Healthy shrimps]
- But it's legs...
- What color are they?
[Brown = Healthy shrimps]
- It looks okay
- They are fine~
[Brown = Healthy shrimps]
Release them after you confirmed their health
Bye bye~
They’re super healthy!
- Now that we checked, let’s feed them. Then we are done with this tank
- Okay!
- They are eating!
- Eat a lot~
[The fishery team distributes the food evenly all over]
[Back to Sorae Port]
Hi~
[Enjoying his free time after guiding everyone to their workplace]
[Going to observe the members after his short break!]
[Are they doing their job properly...?]
(Devoted to the assigned task)
(Satisfied)
[Moving to observe the restaurant team]
I wonder if they’re doing their job well
(Cautious) (Cautious)
[Let’s check them out]
[The peaceful-looking restaurant team]
No, it's okay
This-
[Quietly sliping in unbeknownst to the members]
(Focused) (Focused)
It’s amazing how focused they are
I see you guys are very concentrated on your job!
[Finally noticed!]
I didn’t notice at all
We had no idea
Your concentration is praise-worthy
I wish you had seen us working on the previous chore (whelks)
Did anything important happen?
Ah, the whelks?
[30 mins earlier: war against the whelks]
It's harder when sitting down
My lowerback is sore
- I can finally see the bottom
- Finally
I just know that I’m at my best right now
Auntie, we are done~!
[Describing his tale of bravery with the entire body LOL]
- It was this many
- Really?
[Keita (21) / Has a soft heart]
They’ve been working really hard...
Do you guys perhaps want any drink?
A peach drink, please!
- A lemonade for me
- Lemonade~
- Make it two lemonades
- Two lemonades
I’ll go buy them for you
[Copy that!]
(Awesome~)
- Really?
- Thank you~
[For the clients who has been working hard~]
- Please, wait. I'll be back soon
- I can work even harder
[Guide Keita on his way!]
- Have a safe trip!
- We'll be waiting!
- Is he really buying them for us?
- He's nice
Should I go with him?
- No!
- Let's work on our job LOL
[Concentrating back to work~]
[How’s the 'JM' market team doing?]
[Finished preparing to open and now waiting for the first customer]
- Basket~
- Basket!
[Practicing taking orders before customers come]
- 3 fish!
- 3 fish...
[Practicing taking orders before customers come]
Measure 300 grams
[Lesson 1: Learning how to measure the weight]
- Try putting in 1 kg of fish
- 3 fish for 1 kg
(Trying it out)
OK
(Getting impressed while observing LOL)
Oh~~
(Working hard)
- Put over here
- Okay
[Lesson 2: Remembering the seafood's names]
- He's very professional
- You need to add more
(I gotta do something too...)
- Okay?
- Okay okay
[Octopus came into his line of sight]
Octopus?
- It's "moon-eo" (in Korean)!
- Eh?
- "Moon-eo!"
- "Eung-eo!"
[Trying to remember the names of the fishes]
- "Moon-eo!"
- Correct
[Trying to remember the names of the fishes]
"Moon-eo"
(What about this?)
- That’s "se-woo" (in Korean)*
- "Se-woon"
Ah! "Se-woo!"
"Moon-eo", "se-woo"
[The long-awaited arrival of the first customer]
Welcome~
[Time to show what I’m capable of]
Octopus! Shrimp! (We have them...)
We really got many of them...
[Deserted]
You have to tie it tight
[Takumi is focused on wrapping an order]
- Like this
- Oh! Okay okay
- (I got it) easy~
- Right
[Having fun together]
[Another customer]
- Get a king crab~
- How much are they?
They’re really, really delicious~!
- They are delicious?
- Yes~
- 10 of them?
- 10 of them!
- 10,000 won!
How about this one?
- Can you pick it up?
- Yes
- 1 kg is-
- Buy a king crab~
(Holding it up so the customers can see it clearly)
1 kg is 60,000 won
- 1 kg for 60,000 won!
- 60,000 won!
- You can measure it and I'll give you a discount
Measure(?) king crab
I'll think about it
This handsome young man will pack it to you
[I am the handsome man]
This handsome man will
(Hesitant) (Hesitant)
How much is this?
30,000 won!
(We have shrimps too)
30,000 won
King crab-
(Lonely exit)
- It's very delicious
- King crab-
[Good salesman does not give in]
- We have lots of them~
- He says he'll give you a lot
(We’ll be back)
[Are you leaving already…?]
Don't go~!
[Please come back]
Thank you
[Not long after, an extraordinary customer pays a visit]
- Put it here
- Yes~
[Not long after, an extraordinary customer pays a visit]
[A big customer has appeared]
- One, two?
- This, this, and this... and shrimp
- Takumi~
- Yes! Takumi is here
An order of 30 abalones for 30,000 won! 30 abalones~
30 abalones!
- 30 abalones
- Got it!
[Me, Takumi, has been waiting for this very moment...]
- You need to measure
- Okay
[Me, Takumi, has been waiting for this very moment...]
Five!
[Takumi carefully counts the abalones]
Six! Seven!
(Sho is bagging scallops)
One, two-
- You can stop
- Please give me one more
One more!
(Do you want a bonus?)
[A sudden request for a bonus from the customer]
(What should I do?)
You can give him one more LOL
A bonus, okay!
[Takumi also gets to give a bonus]
- Please give him 3 more
- 3 more?
Ah! 3 more
- 3 more abalones!
- Alright!
[Sales success: Hearty bonus~]
One-
- Two
- Ooh, two!
(It's on me)
Three! The bonus!
(Generous bonus)
There is a lot!
- Please give him a word of appreciation
- Bonus, bonus!
- Thank you!
- Ah, thank you!
A lot, a lot~
(These young boys are doing a good job~)
[The customer is buying shrimps as well]
- Please add more
- OK. More, more, more
(Slow) (Slow)
More, more, more
More~
[Takumi who was watching Sho]
Oops, sorry~ More and more
It's very fresh
- (Older bro), hurry up!
- I'm hurrying
[Moving faster after urged by Takumi]
- Faster, faster!
- Okay
It’s okay, do it slowly~ but many ^^
(LOL)
Slowly, slowly
[Packing up slowly many(?) shrimps]
Don't forget the ice!
(It's my turn!)
Ice?
Ice, please!
[Takumi helps with Sho's wrapping by putting ice in it]
Here
(Thanks, brother)
- Is this much okay?
- It’s good
Sho, put in the fishes
(Takumi is in charge of packing)
Takumi, wrap it up please
Ice, ice
A lot of ice
[Speed and precision]
Many many ice, okay!
[Like a professional!]
[Time to show the result of the lesson!]
(He’s pretty good at it)
Auntie! Auntie! Am I doing it right?
Cut it, cut it!
[Cut the rope and packing is done!]
Everything good? Thank you for your purchase~
[Finished packing abalones, conches, octopuses, and shrimps]
- Thank you so much~
- I hope you sell a lot~
[Finished packing abalones, conches, octopuses, and shrimps]
Enjoy them~
Thank you!
Enjoy your food~
[First sale was a great success!]
Now, one of you has to go quickly!
One of you needs to go and replenish the shrimps!
[Shrimps are sold out thanks to the customer]
[Bring 5 kg of life shrimps]
- Go outside! Outside
- Go out? Okay
[Explaining the direction]
- Go straight upward!
- Upward!
And you'll find the general fish market!
(Fish market?)
Fish market!
[The words are too difficult to Takumi;;;]
General-
There's a building
[This is difficult]
Haha, yes
There's Haesoo Sauna building next to it. Go to the fishery on the 1st floor
(O: Destination) (B: Current location)
There's Haesoo Sauna building next to it. Below that, go to the fishery on the 1st floor
First floor!
- Could you tell me one more time?
- One more time
[The owner is explaining step by step one more time]
Go straight to the outside
- Go outside
- Go outside~
[I brought my older bro~]
- And then go straight upward
- Upward!
[I brought my older bro~]
Yes. If you go straight upward...
- There's Haesoo Sauna
- Haesoo Sauna...
(Do you understand?)
(Nod) (Nod)
- Below that on the first floor, there's Yoo-il Fishery
- Yes
When you are there, the shrimps-
- Shrimps!
- The alive ones-
- Bring back 5 kg of shrimps in the bucket!
- 5 kg!
[To keep the shrimps fresh, speed is crucial!]
You need to hurry back!
[Takumi who is scared to go alone decided to take Sho together!]
- I'm scared to go alone~ Can I (go together?)
- Yes, you can go together
(Trust me, Takumi)
- Ah, thank you!
- Go outside, and to the left
[I’m JO1’s leader!]
- To the left! Left
- Left-
- Wish us luck!
- Good luck!
- Please succeed!
- We will!
[We're going for an errand!]
(Destination)
[Mission to fetch fresh shrimps START!]
There's a shop
- Then there's a sauna, and it's on the first floor of-
- First floor of that building. This place
- Looks tasty~ Right?
- Looks delicious
[Very visually appetizing]
[Both are tempted by the market street food]
- Yum yum yum
- It does look good
- We'll come back
- We are coming back for food?
(Remembering shop manager’s request to come back fast)
(Current location)
[Reluctantly moves on to look for the sauna]
- Sauna?
- Let’s look for the sauna
There should be a sauna around here
There's no sauna
[Where is the sauna~]
This is something you won’t be able to experience in Japan
That’s true
And it’s very hot
Sauna?!
Is this...?
[Is this the sauna?]
First floor...
It's different!
I don’t know anymore
[How are they supposed to find the sauna in a place this big...]
I can't find it... Isn't it over there?
- Is it that one?
- Nope, that's not it
- This one definitely is not
- Definitely not
- Hello~
- Since it's a sauna
[Will they be able to successfully complete their errand?]
I'd really like to find it
[Next week]
[(Difficulty level: ☆☆☆) Bring 5 kg of fresh shrimp]
Go outside! Haesoo Sauna, Yoo-il Fishery on the 1st floor. Okay?
- Yoo-il!
- Yoo-eul Pishery
- Could that be it?
- That?
[They hurry their feet]
- We gotta hurry
- Let's hurry up
(Anxious) (Uncertain)
Is it this one? No?
(Sho follows)
[Will they get there within today…?]
Hurry hurry!
(Tutor)
[The work in fishing village continues]
Hurry hurry
(Student 1)
[The work in fishing village continues]
Welcome~
(Student 2)
[The work in fishing village continues]
(Student 3)
30,000 won!
[The members are adapting quickly]
- Did I do okay?
- You did very well
[The members are adapting quickly]
So fast!
You are a pro!
- Good job
- Yeah!!
[We’ll get lots of money today +_+!]
Thanks for working hard
Finished!
[We’ll get lots of money today +_+!]
- One, two!
- Okay!
[We’ll get lots of money today +_+!]
[Next up]
You who worked hard
Now soar away!
[The members have been working hard for 2 days...]
[Enjoy your time...]
FLEX as hard as you work~~~
We’re at a pool~!
[This is WAVE PARK]
Aah! Crazy! x3
[It's more fun to play with hard-earned money]
[Free time they haven't had a chance to enjoy due to busy schedules]
[Being together makes JO1's trip even more special]
[See you in the 3rd episode~]