- This kind is unexpectedly yummy
[Previously: The members addicted to the sweet strawberries
& forgetting about the strawberry picking showdown]
Mm!
[Chomp chomp]
I'm full!
My stomach is full
Is there a heart-shaped strawberry? Shall we search for it?
It'd definitely be cute!
Do you want it?
[Open wide]
[Here we have someone addicted to it too]
Yum!
Junki, are you working hard?
Yes!
You're not eating your fill and relaxing, right?
[Shifty eyes]
Yes!
Eat it
He'll eat it
[Person who said he was full earlier]
[Chew chew]
Yummy!
Juicy juicy!
Let's eat ice cream~
You can eat ice cream down here
(Really?)
You can eat ice cream
Really?
Really
- Please show it to me
- Okay
- The ice cream is over here!
[Why is Ruki going the opposite direction...?]
[In the end, eating ice cream with Shion]
Ice cream- WHOA!
We'll like to try Hokkaido Vanilla
Yummy!
[Strawberry picking showdown]
[Within the time period, teams split up to choose:
1) The sweetest strawberry
2) The largest strawberry]
[Sugar level of sweet strawberry + weight of large strawberry
The team with the highest score wins!]
I'll aim for these sweet ones
How should I know the sweetness?
These look sweet. I'll get these
This and...
This, are definitely sweet
I'll hide them here
I shall now devote myself to eating
I'm off~
- Keigo are you searching?
- I am, I am
Really?
- I did a spy thing
- What is it?
I bit off the tip of a big one from the rival team
The one I found
Really??
Ruki-kun's
- You did it
- I did it
With that, strawberry picking has ended!
[Good work everyone]
It was fun!
[Stomach full]
It was yummy!
- My stomach is full
- Happiness
Everyone, have you picked something you're confident in?
Yes
Probably
Of coursey~
There are many I want to show
By the way, for us we have one or a few each...
Don't you guys have too many!?
[Truly all members (except Sukai) have a small amount]
[Lots]
From here we can make our choice
Right, from here on
For us, we carefully selected while eating
Once you eat it you can't send it out anymore
We can choose from this stock
[Chomp]
You're gonna eat it?!
Don't eat it!
That's probably the sweetest
Maybe this was the sweet one
- That could be really sweet
- How is it?
It's really sweet~
- So it's sweet
- That's no good
That's no good
Let's choose the sweet and large one
1 per team?
That's right
- This is huge
[Each team goes through careful selection!]
- Look at this
This pretty one
It's pretty but...
This one looks like it's both large and sweet
[The strawberries Ruki is holding...]
[From Ep.14]
[Keigo's doing...!]
[Still not noticing]
[Everyone focuses on Takumi's strawberries]
No doubt it's Takumi's ones
And this looks really sweet
This is the Otani Shohei (baseballer) of the strawberry world
For real
This is the home base
[Takumi's strawberry - Home base]
[Do they look alike?]
- Let's compare them
[Careful selection from the strawberries each person picked]
- This is so pretty
Ok
How is it?
Isn't mine red?
How many did you pick!
Isn't it this one? It's glossy
- This is the one
[glossy]
Let's go with this one
- This is the sweet one
[Thanks to careful selection while picking the strawberries, Shosei's team decides immediately]
- And this is the big one
Shall we go?
- Which one is heavier?
[On the other hand, Takumi's team is still carefully choosing]
Probably this one
No, I don't know
- The heavy one is this
- The large one is that
What about the sweetness?
I'll put out a sweet one
- That's definitely sweet [Shion's secret weapon - glossy strawberry takes the stage!]
This part is definitely sweet
Shall we go with this?
[Which will win?]
[Glossiness that doesn't lose to Sukai's strawberry]
[All members gather after selecting]
Rukkun, was yours bitten by someone?
Hm?
[Reporting directly to Ruki who still hasn't noticed]
Is this ok?
Which?
Here, look at it
[A world of only the two of them]
- Wait a moment
- Mm
[He got me]
Hehe
(snicker)
Ruki what happened?
I put aside a large one for selection
Keigo told me to look carefully
And when I took a look, it got bitten
[Bitten by Keigo]
That's his strategy
Look at his face
(Accomplice)
It's crazy
Have you decided?
Yes we have
Then, shall we start with the sweet one?
[First, measurement of the sweet strawberry]
Yes!
Put aside the large one for now
Please put out one sweet strawberry
Yes
Then, I'm going
Have a safe trip
Let's go!
Go~
Oh? Isn't it large?
We're battling with the size
No, the sweetness, not the size
[Shion's strawberry vs Sukai's strawberry]
Please squeeze the sweet-looking part (serious)
[Putting in the strawberry juice]
[Measure button ON]
[Nervous]
[The result is?]
Eh?
Oh!
[Takumi's team - Sugar level 11.2]
[Average sweetness 10~11 *Rough indication]
We don't know yet
How will this fare?
Shion that's amazing!
Continuing on, it's our team's one
Show us how good you are!
Please!
[Nervous]
Squeeze it properly
Ready, start!
A crazy high number will come out
Eh?
Here it is!
A crazy high number will come out
Eh?
Here it is!
What is it?
Sugar level...!
(Please)
13.7
[Sugar level 11.2 (Takumi team) < 13.7 (Shosei team)]
That is strong
[Shosei's team - Sugar level 13.7]
So the sweetest strawberry is ours, and it's Shosei's team's victory!
Well well well
I can't believe we lost...!
But it means they didn't get to eat the sweet one
So they didn't feel the happiness
We just ate it and didn't get to send it out
We shouldn't do that
It's a game to send it out
We experienced happiness
For the first round, we won the sweetest strawberry
Is that ok?
That's amazing
Nice
- Which are you going with?
[Next, large strawberry showdown]
- Either the home base or
Otani Shohei of the strawberry world
[2 aces among the bunch]
We'll go with Otani Shohei of the strawberry world!
[I've decided on you!]
Let's go!
This is sweet!
It's not about the sweetness, it's the size
Exactly
Weigh the home base later too
[Curious about the home base too]
Right, let's weigh this later
We'll send ours out too
Go! From the soccer world
Go!
Yonashiro Sho from the soccer world! (?)
Yonashiro Sho!
[They are satisfied with it...? Yonashiro Sho from the soccer world strawberry]
It's gonna be a good match
[Otani Shohei vs Yonashiro Sho of the strawberry world]
Then let's start by weighing ours
Okay
[All members focus]
Yonashiro Sho
Did you do something to the box...?
Tsk! I got found out
[What is the meaning of this reaction?]
Ours is 57 grams
57kg??
[Doing well!]
Strawberry fairy team
Yes
Please
Let's go!
- We can definitely win
[Can Takumi's team make a comeback!?]
I'll start!
Surpass the limit!
The weight is...!
57 gram!
[The same weight!]
Go! Go home base!
[Really?]
It's a tie
Eh?
2nd match!
Let's put out or second
Then I'll go with this guy
Okay, Keigo
Then I'll go with this
[Finally sends out the home base]
Rather than this one, that one is definitely bigger
(I'm leaving it to you)
But the weight feels about the same as just now's
[2nd match]
This is filled with our hopes and dreams
Oh no
- What?
- (No way)
47 grams
(We can do this!)
- Can I put it?
[Takumi's precious home base]
- Sure
I have love for this one
I'm gonna do it
Go!
Home base from a baseball match
Ah don't shake it
I'm doing it. Ready, go
Ready, go
The weight is 64 grams!
This is epic
Yay!!
We lost this time
So the weight battle is Takumi team's victory!
As expected!
As expected of the home base
[Results of strawberry picking showdown]
[Final battle is decided by totaling sugar level + weight!]
First, the total score of our team is 60.7
It's high
And Takumi's team is
Total
Hence it's Takumi's team's victory!
We lost this time
As expected, because it's the activity Takumi wanted
As expected of the strawberry fairy
But we ate a lot, so I don't feel like we lost
With that, for the team that lost, we have a punishment
Eh?
[* The losing team wears a strawberry hat to film a strawberry CM!]
We have concluded the winner and loser
Here is the losing team!
Strawberries!
[Strawberry men]
Their faces are scary
You guys are making a funny face
This is a real loss
We would like these cute strawberries to film a CM
Specially for today, we have invited a director
We have invited a director
- (Blank)
- (Expectant)
The super famous director...
Mr. Bo Shion
We look forward to working with you
Hello!
You guys have a great look in your eyes
You look like you could shine
[Happy]
Shion-san, we want a CM that looks delicious
Can you give the strawberries some direction?
You have a great look in your eyes
Is this a punishment for Shion?
This is something I just thought of in 5 seconds
Shall I do it once?
- Oh you're gonna do it?
[Super famous director Mr. Bo Shion's example]
- I'm gonna use this
- You're using that?
You guys will change it up by improvisation
I see! As expected
[What is a super famous director's CM like?]
Straw~straw~strawberry~berry!
Is this it?
This is it
This is it?
We are supposed to do this?
Yes
- Please become a strawberry
- Strawberry fairy apprenticeship
Then, we'll start
[Keigo standby]
Please!
[Action]
Straw~straw~strawberry~berry!
- Wow!
[Super satisfied]
Thank you
- I've decided for you to star in my next movie
[Confirmed(?) movie role]
- Whoa!
(Blank)
Continuing on, Sukai please!
[Sukai standby]
His face is scary!
[Action!]
Straw~straw~strawberry~berry!
Autumn picking, cheeks full of berries
[Impressed applause]
He even made a song for us
He's protecting his body
[CM star]
- Wow
- We took a good one
He's turned cold
We took a good one
- Shosei-kun looks uneasy
[The 3 people who can't laugh]
- Let's continue at this pace
- Leader!
[Shosei: I want to go home]
Please
[Sho standby]
[Action!]
Straw~straw~strawberry~berry!
Ouch!
That was no good
I thought it was going well
But it wasn't that good
This is tough
Well but balance-wise it's fine
[Good work Sho]
Success, success, fail
(worry)
[2 people left]
Syoya please!
Have a look at this amount of strawberries
It's amazing isn't it!
[He escaped!]
Yes. Thank you very much
That would happen
- We left him for last
[Finally! Last!]
- For the last, we paved the road
- Shosei's face LOL
(worry) (pressure) (nervous) (I want to go home)
Are you ready?
Shake it off
We'll start...Shosei please!
Straw~straw~strawberry~berry!
I'm sorry
It's my fault
- We wanted to help you, sorry
[Good work to the strawberries]
Today we ate lots of strawberries
- Thank you
- It was fun wasn't it?
How was it, Ohira-kun?
It was really fun (tired)
He's tired
Strawberry picking was really fun
We got to enjoy the Spring lots, right?
Yes
- Look forward to next time too!
[Sukai's birthday plate on standby]
[Check Sukai's birthday plate in Ep.14]
Today, Kinjo Sukai turns 22, doublet!
He got it right for the first time
That was JO1!
See you next week~
Shall we eat our friends (strawberries)?
[Translation & Timing by @cshinjam]