Let's do this!
[Wanko Ramen Tournament Opening]
[Previously]
[Although they challenged it full of confidence]
[The struggling members...]
[The me of tomorrow is over there...]
[Among them, Shion who finished eating with fierce speed]
[Current ranking]
I will announce the 4th match
[Wanko Ramen 4th match]
Yes
Shiroiwa Ruki vs. Kimata Syoya
Right...
And the support roles are Kono Junki & Sato Keigo
Yes, I look forward to working with you
I look forward to working with you
And the timekeepers are
Kawashiri Ren & Ohira Shosei
I look forward to working with you
Right, Syoya, a word of enthusiasm please
- My throat often gets choked
- Oh my
- So I'm a little nervous about eating quickly
- I see
But...I'll do my best!
Ohhh!
He took off his glasses
Ohhhh~
- Just eat deliciously
- The time to aim for is 1min 47s
That's right...
The wall is too high
At least I want to measure up to it
Oh! You want to finish under 2 minutes?
[Confident Syoya]
I would like to hit around 2 minutes
Wonderful
Yes
- Right, Ruki
- Yes
How is it?
I feel like I've already ate 60 bowls
From watching
That's right
I already feel full
But he's in-charge of being JO1's big-eater, isn't he?
I'll win
[Outfield gets hyped up]
That's great
Full of energy even before it starts
Will there be an unexpected plot twist?
Do your best!
I have my special move
Whoa!
We look forward to that
Right then, the 4th match...
Ready...
Start!
[Wanko Ramen Tournament]
[4th Match Start]
- Go!
- Oh Ruki is fast!
- Ruki is fast for his 1st bowl
I give up
No no that's too fast! You can still do it
[Giving up within 5s of starting!?]
You can still do it
[Been waiting forever]
See, he's waiting!
He's waiting so hurry up and eat
- Keigo-kun has frozen
- Eat, eat
[Syoya also gives up!?]
He's just waving his hand sideways
Syoya?
[Syoya chews properly]
Chew properly, okay?
It's yummy, isn't it?
- Their hands have stopped
- Yummy, isn't it?
They're just people eating by the counter
Both of you, the time...
[Did you forget this is a speed competition?]
Do your best, Ruki!
[Still on his 3rd bowl]
Syoya do your best as well
Syoya has turned into a bunny
HIs face has turned into a bunny
His face is a bunny
[Mouth stuffed]
I can't tell if he's a bunny or a squirrel!
I can't swallow it
I can tell he wants to go for it but he can't
[Cute Syoya]
His face is stuffed
I can tell, I really can tell
Shiroiwa Ruki has put leek in his mouth
- How is it, Shiroiwa Ruki?
- Rukkun do your best
Is this your special move?
[Is he finally showing his special move!?]
[What is his special move?]
It's here!
[Special Move: Cola]
Here is when he makes a big comeback!
What is he gonna do with it!?
He's gonna drink it...!
...That's all
How is it?
Delicious
It's just delicious
[The effect of the special move is outstanding!]
Go go go go go
[The 2 of them continue to eat desperately]
Slow...
[1st place *flying away*]
Shion and Mame have already finished by now
- This is so funny
- Finished by now
Oh, Syoya as well now...
Ruki-kun look at his face
This is dangerous
[Crisis]
Don't make them laugh
&#^!@#$#@*&*
[Forget the match, Syoya eats ramen deliciously]
The first time someone is going for the chashu
He's gone for the eating deliciously route
[chew chew]
(counting)
Pour it in...
There's no love
There's no love in the way you are pouring it in
Ruki's second has lost his all willpower
[Hah...]
Let's do that, try to make the food go down
The thing Akasaka-san does...
[T/L note: Famous competitive eater]
The food-fighter
[Advice from his second, strategy to make the noodles go down]
Did it go down?
Will he be able to speed up?
He's going for it!
From here, it's become a mental strength competition between the two
Spirit and guts
Syoya probably can finish it, no problem
He can finish the amount
Syoya!!!
Syoya do your best!
Will JO1's big-eater give up here!?
[Syoya is the hope of JO1 big-eaters]
Do you give up?
It's sour
He says it's sour
He has prospects of winning
That's true, he's really catching up
Do your best!
Oh, Ruki has taken the lead!
Rukkun do it!
[I got it, I got it]
Syoya you can do this~
[Cheering team gets fired up at a 1-bowl difference]
Be quiet!
[Burst out laughing]
Do your best~
Syoya, will you show your willpower?
Let's eat slowly
He's catching up!
That's great
[glance]
His hand is trembling
[Who will finish first!?]
Oh no he has frozen
[Ruki stops]
Wash it down with water
Will you give up?
- He doesn't!
- So cool!
6 more
[The 2 continue to work hard slurping noodles]
Syoya is left with...4 bowls!
4 more bowls!
[Ruki's condition is odd]
[What's up?]
Umm...I'm seeing stars
OH NO OH NO!!
Clang clang clang!
[Forced end for Ruki with 6 bowls left]
Syoya is left with 2 bowls!
You're not finished eating yet?
It's no good to have leftovers
Ohh that's cool!
Like a drama!
Please play the theme song of Rocky
Here it is! The last bowl!
Go go go!
[Syoya's last bowl]
It's the last!
Cheered on by staff and members...
[JAM all over the world are cheering for you too, Syoya]
What is beyond?
Everyone, devote yourselves!
Devote yourselves!
[Like the climax of a movie]
Will he achieve glory? Or hell?
Now, it will be written...!
Wow!
[Syoya 20 bowls completed]
It's your win!
[Moved]
It's you! Kimata
You're no longer an amateur! You're a pro!
[Wanko world's PRO of PRO]
Both of you did your best
Nice fight
[Good match]
It was a hot match between men
Ah, that's enough
[In contrast to the hot battle, a cool finale]
[Cry]
We're curious...please announce his timing
Syoya's time...
12min 21s
Wow! Nice fight!
Rather than speed, we watched a drama
[Well done]
Ruki you did your best too
Rather than a drama, I saw stars
Here we go
The 5th match is Sato Keigo vs Kono Junki!
[I'll do my best!]
[Pose & expression opposite]
Alright, let's have a word of enthusiasm from each side
This is my first meal in 3 days
Thank you [monotone]
In reality, it's about half a day
Do your best
I prepared just for this
[Ready]
- What about Sato Keigo?
- I'm full
Oh?
But I would like to finish eating
Okay then, the 5th match...
Ready...
Start!
Go!
How will it go?
Just do your best!
Oh Junki is quite fast!
[2 of them go at high speed from the start]
Keigo is fast too!
Keigo is unexpectedly fast
[2 of them go at high speed from the start]
Go go go
Junki is really fast
Junki is crazy
How does everyone eat without chewing?
He's practically drinking it
Their seconds aren't even speaking
[Both seconds desperately keeping up]
This is variety, please say something
Junki is fast!
He's just left with 2...4...6! Wow!
He's finished more than half!
You're doing it
Yum!
You're number one
Don't make him laugh
You're number ONE
He's so fast! Wow!
Junki is so freaking fast!
Keigo-kun, is it yummy?
Junki is about to finish
Last spurt!
You're too fast!
Put it in your mouth and you're done
Put it in your mouth...and you're...done!
[DONE!]
[With shocking speed,
Junki 20 bowls complete]
Junki has finished!
[Yay!]
He's amazing
There's a monster among us
- But Keigo is fast too
- He's fast!
Really fast!
Let's show our manly side!
[Setting up]
[Man who does what he says, Keigo]
- His manliness is amazing
- Wonderful
His body is starting to tremble
- Is this the last?
- No, he has 1 more bowl
You're almost done, Keigo-kun
- With this...
- Last!
Keep the time properly
Once you put it in your mouth...you're done
Ok!
Done!
[Keigo 20 bowls complete]
You're done. Wonderful
[In a daze]
This is crazy
[Applause for the hot match]
This is really tough
Starting with keigo's time
Yes
Please
Keigo-kun's time
[Mouth stuffed]
2min 42s!
Fast!
[Great struggle]
Can Junki set a new record!?
Right, and Kono Junki who we are curious about...
- Wait a minute...
- This is seriously crazy
The time...
- They are already laughing
- Announce it...
...Please!
Kono Junki-kun's time...
1min 25s!
- Wow! Amazing!
- A monster
- Are you for real?
- Gross! [disbelief]
I mean it was like...
There's already a 20sec difference between this
How about you stop being the main vocal and be the main competitive eater?
Main competitive eater
- You're crazy
- You can't do it like this
[Rather than accumulating in the mouth,]
You have to get it down
[Swallow strategy]
So my way was no good
When it got full, it became tough
I see
Keigo are you ok?
[Doesn't seem ok...]
Keigo-kun is fast too
Even though I did my best
This guy is too fast
[Junki at impossible speed]
He got all the attention
(Keigo is) 4th place
[High level battle]
Fast!
That's true, Keigo is fast too at 2min 42s
[Proof(?) of hard work]
- There are noodles here
- Here?
I have noodles (men) here, and bamboo shoots (menma) here
It doesn't go up to the brain
Bamboo shoots and maybe my ears will have seaweed
- This whole thing...
- Becomes ramen?
Nice fight!
Good work!
Amazing
Alright now
The phoenix
The last person, Yonashiro Sho!
[Last is the leader]
Go leader!
Due to the numbers, he is doing it alone
[Due to the numbers, solo participation]
I'll do my best
It's a battle with self
Do it under 2min
Once I sit here it's so nerve-wracking
Everyone is your second
I'll do it under 2min!
10 of us will support you
That's true
A word of enthusiasm please
I have seen everyone's bravery
I would like to finish eating it
- Go! - Speed is important too
[All members cheering on the leader]
Without any further ado, let's begin
Ready...
Start!
Go go go
Where's your 'itadakimasu'?
- His second is...
- Hm? Ruki?
[Second is a little clumsy]
Oi!
The way he pours it is funny
[Picture of watching the leader eat in silence]
At the end, we have a silent time
Sho-kun really?
Y'all are amazing
You don't have to talk!
- Eat it
- You shouldn't talk
Don't talk!
- Pour it in with some force
- Ok
[Legendary second interrupts]
As expected of the pro
[Second exchange]
Doing good!
You're good at pouring it in
[Go leader]
JO1 is behind you!
- It's sour
- Don't talk!
Chew fast
Chew it finely
Show the willpower of the oldest!
Cheer a little more
[Cheering on the leader with all their might]
Show the willpower of the leader!
[Speeds up from the cheers of members]
How many more bowls?
Everyone is watching and supporting you!
Last bowl!
Will he show us his willpower?
[20 bowls complete]
Nice fight!
[As expected of JO1's leader]
Ah...
This is stupid
That's right
[It's a member-requested activity!]
Shall we announce the time?
Yonashiro Sho's time...
3min 10s!
Wow! That's fast
We ate plenty didn't we?
We did
[Good job]
We ate plenty
[full]
Let's announce the results
Okay
I'm curious
The result
3rd place
His time is 2min
Wow! That's fast
That's 3rd place
[As expected of the maknae]
And...2nd place
1min 47s
Thank you
- Aren't you too fast?
- As expected
And the Wanko Ramen Champion is...!
1st place
1min 25s
So fast
There's an award
This is for Kono-kun
Wah, is that ok?
Thank you very much!
[Wanko Ramen Champion]
I can't believe I'm receiving such an amazing award
I'm the king of wanko ramen
- It was simply delicious, right?
- It was wonderful
Next
We'll do wanko udon
That's enough [everyone's consensus]
Thank you very much [bow]
Today, has everyone eaten their fill?
Yes we did!
This was the members' long-sought wanko ramen tournament, wasn't it?
Yes
How was it, actually doing it?
How was it, Sho-kun?
That's right...it was fun
- Are you sure?
- That's suspicious
- We put it in
- That's right
We stuffed it in
It's great it looked like the seconds were having fun
It was painful while doing it
[Wanko Ramen was fun]
Watching it was really fun
[That's right]
You feel great sense of accomplishment after finishing
Let's do something fun next time too
Okay!
With that, see you next week~
Bye bye~
See you next week~