[Forming a line and entering while getting along]
What is this?
Oh, this sure is something
[Mysterious objects on the table]
I'm hungry
- Before that, shall we do our greeting?
- Yes
Ready...go
Who said "Go"?
It's ok, it's ok
[I got it a little wrong ^^;]
Everyone, today we have JO1's long-sought...
Wanko...
Wanko...?
Ramen!
It's not soba
By everyone's request, we are having Wanko Ramen on Hi!JO1 this time
I see
Is there anyone with experience eating Wanko Soba?
Nope
No, huh?
Me neither
A first for everyone
[All members challenge Wanko Showdown for the first time]
That's right
[Wanko Ramen Tournament
- Compete by the time taken to finish eating
- Free to add condiments]
We will do an authentic Wanko Ramen Tournament
Tournament
And this time, it will be an individual battle
Ehh...Win...What is winning?
He means 'What do we get from winning?'
Wealth & hygiene (eisei)
What is eisei? LOL
Isn't it 'fame' (meisei)?
- What did I say?
- Hygiene (eisei)
Please look forward (to the reward)
Then, let's start right away!
YES!!!
[I'll do my best!]
[I won't lose!]
Alright everyone, thank you for waiting
For the first match, I have decided it by my arbitrariness and prejudice and eisei(?)
Hygiene
Hygiene is important
I decided it with hygiene
The first match: Ohira Shosei vs Kawashiri Ren
I'll be in your care
And the important support role, Mamehara Issei and Kawanishi Takumi, please
And the timekeepers, Sato Keigo and Tsurubo Shion
I am worried
Please press it properly when it starts
Are you mentally prepared?
Please do it with sportsmanship
In front of you, this...kayaku? What is it called? Ingredients?
Condiments (yakumi)
Umm...
Kayaku(火薬 - gunpowder)?! LOLOLOL
We can't eat gunpowder
(firework noises)
- They call it kayaku(加薬 - addition) for cup ramen
- They do, they do
(firework noises)
[23yo who loves to make fun of the leader ^^]
Shosei, please give a word of enthusiasm
With spirit, I will stuff it in my stomach!
Oh~great!
No, isn't it "as per usual"?
Right, as per usual
Okay, Ren
I'm not confident
But I won't lose to Shosei
[Ren's declaration of war]
He's stirring me up
Things are getting heated!
Right, then Wanko Ramen first match...
Ah, wait a minute!
What?
['Drink water to make the noodles go down easier' plan]
Putting it in your stomach already?
We're starting
(Fight noises)
First match...ready...start!
Go go go
Fast, fast!
[chew chew]
It's like they're drinking it
Don't chew, don't chew!
Shosei is fast!
This looks so tough!
- Go go go!
- You're fast!
Ren-kun!
20 bowls is quite tough!
Ahh and here...!
There's an obstruction!
[Obstruction is not allowed]
You have finished 6 bowls
Shosei is fast!
Shosei do your best!
- 1 minute has passed!
- I can't do this
(Here you go)
[Fighting spirit lost]
Ren may be reaching his limit soon
Shosei is left with 4...5 bowls! So fast!
This is bad!
This is so funny
The noodles are not dry yet!
They are still chewy
Shosei is fast
Shosei is left with 4 bowls!
[Shosei are you for real]
Do your best shosei!
Shosei's hand is trembling
On the other hand, Kawajiri has a relaxed expression
Kawajiri? LOLOL
Ah, Kawashiri
'Relaxed expression'?
[Blank]
Do you give up?
- No he doesn't give up!
- Cool!
Cool! Go for it!
Ren do your best too! Ren is also left with a little bit!
[Continuing to eat with unyielding spirit]
A little bit more...go go go!
Just...oh Shosei...!
[1 bowl left]
- Shosei, swallow it!
- Last spurt!
[Not moving]
Once you put it in your mouth it ends
[*This is not a still image]
Ren-kun's speed has gone up!
Put it in...put it in...!
[Last spurt of willpower]
He's done!
[Shosei 20 bowls complete]
Shosei has finished eating
[Good job]
Ren is still continuing
Everyone let's cheer for Ren, do your best!
No, no, please eat!
He is moving along steadily
It's the last bowl!
Once you put it in your mouth it's the end
Put it in your mouth, once you do, it ends
Go! You can do it!
Ren is shaking too!
Stop! That's the end!
[Ren 20 bowls complete]
[Praising each other for a good fight]
The hottest battle in JO1 history has finished
For the timing, let's start with Ren
- Okay
- Please
4min 22s
- No but that's fast
- It's fast
Then please tell us Ohira Shosei's time
He's fast~
3min 4s
It's JO1's birthday
[In a daze]
You're right!
[Miracle boy who got the number of the debut date]
With that, the first match ends here
By the way, can we hear your thoughts?
I think I'll come to dislike Hi!JO1...
I want to win
[Setting up for 2nd match]
Let's show our manly side
The 2nd match!
The 2nd match is Mamehara Issei vs Kawanishi Takumi!
Show the will of the baseball club!
Koshien Stadium siren?
Then let's have each person...
[This time is a battle of ex-baseball boys]
Then, from Mame
I have nothing but confidence
Cool!
1min...
1 minute?!
My goal is 1 minute
Great
That means 3s per bowl
What about Takumi?
Yes. Well...I don't know about confidence
He has too much confidence that he doesn't even know
The support role is...
Shion
Yes?
The support is Shion
- And Sukai
- Ah, yes
And the time will be recorded by Junki and Syoya
Then, are you ready?
Ready...start!
Oh Mame is fast!
Fast! Mame is fast!
Eat it! Eat it! Eat! Eat it!
If you don't eat it who will
[Be quiet]
I'll laugh
Mame is fast, he's really fast
[chew chew]
He's eating it deliciously
This is not the time to taste it, Takumi
- This is really tough
- It's tough?
In the second half it gets tougher
Taku-chan do your best...Taku-chan?!
- Mame is fast
- Mame is so fast...he's left with 5 bowls!
Mame is showing his true strength
Mame do your best!
[I can't do this anymore...TT]
Mame is fast!
Takumi-kun...!
Chew it properly
[Chew chew]
Takumi wants to catch up!
Ah, he combined it!
Last bowl!
- Go go
- Last!
Can he do it? Just put it in your mouth
Finished!
[Mame 20 bowls completed]
[At the same time that Mame finished eating]
(clang clang clang)
Oh! Player Takumi has...?
[On Takumi's 6th bowl]
By his trainer's decision, he will give up here
[On Takumi's 6th bowl, doctor stop]
[I'm curious what's Mame's time!?]
Mamehara-kun's time...
Exactly 2 minutes!
Amazing!
That's really amazing
[Applause of praise]
[Current ranking]
It's the 3rd match
In the red corner, Kinjo Sukai
In the blue corner, Tsurubo Shion
For the second, it's the famous Takumi-sensei
We look forward to working with you, Takumi-sensei
And for Player Shion, it's the famous Syoya-sensei
- Are you famous?
- Yes
How are you with eating fast?
Well, normally I don't chew much
Shion is really fast
So I'll just go a little bit faster than usual
- That's right, keep at it like this
- Thank you
Sukai?
By the way, before this filming, I ate 3 bentos
Will you be ok?
Yeah~
Are you ready?
[Has been all good to go since earlier]
Ready...start!
Do your best!
- He's chewing it properly?
- Don't chew
He's not chewing much- oh this is a good match
[Shion going at quite a fast pace]
Shion's pace is fast!
Ah, he stopped
Shion is seriously fast
You're doing good, Sukai
Sukai is also catching up
Isn't Shion-kun faster than me?
Finish one bowl under 6 seconds
The second half is important
Kono pick it up!
Oi! Where do you think you're putting it!
The second is...
Sukai has stopped!
GO!!
[Has finished eating 3 bentos]
Shion is fast!
[In that gap, Shion's last spurt]
The way his body is facing
[Going at it seriously
Looking at the ramen instead of the camera]
He's facing there
Do your best Shion!
Sukai do your best
Chashu
He took leek
Go at it easily
Sukai is crying! That Sukai is crying!
Do your best, Sukai TT
Shion is finishing!
Shion-kun is too fast
[A distant look]
Shion's last spurt! 2 bowls left!
Last bowl! Put it in your mouth and it ends
Last bowl!
[Shion 20 bowls completed]
Shion has finished, we're left with Sukai
[Can Sukai finish eating!?]
Did you put too much leek?
[I don't want to look at ramen anymore TT]
Sukai will you give up?
Let's do this!
[BTW he has 12 bowls left]
Do your best!
Will his second stop him?
Will his second throw in the towel?
His second is looking!
His second will throw soba instead of the towel
[Protection]
He's laughing
Give up?
No
You can do it
He's still left with quite a bit
[Where are you looking!?]
Oh no oh no, give up give up!
[Forced end by the second's judgement]
[Kinjo Sukai KO]
He's looking towards tomorrow
[Looking towards tomorrow]
[Can Shion cross the wall of 2 minutes!?]
Now, Shion's time..
It's crazy
- 1min 47s
- Crazy!
[Applause all around]
This is seriously tough, really
[Current ranking]
[Next episode preview]
[Excitement rises in Wanko Ramen Tournament]
Even the second isn't speaking
[A match with an unpredictable end]
This is variety, please speak
[Lonely by himself, eldest who wants some love]
Please make some noise
Do your best, do your best!
The Wanko Ramen champion is...
[In the end, who is the first generation champion?!]