- Okay say cheese
[EP.8 Family Photo]
[Shooting of family photo in various poses]
- Okay say cheese
Isn't it good?
It's good
- Um...Avengers
[Junki's suggestion - Avengers Pose]
So we just do something Avengers-like?
Or Junki does the pose and we watch?
Try doing it once, we'll watch
We will watch as guardians
Okay...Cheese
[Rawr]
[Avengers Junki & the 10 guardians(?)]
Oh it's cool
...I think we should stop this
- You noticed?
- I think we should stop
Let's all do it together
- Avengers-like
[All 11 will do a hero-like pose]
[The hero Mame chose: Kamen Rider]
- LINE stamp
[The hero Syoya chose: LINE stamp(?)]
[Villain...?]
Okay say cheese
Iron Man isn't like that!
- A hero in his own way
- The strongest one
[Monitoring the photos taken]
This is epic
We took an amazing one!
Here it is!
[The photo taken earlier]
This is great!
Toshio-kun?
♫ I’ll be holding on to it ♫
[Break time - Dreamer (acapella ver.)]
♫ Towards the other side of the dream I’ve envisioned ♫
♫ Oh I’m sure I can head there with you ♫
[Break time - Dreamer (acapella ver.)]
♫ We are still dreamers, dreamers ♫
♫ Go closer and closer, without hesitation ♫
[Break time - Dreamer (acapella ver.)]
♫ This feeling is getting closer ♫
♫ Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah ♫
[Break time - Dreamer (acapella ver.)]
♫ It’ll always be in my heart ♫
♫ Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah ♫
[Break time - Dreamer (acapella ver.)]
♫ Don’t ever let go of this hand ♫
♫ We’ll walk together towards tomorrow, one step at a time ♫
[Break time - Dreamer (acapella ver.)]
[EP.9 April Fools]
[Syoya's prank ①: Edible memo paper]
- I was asked to write a message
[Setting up under the premise of being asked to write a message card]
Rukkun, Rukkun
We were told to write the usual thank you message for Hi!JO1
I kinda don't want to
I don't want to
This is suspicious, you sitting alone here
No no no...I've been writing this all this while
But in the end...
Your handwriting is terrible, it's in a mess
That's why I was told to re-write it, so I'm here
That's nothing, really
Just write normally
I don't want to
I don't want to now. I want to see how things go first
I got tricked here, and I got tricked outside too
Right now I don't trust humans
I don't want to for now
Something is weird!
Because he's been here with a serious face since I came in, so this is weird
This is scary x∞
Please let me escape just this once
I'm sorry...I don't trust humans right now
I'll return once I decide to trust humans again
Damn it~
The plan was a failure
Why??
[Prank failed]
[Syoya doesn't give up - Tries again with the next member]
[Junki having the fake interview in the next room]
Eh? Is this the end?
Is it the end?
We were told to write a message
Write a message?
And show it to the camera, I'll show mine now
Is this no good? Ruki-kun told me my handwriting is bad
What kind of message are we supposed to write?
[Junki who writes earnestly despite having doubts]
[Ta-da]
[Chomp]
You really did it!
- Yummy~
[Edible memo prank (small) success]
[Syoya's prank ②: Edible sponge prank]
Why is Syoya here?
I'll just eat the sponge and go
[Chomp]
Heh?
Is that all you wanted to do?
It was a prank~
Thank you very much
Is that really all??
- That's all
[Prank failed]
What if you use the sponge to pretend to scrub the area?
Leave a space and scrub
Say "help me clean"
Then you eat the sponge, that would be shocking
[Keigo's model-example prank: Edible sponge course]
(He's here?)
[Pretending to scrub]
I'll be in your care~
[Mame's turn for fake interview]
What are you doing?
You startled me
It's dirty here...
[So suddenly?]
- I'm helping to clean
- Why?
- It's dirty over here
Help me
Whoa
That looks yummy...wow!
- Wow
- Were you shocked?
I was shocked
That's all
That's the end?
[Keigo-sensei's prank big failure]
[Fake interview]
[Q. If you were to depict your thoughts of Spring in 5 characters?]
S-Sakura Tree
What I think of Spring, in 5 characters...
Youth
'Youth' in Hiragana
- Breed...Umm...
[Q. If  you were a dog which breed would you be?]
Toy Poodle
I like them so I keep 3 Toy Poodles at home
So the first reason is that I like them
And the fur doesn't shed easily
With the desire towards Toy Poodles
Because I like Toy Poodles
Yes...a Toy Poodle
Breed?
Chiwapoo (Chihuahua + Poodle)
It's a Chihuahua and Poodle mix
Because I like it
Ehhh....the one with short legs
Or maybe not
I'm not that short
Um, then...Golden Retriever
Retrie~ver? Retrive~r?
That
[EP10. Secret Mission]
[Before mission starts, Mame & Sho playing with pointing stick]
Ohhh Shion is probably good at this
No no...You're losing, you know?
Keigo, he's losing
- I'm good, right?
- You're good
You lost
But when this comes near to you, it becomes difficult to see, right?
Sho-kun, do you want to try once?
I really-
I'll go like this
Try hitting it once
Like this
It doesn't hurt
Ok ok ok
But if you hit the eye...
Ouch
[EP.11 Zombie Game]
[Takumi Zombie-chemi compilation]
Wait who is this?
Who is this??
I got it, I got it
It's Takumi
Oh, who is this?
We caught him!
Who?
Mame
Let's hold hands
One more person
Let's decide who will make sandwich and who will make onigiri
[EP.12 Spring Picnic]
How should we split the teams?
The teams will be split like this
The team split will be from the middle...
Which side do you wanna go to?
Hmmmmmmm
Okay...then let's split it here
From the middle
- Oh I see! You get to pick, right?
- Yes
So it'll be split 6-5
[Team split complete]
[Before making the bentos]
[<-Karaage]
[What should I do?]
[Junki who gave in to temptation]
Is it yummy?
[Yeah]
Yummy!
I'm controlling myself
[Pretending he didn't eat it]
Hm?
[Chew chew]
- This is so funny!
[After balloon relay]
[Takumi who had too much fun during the game...]
[I'll roll you!]
[Roll roll]
- Both of you squeeze him
[In the middle of team punishment game]
[Onigiri team playing with giant bubble]
- That would hurt!
[In the middle of team punishment game]
[Onigiri team playing with giant bubble]
Ready...go!
Ah, it doesn't hurt
- Really??
- It doesn't hurt
- Then I'll go in
- Really?
Let's do it
Ready...go
It hurts!
It hurts a lot!
Ready...go
It feels good
[A tough front]
I'll try it once with Junki-kun
[Ren -> Sukai player change]
[Escape]
[EP 14. Strawberry picking]
- I'll tell you a strawberry fun fact
[Junki's strawberry fun fact course!]
Strawberries have these grains, don't they?
That is the actual fruit
[The grainy bits on the surface of the strawberry is the actual fruit]
I have another
Strawberries is a fruit introduced by the Dutch
[Strawberry fun fact ②]
Apparently they used to be called Dutch strawberries
I have another
You have so many!
The tip of strawberries are sweet
Yeah
They're sweet...so the end of the strawberries taste a little sour
So if you eat from the end first, your level of happiness increases
[Strawberry fun fact ③]
I still have another
(You still have another? LOL)
Strawberries are...
[Ren's strawberry fun fact]
...Delicious!
Ah, strawberries are classified as vegetables
[Strawberry fun fact ④]
[Strawberries are classified as vegetables]
It's true!
Yes, if you were to state its' class, it's a vegetable
That's all
[Junki's strawberry fun fact course END]
Itadakimasu
Yum!
[Translation & timing by @cshinjam]