Next, we have the representatives from Japan!
We are not on-screen yet (LOL)
[The trio who enter an empty room]
How is it?
[The 3 people who enter an empty room]
- It has finally come
- Yes
The time has come
What are we gonna be doing now?
The preparations for Mame-chan's birthday party!
[JO1's strongest maknae Mame!
All members will prepare an unforgettable surprise party
for Mame who will turn 20 during filming!]
Let's decorate
We will be taking turns to decorate, so that Mame doesn't find out
We'll be in your care
Let's have a look at this
[Starting off by checking the item Ren is holding]
[Mame 20th BD celebration item 1:
Original banner!]
Oh it's huge!
We have such an awesome item too
So let's start decorating right away
This is awesome
We are like fans
- Then let's do it - Okay
[Decorating start!!]
- This is the 20th anniversary
- Where shall we put it?
For this, isn't on top the best?
[There's no stepladder...]
[Bunny dispatched!]
[While Syoya goes off to get the stepladder]
- Keigo look at Mame from here
- Huh?
Look at Mame from the middle
From where I am
[Playing with Mame's picture on the banner]
[Stepladder IN]
Doesn't he look a little like me?
Here is the stepladder
[Syoya who has returned with a stepladder and tape]
Okay, please do it
Can you put it up top, Syoya?
I'll hold it down from below
How should I put it up?
However is fine
Should I paste it?
[First, deciding where to hang the banner]
I have tape...ah, can you tear off the tape for me?
Ah ok ok
Shall we put it here?
Here
It won't tear off at all~
[Thinking of the most efficient method]
Shall we tie the center bit first?
- Inside
- Here?
- Yeah
- That's possible
[Far]
Shall I move the stepladder
[Move the stepladder]
Then we don't need the tape?
- Just for the middle
- We may not need it for the middle
Do your best! Do your best!
[Banner hanging going smoothly]
That's nice
[This is fun]
Because I used to make clothing
[Experienced in making clothes]
[Doing it while talking about past memories,
the banner that turned out pretty well]
- We can paste the bottom
- I'll tie this part too
[A craftsman]
The time now is...
8.30pm
So that means Mame's birthday is in 3.5 hours
We would like to work a little speedily
How many more do you need, Keigo?
[Stepladder exits]
You don't need it?
No, we are fine
Wow! We've done it
Hey, this...
[God of reflexes!?]
[To finish, decorating around the banner with balloons]
Isn't this really great?
It seems so
Let's hurry a little
Look
I'll paste this here
Look! Look! Look!
Isn't this great?
[Syoya's favourite]
[Let's continue decorating even more!]
Here would be good too
[At that moment!]
- Oh! They have come - You need us
[Time to pass the baton]
[Child 1]
[Child 2]
- Sorry to keep you waiting
- We've been waiting
- We'll help out - Wow
[Next members to help prep]
[Here! Tape]
Then, we'll do a baton pass
Leave it to us!
We'll go and prevent Mame from leaving his spot
- Leave it to us~
- Oka~y
Alright! Shall we?
[Next, the 3 who will decorate with balloons]
[Choosing items]
Let's paste everything here
[Shion is in-charge of around the table]
I'll past the tape, so...
[Junki & Sho working together]
[Troubled over the position of the candle]
No, in front is better
No
[Haste]
That candle is kinda scary
Right? It isn't that good
[U-turn]
[Reliable members, progressing steadily]
That's for a dog
Like this...
[A HOT object appears]
- Ohh
- What kind of birthday is this?
[Mame's 20th BD celebration item 2: Original T-shirt]
[T-shirt: 'Today's protagonist']
What is this?
I've pasted it there properly
[This is an important item! ]
Leave it in the middle
It's Mame's feed(?)
Mame's feed~
Our Maknae...is becoming an uncle
[By the way, finally all of JO1 will be adults]
- We are all...
- He's ONLY 20
Junki what did you do when you were 20?
I was a university student
For Shion...oh that's right
I celebrated it together with JO1's 1 year formation anniversary
That's right
- Sho-kun, please give me some (tape)
- Okay
I did it, doesn't it look great?
What did I do when I was 20...?
It's great
- Put it around the neck
- Oh
- Can you?
- You can't see it
- Here you go, Junki
- Thank you
For real, what did I do when I was 20...?
Can I have some tape?
- Could it be you were just working part-time?
- I was just working part-time
How long ago was this?
Umm...6 years ago...
Isn't that crazy? 6 years ago
- You're an uncle
- I'm seriously an uncle
That's crazy
[Where are there such young uncles!]
6 years ago
Do we inflate this? What is this?
We don't inflate that
I'm concerned about the single gold balloon in front
There's just 1 gold balloon
This? Who put this?
This doesn't go here
No, that...
[Their conversations do not mesh, but a peaceful trio]
[Shion and Sho focusing on the gold wreath]
Sparkly sparkly~
The sparkly thing is in the camera
Down there too
Rustle rustle~
[Giant balloon attack!!!]
- You received a blow
- That would make you go AHH
Sho-kun here
[Sudden visual attack is greatly welcomed]
Shosei has come
[Baton pass time again]
Oh okay
Okay~
[Shosei has arrived, baton pass to the last team]
End!
[Wait a moment!]
[The final decorators are]
Alright!
It's Mamehara Issei-kun's birthday so we would like to decorate
- I brought a cake too
- Oh, that's great
This...this is...
Is it fine to put this here?
- The cake...
- Isn't it best to put it in the middle?
Good work
Where should I put this?
We want to use that for the top, so place that behind
[Member full of individuality appears (LOL)]
Here I go
[Be careful]
What do you want dismantled?
No no no...this is for decorating
[Mame's 20th BD celebration item 3: Big cake with photo]
Cute~
Let's start
- Shall we decorate this?
- Can we decorate this?
If we scatter this it would be cute
[Petals]
What should we do with this?
These red flowers would look nice by the red carpet
- That's nice
- It'll be cute, right?
[Full of sense! Shosei scatters flowers by the red carpet]
I wonder if it's enough?
- Let's just scatter it for now
- Yeah
[After the petals, scattering the balloons around!]
That was close!
This is quite difficult
[Lastly, Ruki decorates the cake]
Do it by your senses
Ah, it's good
It's good
Another 2.5 hours...
1.5 hours to Mame-chan's birthday
I'm looking forward to it!
Heart
3...
The heart is crazy difficult
Isn't it great!
Is it okay?
It is, it's cute
Umm...
We wrote on Mame's cake
We decorated it
[Clap clap]
[With this, the party prep is complete!
We're just left with the actual event!!]
[excited]
Ready...go!
[After today's filming, members have gathered in the decorated room again]
Everyone knows why we are here, right?
Yes!
Mame's 20th birthday party!
All of us decorated
for a grand celebration for Mame
[Because our maknae is precious]
Right now it's...
23:55!
[5 minutes until Mame turns 20]
5 more minutes
5min left, we have no time
[Excitedly waiting while going to call Mame over]
[Nervous]
Here he comes!
[Finally, today's protagonist appears]
[Welcome MAME]
[Shy]
Red carpet!
[Mame's 20th BD celebration Item 4: red carpet]
We did it up till the very end
Look at the camera
[Shy Mame's reaction has broken LOL]
Yes
Mame, what do you think this is?
He can see it a little
Isn't it written there? It writes 'Happy Birthday'
Then let's all countdown to Mame's 20th together!
How many more minutes?
3 more minutes~
Then Mame, please change into 'Today's Protagonist' T-shirt
- Change
- 3 more minutes
[Change quickly!]
- Stand in the middle
- Today's protagonist has arrived!
Then Mame, stand in the middle
1 more minute!
I'm happy, but this is too obvious
It is, isn't it? Sorry, that's our style
Too obvious
Let's pop the crackers together
Together??
Together
There was not a single person in the dressing room
We were busy preparing
We are bad at lying
How is it, it's your final time in your tens
Yes...it's fast
It's not often we get to welcome the 20s together with everyone
So I'm really happy
[A precious time for both Mame and members]
You're turning 20
I'm happy, I want to turn 20 quickly
How many minutes?
15s!
[countdown start!]
[Mamehara Issei turns 20!]
Congrats!
[From today I am 20]
Then let's open the cake
- Then Mame open it
- Is that okay?
I'll just lift it
Cake, open!
[Decorated cake filled with everyone's love]
[Candle still not going out?]
[Candle doesn't go out...?]
[Then let's sing more!]
[After waiting a long time, suddenly a tune begins to play]
[Members confused by the strange candle]
[Finally]
[Hyped up by the strange candle]
This is awesome!
Mame blow it out
- This is amazing
- It's spinning
[Countdown and cake done]
Mame, Happy 20th!
From 17yo, 3rd year in high school till 20yo
What is your aspirations for your 20s?
Aspirations for my 20s...
I want to continue on without change
And to show everyone a Mamehara Issei who has matured a little
I will work hard in my 20s
Wonderful
Mame, now that you've become an adult
What is the #1 thing you want to do right now?
- Do right now?
- Yes
What I want to do...
[Curious big brothers]
I want to kanpai with everyone
[Actually...]
Did you prepare it?
Lastly, let's kanpai!
Wow, is that real?
[It's Cola]
[The filming time is late, so we'll just relish the mood]
This is spirits
The alcohol percentage is 47%?
- No it's 90+%
- About 96%
Cola cooling down~ (song name)
[It's not the real thing, but Mame energy up]
Shall we get Mame to measure the temperature?
We're starting!!
Mamehara Issei has turned 20!
Everyone, let's continue to work hard!
Congrats~
Itadakimasu!
The most delicious thing up till now
Good drinker!
[As expected of an adult!]
How is it, Mame-chan? Isn't this the best drink till now?
You did well!
[20yo Mame and the happy 10 big brothers]
People are gonna really think we are drinking alcohol
No, this is cola ^^
Congrats Mame!
Thank you!
Everyone, good work filming till late
Then it's about time for me to get off work too
Just a little more!
You're really straightforward
Then, see you next week~
With that,
This has been JO1~
See you~ Congrats Mame
[See you next week]
[All of JO1 have become adults and will shine even brighter]
[From now on as well, please support them forever]