[Aomori's extensive snowy landscape]
We're getting closer to a point of no return.
[SHION & JUNKI & SHOSEI are headed to...]
Tsurubo Shion is going wild.
[Oirase Valley Frozen Waterfall]
Kick more! Do it more!
Hey!
Isn't Tokyo colder?
You're right, it isn't cold at all.
I'm only wearing one layer.
Huh!?
I'm serious. This is only one layer.
Take a photo~
I can take it with mine.
(Sad)
Okay, I'll take one.
- Use the flash.
- Oh, sorry.
Okay, cheese.
Oka~y.
I'll take it.
Oka~y!
[The 3 of them finally set off]
This is beautiful!
Can I go in?
(Guide): You can enter from here...
What!?
You can wear snow shoes to enter.
- Okay.
- What!?
- Are you serious?
- Yes, I'm serious.
[They can enter Oirase Gorge
which is a special scenic spot/natural conservation area]
Amazing! This is a valuable experience.
Wow!
[Snow shoes to walk on snow]
Can you get sunburnt even on such a snowy day?
You can, you can.
I mean, the whiteness...
That's right, it reflects.
Even if it isn't sunny...
Oh no, it doesn't fit.
Even if it doesn't seem sunny,
the sun is there.
Wow~
I'm good with snow.
Like skiing and stuff...
Really?
Really, really.
My parents let me do it
since I was 2 years old.
It snows a lot in my hometown,
so I'm quite used to the snow.
Don't underestimate the snow.
I'm not.
[Finally off to search for Oirase Frozen Waterfall]
The ice...
This is scary!
I can't get used to walking in these.
[SHION who is not used to snow stumbles]
This is a piece of cake!
Shion is so slow.
[Reached the icy moss spot]
Wow!
- It's frozen.
- Tiny pieces of ice are on it.
If you look through this,
it's very beautiful.
Wow!
It's goes all the way to the back.
You can see it like this.
Wow, it's beautiful!
- Wow!
- It's beautiful!
[Engrossed with the icy moss]
The ice is amazing too.
The ones with ice is called 'kokegoori'(icy moss).
Kokegoori.
It's really so beautiful.
The blue sky is amazing, isn't it.
- Beautiful!
- This is amazing.
I'm thoroughly enjoying the nature.
We can take in every little detail.
- It's wonderful.
- Right?
[Begins his counterattack against
JUNKI who is having an easy time]
What are you doing, punk?
You're doing the same to me now.
This place doesn't have a name,
but it's wonderful too.
I'm glad to be alive!
Go, go!
[2 of them take pictures]
- Let's go.
- Shion, go!
It's too beautiful.
Be careful!
Don't you fall in!
Don't fall in, Shion!
I'll fall in!
That was dangerous!
It's so beautiful.
It's so beautiful that I wish
both of you weren't in my photo.
[The 2 of them didn't hear that at all]
[Hug]
Let's go!
Everyone, please come here
and take a portrait.
It's really gorgeous.
About the same thickness as this rock...
[Next up is a giant rock]
there's another rock over there.
Whoa! There's another one over there.
- It's said that they used to be connected.
- What!?
The strength of the water alone destroyed it.
It eroded very nicely.
It's a miracle.
Look.
Isn't it crazy how the tree is growing in it?
It looks amazing from this side too.
Maybe I should grow some moss at home.
They sell them at Tokyu Hands.
Oh, don't they sell some around here?
In the hotel,
they sell something called moss balls.
What? That's...
- I'll buy a moss ball.
- Let's buy it.
Whoa! There it is!
It's smooth and beautiful.
It's huge.
- Whoa, look!
- It'll fall!
That tree is amazing.
Isn't it cold?
Now that we've come to the top.
It's getting colder and colder.
- Wow!
- Huh? That's crazy!
Whoa!
Amazing!
It's like a waterfall.
This is the most amazing.
It's just growing from nothing.
It looks like a painting.
Wow!
[Icicles]
Ah! It's cold!
Junki-kun, try touching the large icicles.
It's scary.
Shion, you do it.
Be careful.
You won't have another chance
to touch one that big.
That's like a sword!
I feel like I'll get stabbed.
The big one, right?
Isn't it amazing?
It's too huge.
Don't you want to try punching it?
I want to punch it once.
Wow!
This is awesome!
This is power.
Oh, I have 12 left.
I took so many photos.
This is crazy.
It's photo time.
The next will be better than this.
[Moving to the next HOT spot]
Wow... it's really amazing.
The next will be better than this.
An artwork created by nature.
Oh! "An artwork created by nature".
It was really beautiful.
Art, huh.
Wow!
This is the real deal!
Huh!? Something is growing!
So cute!
They grow from spores.
Oh, spores.
I'll buy moss.
- I'll really buy it.
- We'll buy some back.
Please do.
These are called moss flowers.
[Arrived at the powerful waterfall]
Wow!
Wow! The water splashed on me.
I wanted to see deers.
[To the moss shop at the hotel]
Oh, wow!
This is cute
[Engrossed in selecting moss]
Wow!
[Happy]
I'm choosing this.
[Grandpa?]
[Serious gaze]
To maintain the green, after watering it,
[moss cultivation course]
put it outside in semi-shade.
Outside, okay.
[SHION is fascinated by the Oirase lamps]
Should I buy it?
I'll buy it for real.
Isn't this amazing?
I like that it's not too bright.
This is genius.
I think I'll buy it.
I'm in love with this one.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I think I'll choose this. I love flowers.
This is cute too.
- Flowers?
- I like flowers so I'll choose this.
Wow.
[Lastly, photo shoot outside]
Thank you very much!
It was really fun.