[First impression: What kind of person are you seen as?]
Let's see...
Yes
[First impression: What kind of person are you seen as?]
For Shosei...
I think he simply saw me as a rival
We were teammates but
Because we met during the audition,
Because the first audition trainee we met was each other,
Though he probably saw me as a comrade or teammate as well,
I feel that he also saw me as a rival
[The real first impression is?]
I thought he was this rugged and tough guy, his dance as well
In terms of his appearance
So when I'm wondering which type he is...
When we practiced together,
I realized he was the complete opposite type from his appearance
His dancing is nimble and delicate
His singing as well, he has a clean and delicate voice
'It's the complete opposite~' was my first impression
What he thought of me...
Honestly...
I think he thought 'What's up with this guy..?'
I imagine that's what he may have thought of me
I think I'm a little strange
[The real first impression is?]
Initially, I thought we were around the same age
He seemed more masculine than how he is now
So now he's, how should I put it
He's like a little brother that goes 'Ren-kun, Ren-kun~' affectionately
Initially it was like...while being a teammate
it's properly conveyed that we are also rivals
In a good way, he was hot-blooded
Well he's also hot-blooded now, but in a good way, he was hot-blooded
I see
I think he probably thought I was scary
I did think that a little, initially Keigo-kun was really muscular
So he did give a scary impression, plus he's tall too
But I thought he was really cool, honestly
[He's shy]
Ahh~ Scary
He probably didn't think anything about me
Just a regular...
Person!
Trainee
Well, within me I thought...
That this person would pass (the audition)
Yes. He was in my sights
I think he thought 'This person is noisy'
What I actually thought about him?
Yes
I...
thought he was trying to act cool
[LOLOLOLOL]
- You thought I was trying to act cool
- I thought you were trying to act cool
[Happy]
- Well I did think he was cool at that time
- I'm happy
But I also thought he was trying to act cool
Really? I did?
Yeah
You were this type
Ah, I was cocky?
No, not cocky but
You're like 'Oh~! Isn't it Mame!'
I'm embarrassed
Right, he's that type
- I wish you didn't say that
- He's interesting
He probably thought of me as a kid
Because I was 16- no, 17? So...
I was young at that time
The correct answer is...
That he was cute
Oh!
From that time, everyone was already calling him 'Mame-chan'
I just wanted to become close with Mame
Are you for real?
Ok maybe not that I wanted to be close with him but...
So which is it?
Rather than be close, I just normally wanted to talk with Mame-chan
When he's on his own, or when performing
I thought 'This kid is amazing'
I thought that I wanted to try talking to him
This is embarrassing
It is
What is it...
On the contrary, I didn't think about 'How do others see me?'
- It's a difficult wording
- No I get it x2
So it's not thinking 'How do others see me?'
But instead, I talk to others to find out about that
Ah, that's right
So I didn't think about 'How do others see me?', at that time
That's true x2
So at that point, we talk to each other
Like 'I'm this kind of person' x2
- Right
- It started from there so
So there aren't really any 'How do others see me?' thoughts here
- We talk in order to not have such thoughts
- Right x3
We want to get rid of that
Hence we chatted with each other at the lodge
So I don't remember at all
That's why neither of us remember 'how does he see me?'
- Right?
- Yeah
We don't know
And honestly I don't remember what I thought of him either
Tsurubo Shion thought Kimata Syoya was a genius
Wrong!
[CLAP CLAP CLAP]
Then what is it?
Yes, ummmm...
Ah, it's that kid that went to A class
[A class]
Ohhhhhh
Probably it was that
That's super ordinary
That's just an ordinary thought
Shion happened to be talking to Sukai
And he came to my room, since I'm in the same room (as Sukai)
That was probably our first impression of each other
At that time, what do you think was my impression of you?
- I'm probably correct
- What is it?
- Yankee? (delinquent)
- Yeah yankee
I've said it before
At first I only saw him as a yankee
So it seems
Wearing his patterned shirt with short sleeves
That's right
Coming over like this
I don't do that
No you were like
[Chemistry Test]
[Sunrise or Sunset]
Ready, go!
Both: Sunset
Yaaayy
[Text or Call]
Ren: Text | Shosei: Call
Okay.....
[Tea or Juice]
Ahhhh I see
- Uwaahh
- Wait, this...
The width is amazing, it's like this
[Tea or Juice]
Ready, go!
Ren: Juice
Shosei: Tea
Ohhhh seriously
[Aquarium or Zoo]
Ehhhhh
I know my answer
[Aquarium or Zoo]
Okay, let's go
Ready, go!
Ren: Zoo
Shosei: Aquarium
Ohhhh!!! For real!!!
This is fun
This is seriously amazing
[Which do you do first: Brush teeth or Wash face]
Brush teeth or wash face
Yes
[Which do you do first: Brush teeth or Wash face]
Ready, go!
Both: Wash face
[The food that you like: Eat first or Eat later]
This depends on the food...
I really have to think about this! What should I do?
Okay, let's say 'before' or 'after'
Ready, go!
Both: After!
[Survive in the middle of the desert or
Survive in the middle of the sea]
Ready, go
Ren: Sea
Shosei: Desert
[Run or Swim]
Ready, go
Ren: Run
Shosei: Swim
Seriously?
I don't like the sea but I like to swim
- It's limited to the pool?
- Limited to the pool
[Flower viewing or Fireworks]
Ready, go!
Ren: Flower viewing
Shosei: Fireworks
We couldn't even match at the end!
Ren-kun and I are funny
[Sunrise or Sunset]
Both: Sunset
[Text or Call]
Both: Call
[The food that you like: Eat first or Eat later]
[What is this synchro?]
- This depends on the day!
- That's right
There are times I eat it right away
Right x5
- Whatever x2 okay x3
- Okay x4
Ready, go!
Both: FIRST!
We're not trying to match each other or anything
Ready, go!
Ruki: Zoo
Sho: Aquarium
[Escaped from the camera angle
What is this synchro...?]
Ruki: Zoo
Sho: Aquarium
- Oh he didn't pick zoo
- Aquarium
Because I'm from Okinawa...
Ahhh! Churaumi right?
Churaumi (Okinawa's Aquarium) came to mind
Right...I hate fishes
Ah, it's like that?
You can't even look at them?
[Not good with fish]
Run or Swim???
They think we are fishes
I've decided
Ready, go!
Ruki: Run
Sho: Swim
Why!?
The sea...
Ah that's right. Do you surf?
I don't surf but I swam
[Yonashiro Sho, Son of Okinawa]
Because there's the sea right there
Right, the sea is there
But that's true, because you hate fish
That's right
That's unrelated
Rather than hate, more like I'm no good with them
[Sorry fishies]
[Survive in the middle of the desert or
Survive in the middle of the sea]
Both: Desert!
Ohhh I thought you would choose the sea
No, because I know how scary the sea is
On the contrary
Because I know how scary the sea is
I wanted to be the single flower blooming in the desert
[Sunrise or Sunset]
Ready, go
Both: Sunset
As expected
[Text or Call]
Ready, go
Both: Call
Eh? No way!
Yeah
Do you even call-
I don't really call but I text even less
Ah so that's the case
I'm bad with it
[Which world do you wanna go to?
Harry Potter or Pirates of the Caribbean]
Keigo: Harry Potter
Takumi: Pirates of the Caribbean
Pirates of... the Caribbean?
Yes
Why?
Cool...pirates...
[Aquarium or Zoo]
Keigo: Aquarium
Takumi: Zoo
It's the aquarium for me
Ahhh is that so
Yeah, zoo for you?
Zoo for me
Well both are fine
That defeats the purpose of the question
[Which do you do first: Brush teeth or Wash face]
Keigo: Brush teeth
Takumi: Wash face
Why?
I wash my face first then brush my teeth
Ehhh no way!
But it's unpleasant to have (toothpaste) here, isn't it?
We'd properly clean it off with water, right?
Or with tissue
Isn't it better to do it all while washing your face?
Eh? Why?
Because I don't like to have it stuck here
I don't want it to be spread around
I'm the type to brush my teeth immediately before bed
or immediately before leaving the house
Oh is that so
That's your routine?
I wouldn't call it a routine
- You just don't like it otherwise
- Yeah
It's like that
[Run or Swim]
Both: Run
- Well well well
- It's definitely so
I don't really swim- Well, I do swim but
Running is probably less intense
Yeah
But you chose Pirates of the Caribbean
Is it contradictory?
Yeah, there's no meaning if you don't swim
There's no opportunity to run
There is, like on the ship deck
It's like that
Yes, it's like that. What's up with that?
[Sunrise or Sunset]
Uwahhh. Ready, go
Junki: Sunset
Mame: Sunrise
Is that so?
Well...I don't know
Both are good ^^
Both are good
[Text or Call]
Ready, go
Both: Call
[Which world do you wanna go to?
Harry Potter or Pirates of the Caribbean]
Junki: Pirates of the Caribbean
Mame: Harry Potter
Well both are fine
I'm lax about this
Out of 3 only 1 is the same
[Tea or Juice]
Junki: Juice
Mame: Tea
I see...I'm wavering too
But recently I haven't been drinking tea
[The food that you like: Eat first or Eat later]
Both: After
Ohh great
I like this
[Run or Swim]
Both: Run
Oh, is that so?
- Yeah, unexpectedly
- Unexpectedly
[Survive in the middle of the desert or
Survive in the middle of the sea]
Both: Sea
I can swim, so I was thinking of the sea
I like pirates so...
[Snort]
I like Pirates of the Caribbean so...
I've always wanted to become a pirate
You said a few different things, which is it?
I want to become a pirate
Ah, I see
Yes
I really want to
Are you fine with being the insignificant pirate character?
I'm the ship captain
- Ah, ship captain
- I'm the ship captain
[Flower viewing or Fireworks]
Just choose the one you like
Ready, go
Both: Fireworks
- Fireworks?
- Fireworks
[Sunrise or Sunset]
Both: Sunrise
Hey hey hey seriously?
I thought you'd say sunset
Really? It's sunr- No, but normally people would say sunset
- Right
- But I like the morning
I also like the morning. I like that
- I like the feeling of it about to start
- Right x5
[Which world do you wanna go to?
Harry Potter or Pirates of the Caribbean]
There's only one choice for me
Then I can just match his answer
Just say whichever you actually prefer
No seriously, I want neither
Neither, huh
Ready, go
Both: Harry Potter
[Tea or Juice]
No for me this is...
Ready, go
Both: Tea
- It's tea
- Definitely tea
Juice isn't great for the throat
(T/N: in JP the term 'juice' includes soda etc. as well)
[Aquarium or Zoo]
[Agonize]
It's really a 50:50 for me
Wait a minute...ok I've decided
- For me this is...
- I've decided x3
[Serious]
Let's do it. Ready, go
[Perfectly in sync]
Both: Aquarium
[Outstanding Chemistry]
- Gross! | - Why?
It's crazy we've come this far
I really like animals but
But in the aquarium it's also animals
Well, that's right
I like the animals of the sea
I like to eat them, I also like to look at them
[Run or Swim]
This is an easy one
Wait no we don't know yet
We don't know, but I've decided
Ready, go
Both: Swim
[Long history of swimming]
We both did swimming
[Decide the words written on the first page of the other member's autobiography]
You can go first, I'll write it down
I'll start
'UUUUUNNNNNNN'
In brackets, 'UUUUUNNNNNNN'
- In brackets?
- Yeah
- Do you have a reason?
- Because you always say it
Because I always say it
That's what Shion is made of
- Thank you
- Yeah
'In my past life, I was god...'
'Blah blah...'
'In my past life, I was god, blah blah...'
It starts with that
- Like a story, yeah?
- Yes
[Finally, strike a pose]
Hands and legs, the opposite
'God is in the details'
I got it correct, right?
Yeah x3
I think this these words are amazing and suit Ren-kun
He gets everything done, up to the finest details
How should I say it...I think it suits Ren-kun, so I chose it
'Overcoming'
After becoming JO1, he has talked to me about various worries
He worries, but overcomes it. I often see that sight
So Shosei's first page is 'Overcoming'
[Finally, strike a pose]
'I am Keigo'
With that...rather than a book...
It's a picture book!
It's a picture book that little kids would read
What would Takumi's be...
'10 promises to fulfil my dream'
[Satisfied]
It's great!
- It kinda fits?
- It fits
On the cover, Takumi is like this
Isn't that a little lame?
That kind of picture book.
A picture book Ichirou-san would publish
- Like those that benefit readers
- Right x5
[Finally, strike a pose]
Ohhhh cool
'There's only 1 important thing in life:'
'Muscles'
'Me, and the rest'
That is someone else's words
But something like that
Ah, that type
That type
Like there's only Ruki and not-Ruki
Ah I see
It's split properly
[The 2 obsessed over the chemistry test strike a pose]
If you were to give a present,
would you make it a surprise, or ask the other party
This is easy
Will this be an easy one?
It seems like the decision will split
Ready, go!
Both: Surprise!
Okay, I'll write
"Friends. Hard work'
That's great
For this guy
'Always putting all my effort, always earnest...'
'Live that way'
Isn't that for you?
- Junki-kun added himself in
- 'I live that way'
Junki-kun's mark is added in
'I live that way'
That's great
[Finally, strike a pose]
This is embarrassing