[Sanrio]
[JO1 x Sanrio]
[New Character Development Project]
- We have come to Sanrio Puroland!
[JO1 Creative Co. Marketing Department: At last, on-site training starts!]
I'm the intern Mamehara who was suddenly promoted to Unit Chief
I look forward to working with you
Why are you my superior?
Please ask our Director
Those who complain will have this reflected on their assessment
Dang~ This is super black (*exploitative)
That aside, does everyone know our purpose in coming here?
Yes, of course we know
This is our on-site training for global boys group JO1's new character development project
Whoa that is correct! You have done well!
Why are you talking down on me?
For real
- Because I'm the Unit Chief
[Unit Chief] [Regular employee]
In order to create an appealing new character
Today we will enjoy ourselves at the actual venue
Oh~
Everyone, shall we head in?
- Yes
- Let's go~
Ah!
What?
Look over there!
-It's Cinnamon-kun!
- (Hello!)
[Cinnamoroll who has come to receive the Marketing Department]
- Cinnamon-kun, come here~
- You've come to receive us
[Cinnamoroll who has come to receive the Marketing Department]
Thank you!
(I brought a letter for everyone!)
We have received a letter from Cinnamon!
(What is it?)
Thank you very much!
Then, I will read on behalf of everyone
Yes, please
To everyone from JO1 Creative Co. , welcome to Sanrio Puroland!
Today, in order to study more about our friends at Sanrio,
Please split into 2 teams and clear the mission
Mission?
P.S Look forward to our cute friends' appearances~
From Cinnamon!
Thank you!
Then, shall we first split into teams?
Okay!
[Randomly decided team split]
- Alright, now that we have split into teams
- Yes
- Shall we check our missions?
- Right
Yes
[Opening the envelopes]
My Melody & Kuromi-chan card and Kiki & Lala card
Cute
Shall we go with Kiki & Lala?
- Shall we go with that?
- Can we take Kiki & Lala?
- We have received the Kiki & Lala card
- Yay~
- We'll start by checking ours
- Yes~
This is the mission
Participate in ~Kiki & Lala~ Twinkling Tour
And challenge the "Cloud Animal Collecting Game"
And we are the My Melody & Kuromi-chan team
Yeah~
Here I go
Ride "My Melody Road Drive"
And count the number of My Melody & Kuromi appearances
Cinnamon, leave it to us!
(Do your best!)
With that, shall we start the mission we received from Cinnamon?
Yes~
Let's Cinnamon~
- See you later
- Let's both do our best
- Byebee~
- Off we go!
- Thank you Cinnamon!
- See you, Cinnamon
We're off!
(Have lots of fun! ♥)
We have arrived!
In anything, understanding is important
I see!
So first, we will understand from experiencing
Yes
As expected of Director
Thank you
Without any further ado, let's head in!
Let's go!
This is amazing
Mysterious
- They're clouds!
[Arrived at ~Kiki & Lala~ Twinkling Tour]
It's soft
Young kids can enjoy this plenty as well
Wow!
This is fun
Yeah
- Newbie
- Oh you're quite fast!
[A giraffe is made!]
Isn't this a big win?
- Giraffe = big win?
- There's no big win
- Keigo-kun!
- Keigo!
- It's this!
- It's cute!
Ah, look, it's a big win
[There's a giraffe by the side too!]
- Okay, say cheese
[Photo time with giraffe!]
Don't touch the Director's butt!
Ah, sorry
He kept touching it
Here I go!
Oh yeah Kiki & Lala
Cheese
[Shot with Kiki & Lala & Ruki]
Pardon the intrusion~
It has become a house
Please excuse us~
Over here, please
They are taking a bath
Wah! Cute!
- That's really cute
[Scrubbing]
Here I go, cheese
Lala's is a vacant seat
Waiting for Lala
(I'm waiting)
[Title: Waiting for Lala]
Employees
- We would like to have a showdown with this
[Let's challenge Cloud Animal Collecting Game]
[3:3 showdown! When you touch the stars on the screen
they turn into animals! Collect many cloud animals within the time limit!]
- Leave the middle to me!
- Okok
[Properly split the roles]
Yes yes yes yes
[Collecting animals by dancing]
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
- Shion, are you catching them properly?
- I am I am
[Their result is?]
Isn't it our win?
[Collected them all!]
Yay! We got them all!
- What about us?
[Their result is?]
- Isn't this amazing?
We saved them all
[Collected them all!]
[Both teams have the same score]
- Send one representative to battle 1:1
- Ah good idea
For us, we have Shiroiwa Ruki doing it
Let's go, Shiroiwa Ruki
- For us, Kono Junki
- Go, Kono Junki!
Collect them all
Too near!
Please dance properly
[This is not a dance battle...]
OH NO!!
Go go! You're doing it!
[A serious match! Who is the victor?]
- Got them all
- ALL??
- Isn't ours a little less?
- We can do it
Ah, there's no giraffe!
[Kono's result is 27 animals]
[Final result: Ruki-Keigo-Shion's victory!]
- We lost~
[Regardless of result, Kiki & Lala team had lots of fun]
I'm sorry
We have arrived
It's "My Melody Road Drive"
Our mission is this ride this
And during the attraction, My Melody-chan & Kuromi-chan will appear
The mission is to count the number of times they appear
Let's split into the people who will count My Melody-chan
And the people who will count Kuromi-chan
To cooperate to clear the mission
Yes
Is there anyone who would like to count My Melody-chan?
Then I will count My Melody
Oh, with Takumi
My Melody-chan
Are  you My Melody-chan?
I'm not My Melody-chan
You're not My Melody-chan
We will be in charge of My Melody-chan
- Then, from here...
- Perfectly
We'll be in charge of Kuromi-chan
I'm a little worried, will you be okay?
We'll be fine
- We will count properly
- I got it
While praying for a successful mission, first of all, let's have fun!
- Yes!
- Let's go!
Then, we're off!
- Here we go
- Wow!
Off we go!
Do your best!
[My Melody Road Drive Departs]
Wow! We are turning the corner with a bold drift
Is that Kuromi-chan? Hm? Or is it not?
Ah, Kuromi-chan!
Is that Kuromi-chan?
[Kuromi-chan takes a commemoration photo]
Whoa what is it?
What is it?
- This is amazing
[My Melody's house]
Eh? There's a bed
Ah? When she was a child?
It's Kuromi-chan!
[Discovering the next Kuromi-chans]
- Was that the 3rd?
- It's the 3rd, isn't it?
Wow!
Find it find it!
[Speed UP]
Kuromi-chaaaaan~~
KUROMI-CHAAAAAAAAAN!!!!!
- There's really none
[Kuromi-chan where are you...?]
- Isn't that her?
[Kuromi-chan found!]
[Finally, a commemoration photo with everyone]
We're back
Kuromi-chan!
It's Kuromi-chan
Did they manage to count it?
Was it ok?
That was fun!
[On the other hand,
How is Kiki & Lala Team who have finished their mission doing?]
[We want to play more]
He's playing a game (lol)
Badtz-Maru-kun
You've come!
- (Hey everyone~!)
- Badtz-Maru-kun
Huh?
Badtz-Maru-kun?
They're the same
- They're the same!
[Exactly alike]
They look so alike
- Badtz-Maru-kun is cool
- I want to take a picture
That's right, Badtz-Maru-kun, can we take a photo together?
(Sure! Let's take it together)
Yay!
Then, Badtz-Maru-kun, please hold the polaroid camera...
Cheese
- You're here!
[After photo-taking, they enjoyed themselves with Badtz-Maru]
- I want it! - Cute!
It's a police bike
Badtz-Maru-kun, let's play again! Thank you!
Bye bye! Thank you!
Bye bye~
Thank you~
Cute~
HURRY UP AND GO!
I'm sorry
Bye! Thank you!
[Badtz-Maru-kun, thank you for coming!]
Then we would like to ride as well
[My Melody Team departs]
- Have a safe trip~
- Off we go
Have fun
Off we go~
This is fun!
This is already fun
My Melody!
[My Melody Discovered]
This is still the first, right?
[Getting along shot]
Wow! Scary~
2!
Cute!
This is fun
Look at everything! Here as well!
Ah sorry I wasn't looking
What are you doing!
Eh? Is this okay?
Can we count these too?
[My Melody's family appear]
3...?
[Confusion]
[What should we do]
Wait
Ah Takumi-kun!
- 4! - (nope~)
[Those with only a face are not counted]
- What should we do about these?
[<- My Melody in a swaddle]
What should we do
5?
4?
Oh no
- 5, right?
- 5
- Wait a minute
- Isn't this difficult?
Do wearables count?
Is that?
7!
8!
[Final shot with everyone]
That was interesting
- There were too many feints
[Mission from Cinnamon completed!]
Welcome back
- Good work
- That was fun
- We did it
- You did it?
Amazing
First of all, it's fun
- It's fun!
[Both teams who enjoyed the mission plenty]
It was really fun
By the way, how was the mission?
It was quite difficult
- But we think we should have got it
[Full of confidence]
Doing our best
What about you? Could you do it?
It was no sweat
Doing our best
We have 3 people to check
- Yes
- 3-person
We have more members
That's strong
- Then, starting from Kuromi-team
[Result announcement!]
Here we go
Ready go
Yes, it's 6
We met 6 Kuromi-chan
Was there so many?
Yes
There was so many
We worked hard
I was only looking at My Melody
I didn't think there was so many Kuromi-chan
By the way, how many My Melody did you meet?
Here we go
Ready go
- 9 - 8
8. I'm sorry
It's 8
It's 8 My Melody
- 8 My Melody-chan & 6 Kuromi-chan
[The correct answer is?]
[Kuromi appeared 6 times - Mission clear!]
[My Melody appeared 7 times - close!]
[And here...!]
Everyone! Have a look at that!
- Wah! It's the real deal!
[Kuromi-chan makes a special appearance bringing a present]
Wow!
- Kuromi-chan~
- Cute!
She's holding something
We have received a present from Kuromi-chan
What is this?
Shall we have a look inside?
- Cute! - Wow!
[The present is the commemoration photos taken on the attraction]
- It's the photos we took inside
Kuromi-chan has delivered them to us
Thank you!
It's cute! Thank you!
These photos are good too
But since Kuromi-chan came all the way here
We want to take a picture WITH Kuromi-chan too
- That's right, I want to
- I want to!
Hey, newbie! Grab the camera
Roger!
Thank you!
See you! Bye bye! Thank you!
It's cute! The way she says bye bye
Bye bye! Thank you!
- This is cute
[After the mission the team comes to view souvenirs]
- Wow!
- This space is huge!
[After the mission the team comes to view souvenirs]
- Cute
- It's sparkling
[After the mission the team comes to view souvenirs]
- It's vast and stunning
I'd want everything
- There are many amazing products
- Yes
Now, we'll look around and buy our own items home
Okay!
Then...
- Cute!
[The one that caught Ohira's eye is...]
- Shosei is there one you like?
[Headbands]
I love Purin-kun so maybe I'll go with Purin-kun~
Is one enough?
How many can you wear?
I only have one head, so...
Oh, only one
[Before gathering, My Melody & Kuromi Team buy headbands for everyone]
Everyone, good work on the mission!
Did everyone undergo on-site training properly?
Of course
We had fun
It was incredibly enriching
How was it for you?
Deputy Director, please
We went on a My Melody Road Drive
- Drive?
- (Vroom vroom)
My Melody Road Drive
That's some abrupt steering, are you okay?
We went hard with the drifts
The mission was a little difficult
But without a doubt, we had fun!
Wonderful
- Everyone, since we've finished our training
[Ohira's suggestion!]
I'm thinking everyone must be getting hungry
So I got my friend to prepare food for us
[Yay!]
You're really thoughtful!
That's great
Let's call 'Purin-kun' to get him to come
- Okay!
- Purin-kun
Here we go
Okay
Ready...go
Purin-kun~
[Welcome Purin]
I missed you!
Fantastic
Is Purin-kun going to prepare meals for us?
- That's right, Purin-kun prepared it for us!
- (That's right)
Thank you!
Today he's the head chef
Is it all pudding dishes?
All..!?
No no no
He's shaking a little
You can really tell
He was doing this
- Cute
- (I'll guide you!)
It seems like Purin-kun will show us the way
Please~
[Come this way!]
Let's go
Shall we go?
- Wow! - Looks yummy
[These are the dishes Purin-kun prepared for us!]
Amazing! Thank you!
Were all of these prepared by Purin-kun?
(That's right!)
- Thank you!
[Happy]
This makes us happy
Ah, it seems that Purin-kun has the next order to make...
- So busy!
- Do your best~
Thank you for preparing these for us
Thank you! Bye bye!
- See you
- Do your best for the next order
Bye bye~
So fast!
Cuuute~
Let's say our thanks, including our gratefulness towards Purin-kun!
Okay
Thank you for the meal!
- My Melody Curry
[Flower My Melody Fried Prawn Pink Curry]
A huge mouthful
Yummy!
- Is it the sweet type?
- This is delicious!
It's the sweet type
Delicious curry
As expected of Purin-kun
Then I will try Purin-kun's curry
[Tiger☆Purin's Chicken Katsu Curry]
Itadakimasu
For Purin-kun
Yummy!
Then, shall I go for the ramen?
[A classic! Kitty soy sauce ramen]
Ramen is definitely gonna be delicious
Yummy
[Director & Deputy Director's Mukbang]
Yum!
- Delicious, right?
- Delicious
[Character Daifuku]
This is a custard mochi
[Kawanishi takes a bite too]
And this heart too...
That looks yummy
Takumi, is it good?
[Expressing the deliciousness by actions]
From that expression, it must be good
It's good?
(Yeah!)
[Everyone ate Purin-kun's dishes deliciously!]
We will bring the excitement we got from today back to the office
And next time we will finally decide on a concrete concept for the new character
I see
That's great
Yes
[Suddenly?] That has been Unit Chief, Mamehara
Why are you still directing this till the end?!
(Hehe)
[Next episode preview]
- We would like to decide the overall feel & concept
[JO1 Creative Co. who has felt all sorts of things from the on-site training]
- Yes
- What about the bond between the characters?
[JO1 Creative Co. who has felt all sorts of things from the on-site training]
- I see! - Great!
[Finally, the actual new character development starts!]
- Any more? Throw out your ideas
- For JO1 to see their dreams with JAM...
[In the end, what is the concept of the next character
suggested by JO1 Creative Co.?]
- Let's do our best!
[Look forward to the next episode!]
[Translation & timing by @cshinjam]