[Sanrio]
[JO1 x Sanrio]
[New Character Development Project]
[Previously at Sanrio Puroland on-site training]
[JO1 Creative Co. who deepened their knowledge
in order to develop a new character]
[Based on knowledge gained from Puroland.
What will they be doing today?]
We learnt about the exciting fun & entertainment from last week's on-site training
Yes
Kono-kun, what left an impression on you?
There were many cute characters, right?
There were
We were really healed by their presence
They were cute
Does anyone else have any impressions?
- Then me - Yes
[Active new employee]
Cute characters being a given...
But they wore all sorts of different clothes
True!
[Chef Purin-kun] [Fashionista Badtz-maru-kun]
That's something to enjoy
[Focus on characters' various clothing]
So something like choosing your favorite clothes of your favorite character
You noticed a good point
I think we've learnt various things
So this time, we'd like to make use of what we learnt
Today, before we get to the specific plan of the character
We want to decide to overall vibe and concept
I see
Is there anyone who has questions?
- Yes - Oh
How can someone who hasn't even entered the company become a unit chief?
Well, he gave us a wonderful presentation last time
I would like everyone to have a look at this
Everyone is handsome!
- Intern! - Wow!
That's true, but...
[New employee Kimata who is dissatisfied with being overtaken]
The company focuses on performance
To be promoted, you have to perform well
Please perform well
So everyone, please come forward, please put out many ideas
So if we say something amazing here, we may get promoted
- That's right! - Okay!
Go
Please put out your thoughts and feelings
[New character concept meeting starts]
Yes
Tell it to them!
It's that...!
What is it?
[Expectant]
(Thinking)
It's nothing
That's because you haven't written anything!
You haven't written anything here
[Blank]
Yes!
Oh, Kono-kun
Puroland was vivid with their use of various colors
So for our(?) character as well...
Our...?
- The character we are thinking for JO1
(Shifty eyes)
The character we are thinking up
- JO1 character
[Kono Section Chief who cannot keep up with the world view]
Should also use cute colors
I want to make the colors vivid
Colorfully
Vivid and colorful
As expected of senpai~
- Yes!
- Yes, Ohira-kun?
I like a soft feeling like Purin-kun & Cinnamon-kun
- That's important!
- You get it~
I think a soft image should be the motif!
Can I touch it?
It's soft, isn't it?
Yeah it's soft
Is there anything else?
I think it would be good if there's a bond between the characters
[Extreme stage fright ^_^;]
[Just like JO1, the characters bond is also important!]
Why is only that word enlarged?
Because the bond is important
Does Sato-san have any ideas?
Right..!
For JO1 and JAMs to see their dreams together...
Uhh...
What are you looking at?
See it and...!
No, I'm kinda...
...Tired
[Eyes suddenly tired?]
Can you present to the director properly?
Where have you been looking at since just now?
Yes...ummm...
Please excuse me
[Sato's tired eyes not really recovering]
For JO1 and JAMs to see their dreams together...
A design that cheers one up from looking at it
That's important
- Then, may I?
- Yes yes
Just like Sanrio characters,
A character that allows people to get along just by being there
That's important. Really good
Like for JAM & JO1 to be closer?
- I see
- That's great
Like being able to hold hands
Then, it's to feel closer
- Can you write faster? - Sorry!
[Re-writing to make it easier to see]
You're not very useful
Yeah, do your best
And 'when it's with everyone, everyone can get along'
'Get along'
Continue putting out more ideas
Are there any more?
How is it?
Ummm
11 people...
- You've only been writing
[Shiroiwa Secretary who has only been writing]
Then, does Shiroiwa-kun have anything?
The 11 of them, not by addition but by multiplication,
The image of extending infinite power
I see
Infinite
In other words...
In other words..?
[Expectant]
[The result it...?]
There's nothing
Nothing came out
Is the calculation too difficult?
Right
How about our Unit Chief Mame-kun?
You haven't spoken at all, are you ok?
Right...
It's to be a loved character after all, right?
- Wonderful
[Aiming to be a character loved by everyone]
'A loved character'
It would be great if we could make it into merch too
True
JO1-san has member colors
That's right
They have member colors?
It may be good to make use of it too
I see, that's good
Yes! May I?
Go ahead
We should make use of each members' individuality
To think up of a character
Ahh~ good one
- May I?
- Yes
Keigo-san just mentioned
Individuality
JO1 members' individuality is strong
It's strong indeed
To make full use of their individuality is wonderful
But using their individuality too much may cause an eccentric character
Isn't it better to emphasize on cuteness?
Cuteness-
While maintaining its cuteness
We add their individuality
For everyone to say it is cute
That's great
Yes
Does anyone have anything else?
Something that you feel 'I want to add this in'
What about Kawanishi-kun? Do you have anything?
- After all...
- After all?
Cute...right? They were cute
They were really cute
Hence
[What does it mean?]
What does it mean?
It means 'Having fun together forever', doesn't it?
That's right
JO1 & JAMs walk together with the character forever
This is it
Wonderful
We came up with plenty
This should be sufficient
[A meaningful meeting that produced many ideas]
[Vivid & colorful, Soft, Bond, Closer, Get along, Energy!]
[Merchandisable, Member colour, cuteness & individuality, Lovable, Fun together, Forever]
Referencing the ideas collected from everyone
Shall we decide on the new character's concept?
Let's!
Based on this, We can understand that JO1 is a group that can give dreams to people
And they are nourished by the support of many people to carry out their activities
Looking at the same dream, aiming for the TOP together
Making 'aiming for the TOP' the big theme, what do you guys think?
- Wonderful!
- As expected of Director!
The best!
Let's do our best!
[New Character concept decision]
[GO to the next step!]
- First, this person. JO1's leader, full of individuality
[To reference for each character design,
presenting the survey received in advance from JO1 members]
- His characteristics are kinda amazing
[To reference for each character design,
presenting the survey received in advance from JO1 members]
[Based on the meetings up till now, finally creating the draft!]
[In the end, what draft will be created?]
[Look forward to the next episode!]
[Translation & timing by @cshinjam]