[Sanrio]
[JO1 x Sanrio]
[New Character Development Project]
JO1 x Sanrio New Character Development Project
Finally, the lovable 11 friends, JOCHUM has been born!
Thank you very much
[We've been waiting]
Thanks to Sanrio!
We'll introduce the new characters once again
Yes
[YA-NU-KA-MI | MAMEchi | POP-POH]
[RURU | moco | Bira]
[CHIMATA | micoon | CHULALA]
[PiHAi | RAIN]
Through the Puroland training last time,
"Combining the feelings of love between JO1 & JAMs,
Looking at the same dream, Aiming for the top together"
Is the grand theme we are centering on
This time, we'll think of how to develop JOCHUM
And the means for JOCHUM to reach the people
Yes!
With that, the 11 characters of JOCHUM are complete but
If there's something you'd like to do from now on
Or something new you'd like to try out
- We'd like to hear your thoughts on it
- I see
- Let's see...
- Yes
- Yes Kono-kun?
A collab with their great senpai Cinnamoroll-san
That's true, he's a great senpai
If there was a sight of JOCHUM with a great senpai playing together
I think it would be fantastic for us
It would look charming
Having everyone watch them dancing and singing together
That would be wonderful
Any others?
Yes
It's quite big-scaled...
That's fine, it's fine to dream big
What about a mini anime
- That's a good one
- I want to make a short story anime with everyone
I see! Wonderful
- That' a good one
[Kimata nice idea]
Ideas like that are fine too
And we'll have JO1 members do the voices of JOCHUM
Ohh!
That's refreshing
- Wonderful
[As expected of Deputy Director]
Yes, Tsurubo-kun?
Everyone will become their character...and dance
[Dancing JOCHUM!]
That's a good one!
11 characters x 11 members collab would be interesting too
True, that's a good one
Having a performance with many people
[GOOD JOB Employee Tsurubo, Unit Chief Mamehara]
Speaking of performance, a Music Video and such is a given too
That's good
- That's cute
- Wonderful
Shall we do a CM?
'Shall we' LOL
Let's do a CM
We want it to reach youngsters too after all
So what about a LINE stamp?
- Good one!
- That would be used a lot
There are 11 characters
I think we could do a stamp that matches each character
- That's true
- It'll be cute
It's easy to use as well
And there are 11 characters in JOCHUM and they have strong personalities
So what about doing a POP UP?
A café would be good too, right?
Since there are food-lovers too
I wish for more and more young people to know of these characters
Are there any other ideas?
What about goods?
That's good
Plushies?
[JOCHUM Plushies]
That's important
That is decided!
- It's decided?
[Adopted]
- It's cute isn't it?
- We'll adopt that idea
Wonderful...that's right
We'd want to collect them all and display them (plushies)
Goods are good too but
The direction of the characters and what demographic you want the character to be known by
If there are any ideas, please
Yes!
- Sato-kun
- I'm Sato
First of all, to be known by JAMs
And people who love Sanrio characters, we want many people to know JOCHUM
And since we (JO1) will Go to the TOP
We want to be active all over the world
Yes!
So I want to take JOCHUM to the world
To raise up together
[Grand but wonderful dream]
Wonderful
And Sanrio-san has Sanrio Character Rankings every year
Just for JOCHUM to enter the ranks
The rankings eh?
Sanrio's fans, as well as our (JO1) fans
I want them to be known and loved by various people
[Unanimous goal]
Wonderful
That's good, since there's a challenge as well
Right, we'd like them to enter (the ranks) right?
We would be happy too
- Thank you very much
[It was a meeting filled with love towards JOCHUM from JO1 Creative Co. ♥]
We have decided on the dream & vision, so now we'd like to ideate for the goods
Yes
Using the materials in front of you freely, let's create some original goods
Yes!
Let's go
[Employees of JO1 Creative Co. silently creating JOCHUM goods]
Cutting...
Drawing...
Thinking...
[While thinking of the future of JOCHUM that was discussed during the meeting]
[Putting their heart into each and every one...]
[What kind of goods will be made?]
This is that...
[Employee Shiroiwa who is done right away]
Badge
Oh? How is it?
JOCHUM Badge
That's cute
This is easy to attach anywhere
Like on a bag
Walking around with this, the time together with JOCHUM would increase
I'm done too
- Oh? Please
[What kind of goods did Section Chief Kono make...?]
Please show it to us
Keychain
Cute!
That's nice
A plushies keychain of that size would be good too
- Ah! A smallish one right?
- Yes
That's true
This can be attached anywhere, like on a bag
It could be attached on a makeup pouch too
Something that can be brought around may be good
Looking at the opinions (of JAMs from twitter), plushie is quite popular
It's as expected
90% of them...
Ah that many?
Yes, they checked the box
Let's churn out more and more
Yes
I'm done
Socks
That's nice
And at the ankle is the JOCHUM character
and the message 'let's walk together'
Wonderful
Cute!
[Employee Kawanishi who thought of these socks is cute]
[Employees of JO1 Creative Co. with non-stop ideas]
I made a iPhone case
But it's not a case...it's a...what do you call it?
Stick on?
The one that you hold between your fingers
[Do you get it?]
The one that goes like this!
The one that protrudes out
What is that called?
Smartphone ring!
I also made a smartphone accessory
I made an iPhone case
Wonderful
Something like this, it's cute right?
JOCHUM will fulfil their dreams together so...
A friendship bracelet
Wonderful
The word JOCHUM is written
- Here!
- Yes, Tsurubo-kun?
It's this
What is it?
About 30cm, made of plastic, a light holding an alarm clock
[A novel idea]
Awesome!
The actual character lights up
And there's an alarm clock
He's holding the alarm clock like a pillow
And there is one for each character
[A functional product that makes it fun to wake up early]
It's cute
That's good
[JO1 Creative Co. comes up with various goods ideas]
- Are there other ideas?
[What kind of idea will come up next?]
- I'm thinking now
[Serious]
I have one!
Oh? Please
Toothbrush (for kids)
Toothbrush
12 designs of toothbrush
[Each character + group ver.]
Wonderful
And the toothpaste has a few flavors
Ah I see, though there are 12 toothbrush designs
Wonderful
Mamehara-san, how is it?
Mamehara-san is cutting a lot of things
Here I go
[Last spurt while being watched over by everyone]
Please wait a second...
Like this...
What about a pass holder?
- Cute!
- Pass holder is good
Isn't that fantastic?
I think both students and working adults can use it
Wonderful. Both students and working adults can use it
[Other cute goods were created as well!]
Everyone has great goods ideas
We are looking forward to the completed goods
- Yes!
[Excited]
We're really looking forward to it
In what way *our* goods will be...ah sorry...
OUR?
Looking forward to how JOCHUM's goods will turn out
That's right
We'll like to propose these goods ideas to the team in-charge!
Yes!
Let's meet next time at the Sample Meeting!~
[Translation & Timing by @cshinjam]