[Sanrio]
[JO1 x Sanrio]
[New Character Development Project]
[This is JO1 Creative Company: Marketing Department]
[In order to satisfy the clients today,]
[The employees are working their hardest]
Senpai, senpai, how do you do this?
You don't know how to do this?
Deputy director
I have completed the documents you asked me to handle last week
Oh!
- Please give them a check
- Thanks
Yes
[Deputy Director: Kawashiri Ren]
You made a mistake again
Do it over
I'm sorry. I'll check it again
[Employee: Sato Keigo]
Yes, I understand. Yes
I look forward to working with you
I'll call you again
Yes, yes...
[Global JO1 Creative Company - Handling calls from overseas]
[Employee: Kinjo Sukai]
This here is an especially important person
It's best if you set this as a core target
Ohhhh I see!
- Do you understand? Can you handle it?
- As expected (of a senior)!
[Employee: Ohira Shosei]
[Intern: Mamehara Issei]
Senpai!
- Then that's good
- I see!
Yes
[New employee: Tsurubo Shion]
[New employee: Kimata Syoya]
Ehhhh wait a minute....
Where did I save it to again?
Takumi
What are you doing this weekend?
Wanna play basketball?
[Employee: Kawanishi Takumi]
[Employee: Shiroiwa Ruki]
Oh, sounds good
Yeah
Then, the loser has to treat the other to 1 week of lunch?
Ohh, sounds good
Let's go, let's go
Good morning, everyone
- Good morning
[Director: Yonashiro Sho]
Good morning~
Director, good morning
Morning
[Section Chief: Kono Junki]
[JO1 Creative Company - The agenda of today's meeting is...?]
Today! We have gathered here because...
Yes!
- Our JO1 Creative Company...
- Heave-ho!
- Marketing Department...
- Here we go!
Has received a new request!
- I see
[What is the new request for the Marketing Department?]
Have a look over here
(Click)
- Ho ho ho
- I see
"Planning to make JAMs feel even closer"
- Actually...!
- Yes?
That global go-
Director!
Director, what happened to you!
Ahem
That global boys group JO1
Requested for us to devise a plan for JAM to feel even closer to them
EHHHH JO1?!?! FOR REAL?!?
That's amazing
Did that kid just say 'for real'? He's a new employee, isn't he?
Is this for real?
Are you our new employee Tsurubo-kun?
- Is this for real?
- I apologize
I'm the director here
I will give him a stern warning
Ahh~ Sorryz~
Please teach him to mind his language, seriously
But Director, it's our corporate culture to be able to speak our opinions freely
- That's right
- That's right...I forgot
- Then, how about we ask everyone for their opinions?
[Let's ask everyone for their ideas regarding this request!]
Yes!
Oh! Please
Oh, Kawanishi-kun
Yes!
Speaking of JO1, there's a member called Sato Keigo
- Ohhh, yes there is
(There is)
Speaking of Sato Keigo, he's the number one fashionista
- He's amazing
[Touched]
- That's what I think
[That's right]
Hence, "Sato Keigo's Fashion Check"...How about it?
[Kawanishi's idea - Leave JAM's fashion coordination to JO1!]
Isn't that great?
- JAM's fashion...
- That's great
Eh? He is THAT handsome?
- He never said that
- Didn't you say that?
- He didn't
- I'm talking about fashion
Ah! His fashion!
His face is handsome, and his fashion sense is also (good)
[Ohira is a KEIGO fan?]
Then, what about this?
Making food for all JAM in Tokyo Dome?
[Scaled-up in one shot]
That's quite something
You made a huge step
Then, what about playing dodgeball with all JAMs?
That's epic too
- (Good one)
- JO1 is good at it
Something like this?
Those are not bad ideas, but...
This is a plan for JAMs as a whole to feel close to JO1
[We want a feasible idea]
I see
Close...close...
[When good ideas just don't come to mind...]
Yes!
- Oh?
- Yes?
Yes!
- Oh?
- Yes?
In that case...
We ought to make a character that's the embodiment of JO1
You've got brains
Wonderful
Speaking of characters...the one who makes characters loved globally
Isn't it Sanrio-san?
I see!
This is the only option
[Click clack]
[Sa...n...ri...o...]
That's it
Speaking of Sanrio, there's also my beloved Purin-kun
- How much have you collected...?!
[Since when?! Ohira's desk overflowing with Pompompurin]
Pom-activity
What is Pom-activity??
No...right now we're talking about a collaboration with JO1...!
With Purin-kun around, we don't really need a JO1 character
- We need it!
- Ah, we need it?
- Yes!
- I'm sorry
Yes!
Yes, Kono-kun
How about we ask Cinnamon for advice?
[Since when?!]
- Ohh - Yes
[As expected of Section Chief]
Cinnamon actually...
In 2021, won 1st place in the Character Awards two years in a row
- A superstar!
[Glittering Cinnamoroll's award history]
- Ohh
[Kono's idea: Ask superstar Cinnamon for advice]
- Look at him
That is good too
But the recent trend is artists
My attention is on...
[What is it?]
Beatcats
♫ My secret side I don't show to anyone ♫
Don't sing!
Sorry~
If I was reborn
I want to become Gudetama
Ohhh
- Please guys...we're talking about JO1
[Calm down]
Can someone talk about JO1!
- Yes!
- Oh!
Kawanishi-kun, I'm counting on you
Leave it to me
Speaking of JO1...
Singing, Dancing, Visuals
Oh
Everything is perfect
- True...!
- That is the case, right?
This is exactly what I've been waiting for @#&%
If we think of a character with all these factors combined...!
Oh!
It's Kitty-chan, isn't it?
What do you mean? Please explain
Kitty-chan is super popular, from kids to adults
As well as with overseas celebrities
Kitty-chan who is loved by everyone
That's it
Takumi-san, you're cute today as well
Ah, thank you (shy)
[Hello Kitty is good too but]
- Don't forget about Gudetama
Pompompurin for the win!
It's Beatcats!
It's Cinnamon
It's Gudetama
Be quiet!!!
♫ I don't show to anyone ♫
Shhh
What are we talking about?
For crying out loud
We've been saying that we're making JO1's new character, right?
Well, well, director...
Please calm down
Seniors!
I've been listening, and you've been speaking off-the-mark...right?
You are the intern, Mamehara-kun?
In the first place, everyone...
Do you even know JO1 well?
JO1?
No...actually we don't really know...
I thought so
Director doesn't know either?
You don't know, do you?
My apologies
Well then everyone
Let's have a look at this
[Let's look at the video prepared by intern Mamehara]
Cool~
The white-haired guy is good at dancing
It's cute~
It's refreshing
Wow
Everyone is handsome
Yeah
- What was that?
- The vibe has changed
This kid seems good at singing
I see. Ahh it's cool
Isn't that guy the coolest?
Yeah, he's the coolest
He's the coolest
Doesn't he look a little like Kawanishi-kun?
[Like twins, identical]
He looks like you a little
I see!
[Before making the new character,
the Marketing Dept first has to learn properly about JO1]
Everyone, please watch and learn from this properly
Yes! I will learn from this!
Isn't the intern the most solid one here?
Intern, you did well
We want to make a JO1 character with Sanrio-san
Next time, how about we all go to Sanrio Puroland for an on-site training?
That's wonderful
That's a good idea!
Can we simply go for a on-site training like that?
Rest assured, everyone
I know Cinnamon's contact
[Really?]
So I will make an appointment now
Did you say Cinnamon???
No, no, that's impossible!
Ah
Hello?
Cinnamon?
Are you serious?
Does Cinnamon have a smartphone?
Hello! Cinnamon-san?
You collaborated with JO1 for a dance, right?
- Oh, that's right!
- That's true, I recall there was something like that
They really know each other!
We would like to make JO1's character in collaboration with Sanrio-san
Oh?
Oh!
You'll talk to a higher-up for us?
[Really?]
Then, can you ask them?
[Nervous]
They said they'll be happy to cooperate for JO1!
[Unbelievable]
"They'll be happy to"?
- This is amazing
- Thank you
Next time, we'll visit Sanrio Puroland, k?
"K???"
So, we've gotten permission from the other party
- Amazing!
[Intern's great success:
JO1 x Sanrio new character project decided!]
You're an intern?
Yes, an intern. I'm Mamehara
Your employment has been decided
Ohh thank you very much!
Congrats!
- I have your employee pass
- Oh!
Have a seat
How about I give you a position as well
You'll be Unit Chief
- Wait a minute!!
[Intern -> Unit Chief]
[Super speed promotion]
- Is this ok?
- It's fine
- Thank you
- We can make use of you
[No way...]
Then next time, we'll be at Sanrio Puroland to show you our on-site training
[Smug face]
This pisses me off~
This was Unit Chief Mamehara
Wonderful!
Hey everyone, please clap
Are you for real!
We have come to Sanrio Puroland!
[Next episode preview: Finally on-site training starts]
Look at that!
[A special guest makes an appearance?!]
- This is fun
[While enjoying various attractions]
[JO1 Creative Company who learns about Sanrio!]
Takumi-kun, what should we do?
- KUROMI-CHAN!!!
[Look forward to the next episode!]
[JO1 x Sanrio New Character Development Project]
[Translation & Timing by @cshinjam]