[Sanrio]
[JO1 x Sanrio]
[New Character Development Project]
Last time, each time put together the characteristic cards, right?
Right
[The employees who split into 2 teams to fill in the opposing team's profiles]
This time, using the profiles, we will present them while checking the answers
Understood
To better understand the characters
Right
By the way, the person who presents the best will be promoted on the spot
So everyone please do your best
[Promotion?!]
- Really?
- Really
- I'll do my best
- Please do your best
Then, the presentation order...
First, Kawashiri-kun
Understood
Please
Then let's check the correct answers right away
This is Kawashiri Ren-san's character, his name is RAIN
RAIN-kun
His dream 'surprising people all over the world', this is correct
This is correct
By the way, why is his name RAIN?
There's a magic that he's best at
And that is the magic to make it rain
From that, his name is RAIN-kun
- Ta-da
- Wow
His favorite word is 'Wow!'
'Wow!'
Doing his magic, he's happy to be praised with the word 'wow!'
Continuing on, the one he's together with often is
PiHAi-kun
Kinjo Sukai-san's character, PiHAi-kun
Actually
He is PiHAi-kun's real older brother
Ehh?
- Is that so??
- There's such a setting..!
I thought they looked similar, and they're siblings
Finally, a word to JAMs
'I'll take you to a world of dreams and emotion!"
Wonderful!
- I see
- That's great
That's wonderful, as a magician, an entertainer
He's the mirror of magicians
And now let's look at the concept art prepared by Sanrio-san right away
Cute!
The bird is cute
To think there was a bird inside...!
- Wow
- Thank you very much
That was Kawashiri-san's character RAIN-kun
- Wonderful
- Thank you very much
I want to hurry up and see everyone's concept art!
Next is Shiroiwa Ruki-san's character
He's full of charm
I'll go through it quickly
First, his name is RURU
He refers to himself as RURU as well
And the dream card that everyone has chosen is correct!
[Become the king of healing for everyone]
Here, it writes that his skill is 'Kiss'
This is incorrect
What is it?
The correct answer is
'Can fall sleep anywhere right away'
Ehhh!
And the trademark phrase, it writes 'chu*' here
[T/N: kissing sound]
His trademark phrase is 'chu'?
This is also incorrect
Well it's true that it seems like it'd be correct
But it's 'I'm hungry'
Ehhh!
So it means he's a spoiled prince, is that okay?
Everyone, please treat him well
Then I'll take this off
I'll also go through this quickly
Favorite colour is white, favorite food is dessert
And he also has MY BEST Dessert ranking
#3 - Candied sweet potatoes
Is that so?
#1 - Crepe
That's sweet
And among crepe flavors, he likes ibanacho
What's that?
Ichigo(strawberry)-banana-chocolate crepe
Hehhh~
Ibanacho!
Ibaraki-cho(?)
He loves Ibanacho!
And there's a concept art so
It's totally different!
- This
- Cute~
I'd be happy if you pay attention to the back of his feet
I want him to sleep and eat a lot
That's all
- Cute!
- Wonderful!
Really cute!
Please treat me well
Then, I'll like to start right away
Are you okay? Your shoulders are a bit...loosen them
I'm sorry
Thank goodness, it's back to normal
Then, I'll like to start right away
His name is POP-POH
Like 'POP-POH-chan'
His dream 'an easy life', this is correct
- Ehhh!
- This is correct?
- 'An easy life' as a dream...
- This is correct
And...small type(?)
[T/N: They are meant to fill the blood type here]
That's true!
Because he's a small type, please call him POP-POH
Because he's a small type, POP-POH
And his skill
'Fighting', this is incorrect
It's wrong!
Because he wants an easy life
Because his stomach is his charm point
[Curious]
'Sleeping'
His skill is sleeping
And his trademark phrase is 'Po'
I'll go through these
Here I go!
MY BEST Ice Cream
[Strawberry, Chocolate, Mint]
A word to JAMs
Yappo~!
[In love]
His voice is quite low, Yappo
Finally, I'll like to show everyone the concept art
Please!
- So cute!
- He's winking
His special skill, winking
- Wow!
- Cute!
I'm very satisfied!
Wonderful! Thank you very much
I am the new employee, Kimata Syoya, please treat me well
His name is CHIMATA-kun, this is correct
His skill 'full-out', this is wrong
- It's wrong
- I wonder whose is this?
His skill is 'playing'
- It was 'playing'
- That's right
His trademark phrase 'I'm hungry'...this is actually wrong
It's wrong? What is it?
Actually, it's 'Why?'
'Why'- ahhh (unexpected!)
And the important part is from here on
Then, I'll open it
Favorite word 'This is a Japanese native' (???)
I don't know what he's saying ;;
If you don't know, no one else would know!
I think Kimata-san was obsessed with this
A word to JAMs...
"Hello, thank you very much. Hm? This is a Japanese native"
So that's what it was
Thank you very much
If you were that obsessed with it, then don't forget it
Right, I was really obsessed at that point in time
Shall we go to the concept art?
Then, OPEN!!
This is a Japanese native
Cute!
(He's honest)
Too cute!
- This is great
- Too cute
- Wonderful
- That was Kimata Syoya
His name is CHULALA
His dream 'Space invasion' is correct
It's correct
His trademark phrase is...'da na.' at the end of his sentences
- Ehhhh
- We were wrong
Let's continue to this
MY BEST special move
#1 - Laser from octopus
Laser from octopus?
- The (octopus) above?
- This guy
That's someone else's power
- #2 is?
- To stare
What do you mean?
Only #1 is very powerful
The one who is often together with him is this parasitic octopus
It's parasitic
Let's see the concept art
Isn't this great?
- Cute
- It's great
The laser from the eyes too, the special move
- He's also saying something, we don't understand though
- He's saying something
That's how it is, thank you very much
Then I, the Director, will present
Firstly, his name is YA-NU-KA-MI
Cool
Do you all know the meaning?
It means the God of the house
Wonderful! You are doing good
- You're good too
- Okay, please move on
I'm the Director, you know?
[I'm sorry]
And his dream is also to become a full-fledged guardian deity
- Wow!
- You're doing the presentation instead!
And his charm point is that he's typically inside this cup
And his trademark phrase is 'nankuru naru', this is correct
Let's look into the details
His favorite food is Goya Champuru
He's really pushing the Okinawan agenda!
Goya Champuru
And his MY BEST snacks
#3 - Tannafakuru
Tannafakuru
What is that?
Never heard of it
You haven't gotten your throat dry by Tannafakuru?
I don't know!
It's a famous Okinawan snack
Tannafakuru
It really gets your throat dry!
I don't understand what you're saying without subtitles!
Tannafakuru
And here's the concept art
He's laughing!
He's protecting the house in this state
That was YA-NU-KA-MI's introduction
Thank you
Then, I'll like to introduce him
His name is not FULL-OUT!!! Are you dumb?
It's not Full-out?
In the first place, there was no blank to fill here
Please don't change it
His name is micoon!
- Either (name) is good
- As you can see, he is shaped like a mic
His dream is
Brighten everyone up with his singing!
There hasn't been a single correct answer yet!
His skill is whistling
Next, is shortcoming is
There's a permanent echo on his voice
I don't really like that
It's hard to hear what he's saying
There's always an echo
His trademark phrase is not 'space invasion'!
I would hate to hear that being said with an echo
It's wrong! Finally it can come out, here...
- It's 'Full-out'
- Ah, here it is
Continuing, ta-da
His favorite place is the onsen
Is it okay for him to enter the onsen?
[He's a mic, right?]
It's okay
He will only enter alone
Because he would electrocute others!
A word to JAMs - 'Let's sing together.'
With those feelings, that was micoon
Everyone, please love him a lot!
Then, I'll like to move on to the concept art!
Please!
He's jumping!
Cute!
- That was all
- Thank you very much
Here is the profile of the character I thought of
His name is Bira
He refers to himself by 'uchi'
It's uchi
His dream 'Make everyone all over the world happy'
That is also right, but the correct answer is...
'To become JO1!'
He looks up to JO1
His skill is not 'chu'(kiss)!
It's not? But he's doing a chu (expression)
Totally wrong
It's 'kiss'
IT'S THE SAME!
His hobby is fortune telling
He can do fortune telling with his petals
With the petals? Does he pluck them himself?
He only has 11, they will be all gone
They grow back right away
His trademark phrase is not 'I will protect you'
Ehh?
It's close
It's 'chu'
What's the difference?
These two? They're totally different!
The thing he cherishes is his flower petals
But he does flower petal fortune telling though?
He cherishes them, but he does fortune telling for the people he cherishes
I see!
- Like for Keigo-kun
- Yes, he's like that
This is Bira-chan's concept art
He jumping
Thank you very much
Please treat me well
This kid's name is PiHAi
(RAIN's younger brother!)
Sukai-san's name is written by the kanji '碧海'
If you read it in Chinese, it's PiHai*
[T/N: It's actually BiHai]
- Really?
- It's really PiHai
Is that so!
Hence, I named him PiHAi-kun
- His dream 'to become a pilot'
- Is this correct?
This is actually...correct
And his strong point is 'sociable'
Even though he looks like this, unexpectedly he's sociable
But his shortcoming...
His shortcoming is 'quiet and poker-faced'
One of the two must be a lie?
Then, let's go deeper
His favorite place is the house!
He's not sociable at all though?
From what we see so far
It's like 'actually, on the inside he's sociable' (?)
A word to JAMs, 'Don't leave Pi alone'
He gets lonely easily
He has this cute side
Then, PiHAi-kun's concept art, 3, 2, 1, ta-da!
Cute!
He's cool
That's all
Thank you very much
I'd like to start now
His name is moco
- His dream 'to sleep'
- Is that right?
Wrong!
It's 'make everyone all over the world happy'
Because he's an angel
His skill 'kiss & magic' is wrong
It's not kiss magic
It's to get onto a cloud
Because he can fly
His trademark phrase 'mocomoco mocomoco po'
Wrong!
- It's wrong?!
(Culprit)
It's close
It's just 'mocomoco'
It was close
Let's continue
- This is funny
[moco party]
MY BEST moco
Here is MY BEST moco! #3!
Please start from #3
mocomoco!
Well, that's #3
#2 - moco!
[curious about #1]
#1, moco
moco
#2 and #1 are the same!
Why is #2 the one with the exclamation mark
That's all
I like moco TT
Next, the concept art please!
Cute!
- He's on a cloud
- He is, holding a heart
He's cute. Thank you very much!
Then, let's have the unit chief!
Yes!
Let's raise the energy!
His name is MAMEchi
Because he's called Mame-chan
So MAMEchi
His dream 'to protect everyone's smile' this is correct
Completely correct
His skill 'fighting' is correct
It's correct
And his trademark phrase is not 'da na.' at the end of his sentences
It's not. What is it?
It's 'I(boku) will protect you'
Because he's a hero
Please treat him well. Let's move on
But he refers to himself as 'oira'
Yes...oira..!
So it's 'I(oira) will protect you'
It's written as 'boku' but read as 'oira'!
Ahhh!
The general concept!
A hero who revolutionizes the general concept
As expected of Director, you follow up well
His favorite colour is red, he has red on him too
Food is curry...
Well...he likes delicious food the most!
Everyone likes curry after all
He's like a protagonist
A word to JAMs, 'I(boku) will protect the world & your smiles!!"
You said boku again!
Isn't it 'oira'?
The general concept...
Revolutionize the general concept
General concept hero
With that, here is the concept art!
Cute!
Just before fighting
It's cute, thank you very much
Everyone's presentation has finished
I think we have gotten a better understanding of JOCHUM
How was it?
I think we have gathered a bunch of wonderful characters that strike a good balance
Everyone's presentation was good
It's difficult to choose one person
But we'd like to decide on the employee to promote
Yes
Everyone, please wait a moment
- Everyone was good
[Gathered after the presentation]
- What do you think, Unit Chief?
[Deputy Director|Director|Unit Chief|Section Chief]
Wonderful. I think it's good
How is it?
He'll be the Supervisor
We have decided
[The person who will be promoted is?]
We'll choose this person
We have decided
We have decided on the person who will be promoted here
Director, please announce it
The member(?) who will be promoted is
Kawanishi Takumi-kun
Thank you very much!
Congratulations
The reason you were selected may already be obvious but
Based on our corporate philosophy, always 'smiling', always 'energetic', always 'full-out'
We think you meet all these 3 criteria
Congratulations
[Supervisor Kawanishi Takumi]
- This is great
- He is sharp
Thank you very much!
The full picture of all 11 characters have been revealed
Next time, for JOCHUM to be known by more people
We will like to think of the long-term dream & vision, and the development of goods etc.
Look forward to next time as well!
[Translation & Timing by @cshinjam]