[Sanrio]
[JO1 x Sanrio]
[New Character Development Project]
Hmmm everyone is taking so long...are they coming yet?
- I have something important to talk about today
[Director waiting by himself in the meeting room for JO1 Creative Co. employees]
Director! Thank you for your hard work
Good work!
I apologize for keeping you waiting...
Are you alone?
- No, the other employees are coming too
[Only 2 people in a big meeting room...]
- Really?
- Yes
- Everyone!
- Thank you for your hard work
- Good work today
You've all finally gathered, thank you
Thank you
- Sorry for calling you all here
- No problem
Has everyone gathered?
Yes
Director!
You've gathered us here today, couuuuuld it be.....
You're sharp, Kawanishi-kun
Truly sharp!
Last time we thought up of various goods, do you remember?
Of course!
The JOCHUM goods samples have finally been completed!
That's really fast!
It's fast
I'm looking forward to seeing how the goods we proposed turned out
I want to hurry and see the completed version
Director, have you already seen it?
Well well well...
Hurry and show it to us too! Right?
We want to see it!
- WELL WELL WELL
- Hurry show it to us
Well
Calm down
SHOW IT TO US
[Mood-maker Supervisor Kawanishi's sense of humor never misses]
I'll bring over the goods samples right away
Please close your eyes and wait. I'll bring them over
- Close your eyes properly
- Okay
They're wide open
Close your eyes
I'm sorry, it was the other way around
[What kind of goods have been completed...?]
Okay! Everyone, you have your eyes closed...right?
I've brought them, so shall we open our eyes on the count of 3?
Yes
Here we go
Please open your eyes!
1...2...ta-da!
- Wow!
- Cute!
Everyone, please have a closer look
The ones in right in front of you is JOCHUM's plushies
Cute!
- Everyone, it's okay to hold the plushies
- Is it okay?
It's okay
- Yes, please pick them up
Please pick them up
Oh! It's fluffy
The details are properly included, the nose part
[Up till the fine details, they are very cute <3]
With that, let's hear your thoughts of the plushies
Then, firstly...
Ruki-kun! How is it?
At the start, I said 'please make him white and fluffy'
Yes
- The feel of him is really nice
- He's fluffy
Wow
And fluffy
And here, the name is properly...
Ah, It's written
'RUKI' is written on the pads
And he has his pacifier attached
And the crown is firmly on too
It very very cute
Adorable
Thank you very much
Then, Mamehara-kun
Can we ask your thoughts?
He's cute!
And the beans...the 2 beans are properly...
It's attached to the belt and the scarf
Look, on the back as well, the scarf is attached
- He's cute
- There's no doubt that he'd be a superhero
Yes
Cute...his face is cute
MAMEchi~
Then, Kawanishi-kun!
- Yes!
- How is it?
Omg he's...
He's just so lovely
Nyanyanya~
Stop that
- Is he as per your expectations?
- It's as per my expectations
The strawberry is also firmly...
This can't be taken off!
Oh it can't
- Because this grows from him
- It grows from him
Thank you very much
Besides the plushies, please have a look here
There's keychains
Stickers
- Ah these are stickers?
- Yes
Cute
That's right
And there's can badges too
That's nice
How is the keychain?
Cute
Really cute
- You can put it on your bag
- I want to put it on!
Junki, how's the keychain?
yours is a little small
Micoon is a little smaller after all
Cute~
We want everyone to attach it
Like on their bags etc. we would love for them to attach these
- Cute...there is everyone's
[This is Section Chief Kono & micoon's world]
- Please have a look at them later
And the can badge
Wonderful
That's cute. Everyone can attach it to their employee passes like this
Everyone please put it on right now
This is an order from your superior!!
The face is covered
That's the face
So cute
Everyone can try attaching the can badge to their employee passes
Well you can attach it onto various places
There are all character versions, please have a look later
They can be used in a cute way
Lastly, shall we look at the stickers
Sometimes I go far away on vacation
You could paste this on your suitcase
Oh that's a good one
You can go together to various place
Going for a vacation together...that's good. Wonderful
Ummm...could I get promoted?
That may be a possibility!
Thank you very much
It's not that easy you know?
Ah I'm sorry. So strict
Tsurubo-kun, how is it?
This size is good, it could be pasted on the phone
Please do paste it on your phone
Cute
Shosei-kun, how is it?
It would be cute to paste this on headphones too
Headphones!
Wonderful
A good job was done
It's wonderful
You could paste it here too
It's nice to touch too
Including all the details everyone was particular about
It has all been adopted nicely into the design
It's okay to get the characters individually, but to line up a complete set...
- That'd be awesome!
- It'll be really cute
Everyone, please try completing it
Yes
By the way, the goods isn't the only thing that has been completed!
Ehhh??
Is there something other than the goods?
Actually one more thing has been delivered by Sanrio-san
Really?
Did you also know about this, Director?
No, I didn't hear about this
Really?
Haven't you become even more remarkable than the Director?
- Well well well...
[Smug face]
For now please have a look at this video
[Enjoy JO1 Creative Co's reactions]
Apparently there's a house that if you live in it, your dreams will come true
- Cute - Wow
- CEO! - Isn't it CEO?
They look alike
Eh? He's holding some paper
His documents are...!
Cute!
They're moving! Cute
Cute~
Cute!
- Micoon~
- They're moving
Wow!
They're seriously cute
It burst!
Selfie
- He's playing guitar
- It's YA-NU-KA-MI
He's playing guitar
Guitar is cool!
Cute
He's floating?!
Shosei is flying
CUTE!!!
Seriously so cute
POP-POH-chan
POP-POH's eyes were sparkly
The paper flew to him like
It was so cute
Each character had different items, like the guitar
Junki's had a soccer ball
He was kicking the soccer ball
- Mame-chan's with the net
- He was holding a net
Wow
MAMEchi~
Shosei(moco) was flying!
He was flying just now
As expected of an angel
Amazing
Too cute
Developing them together with Sanrio-san, such cute characters of JOCHUM were born
Thank you very much
On top of that, we were able to see such a wonderful animation
Sanrio-san, thank you very much
From now on, not just JO1, but JOCHUM will be by JAMs side
And they can feel closer to them
Yes
That's right, and not just JAM, we hope they will be loved by many people
Surely they will become characters that are loved by people all over the world!
Because CHULALA is around, they will be popular in outer space too
Let's aim for outer space
And from today, this project's Twitter & Instagram official account
Will be renewed as JOCHUM's official account
And JOCHUM's official YouTube and TikTok account will also be opened today
TikTok too?
That's right
Everyone, please subscribe and follow
And look forward to how JOCHUM will spend their daily lives!
Thank you very much!
And!
And?
Actually
These JOCHUM plushies
From tomorrow, 8 November, pre-order sales will start!
Wow
The application ends on 15th November
So please check it out
Yes, please!
JOCHUM, born from JO1 x Sanrio New Character Development Project
Please treat them kindly!
Bye bye~
[Translation & Timing by @cshinjam]