[Sanrio]
[JO1 x Sanrio]
[New Character Development Project]
[Previously: JO1 Creative Co. who decided on the project's broad theme]
[This time, referencing the questionnaire received beforehand from JO1 members,
finally tackling the characters' designs!]
- While being aware of this representative theme
[Finally, to the individual design making]
We'll now work on the character making
Okay
- Actually I have requested a questionnaire to be done by JO1 members beforehand
[To understand JO1 members better, a questionnaire to know their characteristics]
You do your job well, as expected of the Unit Chief
While referencing the results of the questionnaire,
Let's make a more concrete character design
- Right
- That's great
Questionnaire...Unit Chief you sure work fast
- No no no
- You're really excellent
Thank you very much, Director
- Then, new employee Tsurubo-kun, the data please
- Yes
Here it is
- You're making use of him right away
[USB with the data]
Thank you
I'll take it
The hierarchical relationship has been clearly laid out
Wait, you're just an intern!
[Still unconvinced, employee Kimata]
The ordinary employee over there, please shut your mouth
"Ordinary employee"??
[Upset]
(There there)
This is meritocracy
I'm not convinced
Regarding the dream collab between Sanrio & JO1
We've come to the design stage
Yes
I, Mamehara, who has been promoted to Unit Chief in top speed
Have been entrusted with this questionnaire
Here it is
Oh~
Firstly
JO1's leader, full of character
Envelops the members warmly
A mother-like existence to everyone
What do you think?
Great~ He's handsome~
He's cool
His characteristics...he wrote 'airhead' himself so I wonder if he really is an airhead or not
Could he be pretending to be an airhead?
[Airhead pretense suspicion??]
But it's just 10% so it's pretty much 0%
[Yonashiro Director desperately advocating]
Is that so?
This is interesting
[sensuality 40%]
I'm curious about that
We don't really say 'sensual' about ourselves
Because this is the result of the questionnaire taken beforehand (?)
Well, he is probably confident in his sensuality
It's easy to understand
For some reason the hashtags are the same as the characteristics
I wonder what's that about
[Place to write hashtags that expresses themselves]
[Sensuality 40%, kindness 30%, manliness 20%, airhead 10%]
Did he get the questionnaire wrong?
Maybe that's where he's an airhead
Shall we move on to the next one?
Here's the next member
Poker face is his charm
Dancing a given, he's actually good at drawing too
Kinjo Sukai-san
Wonderful
- I'm curious about his habit
- Sticking his tongue out
[Curious about his habit]
What does it mean?
(Yeah yeah)
(Sticks out)
I'm curious!
- What is this?
[Another thing that piques curiosity...]
- Savings zero?
- Zero?
I'm curious about how he lives
Though his savings is zero, it writes "I can do it"
[Seems like a positive character]
It's his feelings
But after that it writes "See You"
But with the tongue sticking out, if we can make a cute character that'd be great
[Each person's questionnaire expresses their individuality]
Here's the next member
He has come!
Exceptional transparency
Everyone's prince
Shiroiwa Ruki-san
Wonderful
This guy also wrote "coolness 30%" for himself
He must be quite confident
That's right
He has confidence
By the way, what's "prince-ness"?
Isn't it 'egg-ness'?
Egg-ness??
[Egg-ness??????]
(Where)
Egg-ness(?) 20%!!
There's no dot
Ah, no dot
Wait-
- Which is it?
- It's the opposite
- Ah, it's like this
- It's the opposite!
It's prince-ness
Perhaps it's a sparkly character
Prince
Isn't it good?
[Easy-to-understand characteristics!]
It's easy to understand
Next, we have this member
Here he is, JO1's youngest and beloved Mamehara Issei-san
Reliable and sharp performance
I'll continue presenting from here
Oh I see, from here on
It's Mamehara Issei-san! Reliable and sharp performance
A man who will always continue growing
Mamehara Issei
- Heave-ho!
(cute)
If you look at his face you can see he's adorable
Heave-ho~
His habit is 'heave-ho', does he do it or say it...?
Isn't it a favorite phrase?
Ah, it's a favorite phrase
I'm curious about the 'Offensive Power 50%'
It's this, he inserts this phrase to his attacks
He goes 'Heave-ho~'
I don't like that
[Heave-ho festival]
Is that an attack? (※it's not)
Isn't it a favorite phrase?
Right, well maybe a character that expresses childlike-ness would be good for him
But 'feeling of the youngest' and 'cuteness' is just 2% each
2%?
Maybe he's holding back
We don't usually say this about ourselves
Here's the next member
JO1's dance leader, Kawashiri Ren-kun
Wonderful
He 'laughs a lot' so his smile is one of his characteristics
I see
He laughs a lot and has a cute face
But his 'cleverness' is 40%, his mind is excellent
- He wrote 'clever' about himself
[He says this but...]
[※Later]
- His cuteness is 70%
Cleverness 40%
Right, and attack is 20%
Defense 15%
Agility 15%
Physical strength 10%
Seems like he's gonna fight
I feel like I've seen such stats lineup before
I wonder if he fights?
He's saying if you bring him along, he'd be useful
But he can't do anything by himself
He can't do anything by himself?
If Mamehara-san brings him along, the compatibility will be perfect
[It might make a good relationship?]
Let's move on to the next one
Next is JO1's beauty-in-charge
Purin-kun's friend, Ohira Shosei-san
Purin-kun's friend
Because he's said to be the beauty-in-charge
So his cuteness is 70%!
Wow that's strong
What are these hashtags?
[#angel #passion #love #effort
#healer level MAX #angel level MAX #god level MAX]
He's a healer class!
They're all MAX
If that's the case, write 'cuteness MAX' instead
The character's image comes to mind easily
That's right, his keyword is 'Angel'
We should make use of the kansai-ben, since it's his habit
That's right...kansai-ben
How I imagine it is fluffy floating character
- That's why it's an angel
[Agreement]
- A cute one
Next is JO1's airheaded boy, sushi-loving Kimata Syoya-san
[Airheaded boy]
His charm is nihility
- Yes (answering for some reason)
His habit is scratching his nose
Scratching his nose
That's right, he's kind of strange
Appetite is 45%
Agility 5%
He has as much as 35% for strangeness power
Earnestness 2%
Flail 13%
It's quite detailed
You can tell by looking at this but he's a little strange
He's someone with a big appetite
He also loves sleeping
His face is a little rabbit-like
We can lean towards food or towards the rabbit (for the design)
That's true
I think it'd be good
Both ways work
There are various directions to take this
- Wonderful
- Yes
Let's carry on
Next we have...
Oh my!
Who is this handsome man?
Here he is!
Then, from here on...please
[Passing the baton to Shiroiwa]
Yes
- Oh my who is this handsome man
- I already said that
He's reading straight off the script
Outstanding proportions like a model
It's Sato Keigo-san
That's all
Hey!!
There must be more!
- Let's go a little deeper
- Is there more?
I'm curious about this 'monster' here
[Monster??]
- What does it mean?
Is his face like a monster?
Shall we fire him?
- I got it wrong
[It's a joke ^^]
He's probably...a bit of a weirdo
- It's 50%
- That's right
- Because he's a weirdo so he's monster-like, maybe?
Right, right
An out of the ordinary feeling?
Someone called him a fashionista earlier, right?
He's a fashionista, he's wonderful
The best among them all
What about his face?
His face...
(Expectant)
Looks good
Somehow looks good
What do you mean by 'somehow'?
He doesn't have much peculiarity
He's a bit of a weirdo but without much peculiarity
Why do you know so much about Keigo-kun?
Um...
[What is it?]
[Curious]
We're friends
Oh you're friends!
Is that so!
I'm sorry I called him a monster
[Marketing dept. Sato is actually friends with JO1's member?!]
- I see, fantastic
[It seems we can create another character with individuality]
- I can imagine such a character
I feel we can make a good character
[Next member appears]
- Wow - Seems noisy
[Strong reaction (lol)]
He is JO1's main vocal
With a sweet singing voice, Kono Junki-san
His 'honesty' is 50%
That's a wonderful thing
He must have been born to a good family, his parents must be good people too
[PR time for some reason]
- Wow
[Satisfied]
Speed 20%
Shy 10%
Smile 10%
Brain 10%
Shiroiwa-san you're laughing a little
He gets excited but 'smile' is a low percentage
- The smile is quite little
- That's right
It writes 'energetic' but 'smile' is little
Maybe he gives energy to others
Not himself but towards others
That's right
As a character, it's easy to understand
- Yes, his profile is like this
- Wonderful
And next is...
With a sweet visual and edgy rap, Tsurubo Shion-san
Oh~ Rap
He's cute
His hashtag is 'mochi'
His 'adaptability to unreasonable behavior' is 30%
Does he have some kind of special move?
He does!
Pi~me from his brain
[T/N: it's just Shion gibberish]
THAT???
(Takumi-san <3)
You know it??
[THAT!?]
You know it?
- Wow! Pi~me from his brain?
- That's right
Seems like it's amazing
Maybe it'd be good if he adds that in
[+ special skill: pi~me from the brain]
#New sensation tough-soft BOY
Tough-soft
He's tough but he's soft
It's easy to understand(?), image-wise
It's easy to imagine
- Well it's like that
[Tsurubo-san's questionnaire ends here]
- With a catchy hashtag
'New sensation tough-soft' is funny
Lastly
National treasure ikemen Kawanishi Takumi-san
[National treasure ikemen]
(I don't know much but) That's wonderful
- That's true
- It seems like he's saying that about himself
(I don't know much but) I think it seems he didn't say it himself
- Do you know about it?
- He is told by others often
Is that so!
Maybe it's not so good to say that too
Where are you looking?
Looking above
I'm curious about the hashtag on the right
You're curious?
I'm curious about #full of sense
What is that about?
Well, he can do something maybe
He can handle things
(I don't know much but) He probably can handle things
[Putting into practice for some reason]
Like this
He can do it
How was it?
It was great
I shall reference this
He has amazing responsiveness
Well it's like this
So funny
We are done with all members' questionnaires
I see, thank you
Based on the results of the questionnaires
We'll like to think of each character design
Is everyone alright with it?
Leave it to us!
We'll do our best
Then let's get thinking!
Yes
Alright!
It's great
What should I do?
It's difficult~
Then...simple...
...but cute
And something like this is nice too
Is everyone done drawing?
Yes
Ok, then
- Tsurubo-kun
- Yes
- Collect them
- Ok, I understand
- I'll leave it to you
- Yes, excuse me
I'll leave it to you
It's heavy~
Then, I will hand these drafts to the design team
We'll leave it to you
[Next episode preview]
Excuse me!
I've brought the design roughs!
[Characters who have taken shape]
Here it is
[Characters full of individuality that could only have been created by JO1 Creative Co.!]
[Look forward to the next episode!]
[Translation & timing by @cshinjam]