[Sanrio]
[JO1 x Sanrio]
[New Character Development Project]
[JO1 Creative Co. meeting room]
Previously, we received a request from JO1 to make JAMs to feel closer to them
And we created the drafts of the characters
We did indeed
[Previously: The employees drawing the character drafts]
- We created the drafts - We did indeed
[BTW, where is new employee Tsurubo?]
I'm sorry!
Oh? What's up?
[New employee Tsurubo appears at the meeting room in a great hurry]
I brought the design roughs!
[The important rough artwork was entrusted to Newbie Tsurubo by Sanrio]
This time, Sanrio has cooperated with us
- Ohh~ - We're thankful
I made the request
Thank you
As expected of Mamehara-kun
You're on your way to become the director
Heave-ho!
That's too fast
Let's check the designs one by one and think of their nicknames
Yes
That's a huge responsibility
Then, let's look at them in order
Yes
We'll present starting from me, the director
I was in charge of Yonashiro Sho-san
- The leader's
- That's right
He's the oldest, and I'm also the oldest here, so we may get along well
- Then, let's get to it right away
[Director who is faithful to the setting]
This is what I thought up
[Draft by the Director]
He's from Okinawa, so speaking of Okinawa, it's "Shisa". Everyone knows it, right?
It's Okinawa's guardian deity
So I wanted to add the Shisa
- And he loves coffee
- Yes
I wanted to add coffee to the design
I put the Shisa into the coffee cup
[As expected of the Director]
[With Sanrio's cooperation, how has the illustration changed?]
Here it is
[Rough drawing]
- Cute! - Wow!
[Design that far exceeds expectations]
The Sanrio-ness has increased
It's wonderful. The use of colour is cute too
My proposed design has turned out like this
Wonderful
I'm up next. Please treat me well
I'm in charge of Shiroiwa Ruki-san's character
- Then, let's look at it right away
- Yes
- Here it is
- Oh my!
Cute!
There has been information that Shiroiwa Ruki-san owns 3 poodles
So I made a character using the motif of a poodle
And his member colour is white, so I thought of making it a white fluffy poodle
- That's why it's white
[Already cute <3]
Is there a point you're particular about?
The point I'm particular about is below the feet
If you look carefully, the paw is a heart with 'RUKI' written
An illustration full of ideas - how has the rough drawing turned out?]
Here it is
Cute!
It's super cute, isn't it?
According to sources, this kid can't sleep without a pacifier
And the bottom of the feet will be recreated as I designed
- That's it for me
- Thank you
A wonderful presentation
Then, I'll pass it to the next person
Yes. Unit Chief Mamehara
Yes. Please treat me well
I thought of the design for Mamehara Issei-san
Here is my draft
Cute!
It's cool
My art is wonderfully terrible
But it's a dog
Mamehara Issei-san looks like a puppy so I tried to show that
And he has a belt that writes 'mame'
- Whoa it writes 'mame'
- That's awesome
And I wanted to try adding a scarf
He likes hero transformations so I imagined that while creating this
So here is how it is after cooperation from Sanrio
[Stole the hearts of the employees <3]
The belt has a bean
Cute!
There's a bean here too
The beans are different
And his member colour red is included too
It feels like a main character
I'm really satisfied with this
"I'm really satisfied with this"~
I was in charge of Kawashiri Ren-san
Frist, I shall humbly introduce my draft
Here it is
It looks quite complete already
It seems that Kawashiri-san is said to look like a fox by his fans
So firstly I used the image of a fox
And his hobby is magic, so I used the image of a magician
He has a hat, and I drew a dove as his companion separately
But it could rest on his head, or be together with him
[Deputy Director Kawashiri's illustration full of ideas - How has it turned out?]
Here is the rough drawing from Sanrio
- Cute! - Cool!
He's wearing his hat diagonally stylishly
True, it's stylish
They made it really cute, I'm very satisfied
Thank you very much!
[After the deputy director, a slightly nervous Kinjo]
I'd like to introduce my draft right away
W-where should I press?
- The side button, that one
- This?
[Presentation continues after pulling himself together]
Cute!
First of all, I'm in charge of Kinjo Sukai-san
I captured all the information about him
I created a character that matches some of those traits
Wonderful
So it turned out like this
Explain it!
His dream is to become a pilot when he grows older
And to fly in the sky, because his name is Sukai
And you can bring him around the world
I see!
You even wrote his height
He's 3-4 years old
- 3-4 years old!?
- He's huge!
But he's 150cm
That means he can grow even taller
[Curious about the rough drawing...]
Here it is
Cute!
His tongue is sticking out
Right, there has been information that Sukai-san's habit is sticking out his tongue
It's really cute
Wonderful, thank you
[Nerve-wracking presentation ends without problems]
I thought up the design for Kawanishi Takumi-kun
For now, shall we look at it?
Yes
Here it is
Is this a...penguin?
This is a penguin
I wonder why it became a penguin?
[It's us who want to know LOL]
You're the one who came up with it!
Before you realised...
A penguin simply came to mind
I see
It fell from the sky
That's why I made it a penguin
it's name is 'Pocchari'?
No! It's characteristic is that it is 'pocchari'(chubby)
It's characteristic is chubby, I see
[Director's airheaded comment]
It's a penguin, so it likes ice cream
It likes ice cream
I see
[What kind of illustration has the ice-cream-loving penguin become?]
Here it is
[Employees who start smiling involuntarily]
You can truly feel how much he loves ice cream
[He's wearing it!]
It's really cute
It's proper chubby
Right, the plumpness over here is really great
How is the completed art?
I'm very satisfied
[Full of cute illustrations]
[High expectations for the remain illustrations]
I'm in charge of Ohira Shosei-san
I'd like to show my draft
Wow! It's a good drawing
Ohira Shosei-san's character is said to be like an angel
I see
So I tried to imagine that and added wings
Angel wings
You even added colour
It looks like a medicine notebook
The cover page
I kind of get it
Then, the drawing that Sanrio helped us with...
I want to see it
[Moved]
Really awesome!
Cute!
The wings are cute
The hair is a little long, perhaps they helped me lengthen it
[Hairstyle imitating Ohira-san]
Wonderful~ Thank you
This surprised me the most
Next is...
[Newbie Tsurubo's turn to present]
I was in charge of Tsurubo Shion-san
First, here's the original draft
It has a ton of individuality
Is it only the face?
It's a chihuahua
I see
I wonder how this turned out
- This is awesome!
[He checks it beforehand]
Because it only has the face
The individual characteristics may start to clash
I wonder what they decided to get rid of or keep
- Shall we look at it?
- Yes
Here it is
Cute!
They kept the cheek
The original image is...
The original image is...this
It's scary!
It properly turned into a 'Sanrio' character
I'm really really satisfied
Thank you very much
First of all...I'm a huge fan of Sato Keigo-san
I'm a huge fan so I was in charge of Sato Keigo-san
First...this
Here it is
The first plant
He likes pulling pranks like a Pierrot
So I tried to make it Pierrot-like
I drew it in a cute-weird way
Let's see how it turned out
Here we go
Cute!
Wow!
- It has the Pierrot-ness
- The body is awesome
They kept the freckles
Thank you very much
- He's satisfied
- I'm really satisfied
Thank you very much
I'm in charge of Kimata Syoya-kun, please treat me well
Let's have a look right away
He looks strong
Kimata-kun owns a bunny at home
I see
It also seems his fans say he looks like a bunny
So I used a bunny as the motif
His eyes are sparkly
Is this the point you were particular about?
Right, there are sparkly Sanrio characters
So I wanted to make it a bit sparkly
Then, let's have a look
How did it turn out?
Cute!
WAH IT'S CUTE
This part...
The shape of his mouth is like Kimata-san
[Employee Kimata who naturally moves towards]
- Not you
- I'm sorry! I thoughtlessly...
It's nothing!
[He's a new employee so please be lenient on him]
Thank you very much
[That leaves Section Chief Kono]
We're on to the last one
You must be used to presentations already
That's right. I've climbed up till this position, after all
[Is that person such an important person?]
You come this far with your presentation skills alone
That's right
I'm presenting Kono Junki-san's design, whom I was in charge of
That dude
Don't say 'that dude'!
They are our clients!
(sorry)
This is what I came up with
Kono Junki-san is JO1's main vocal
And he loves to sing
- So I made it a mic
- Ah, that's a mic?
What did you write on the bottom left?
It writes 'THIS ONE', telling them to make this
'THIS ONE' as in 'this one please'?
We can see his usual English skills too
[As expected of Section Chief Kono, showing off his English skills during the presentation!?]
- The tail is...?
- The tail is a power outlet
Like a wire cable coming out
I wanted to make it cute
How did it turn out?
Let's go
They got us!
- Cute!
[Cuteness with outstanding destructive power]
- I get Gudetama-senpai vibes from this
- That's true
The roundness
The size is great
A little tiny
It feels he could sit up here
It's great
As expected of Sanrio, thank you very much
[All members' presentation complete]
With that, wouldn't you like to see all of them gathered together?
We do!
Here we go!
It's awesome
Junki-kun's is tiny after all!
Tiny~
- Sho-san's
- He took off the cup
He can stand too
Mame's being in the middle fits well after all
It does
It feels like the main character
That's true
We've seen all the characters, and they are sufficiently cute
However, to make an even better character
We'll now like to brush up the designs together with Sanrio's designer
[Meeting with Sanrio's designer]
The blue eyes...
If possible...
I'd like to plump up the shoes to be more Pierrot-like
It's great
Can we try making the body more bear-like?
Wow
I don't know which is better...
...Whether to add this or not, right?
Shisa is like the home's guardian deity
It sits at a high place in the house
A smooth feeling is possible too, like this...
I want him to look like he's in a daze
If it's possible...
I want the fur to point upwards
This one is really really good
Speaking of which, we have to come up with wonderful names for them like JO1-san has
That's right
Let's think of wonderful names
Here we have 8 suggestions
Among these, please see which you like best...
JOBFF
Radio?
We'd like to make a decision
I see
What do you think, everyone?
JOCHUM is cute
JOCHUM is cute too
A short one may be best
That's true, generally I think a simple one is good
At a glance, it's recognisable
Then isn't JOPANY good?
For the words, we want to include JO1
There's also other words like TOP and JAM
Are there any words you'd like to include?
Is there a good word to add...
They are kids aiming for their dreams
Then we should include 'DREAM'
It feels like that
But it'll become too long
Then isn't it JODREAM?
True, we'd want to add DREAM
[Troubled over whether to prioritise ease of saying or the message]
I have a suggestion...
JOYPEEP
Meaning 'fun'?
Then the Y will be a heart like this
Then, we'll narrow it down to 2-3 names
Most of us are thinking to keep it short and sweet
JOPEEP is popular
Or JOPANY is good too
Or JOCHUM is good too
[Name candidates to suggest to JO1]
Seems like something short and catchy is popular within the company too
Yes that's right
I, the Director, will take these name suggestions directly to them to confirm
[We'll leave it to you, Director]
Thank you very much
With that
We are approaching completion
And next time, finally...
We will conduct the final presentations
Finally
Our suggestions, along with Sanrio's cooperation and JO1-san's opinions, will reach completion
Please look forward to it
With that, today's meeting has reached its end
Thank you very much
[Good work]
[Next time: Finally the characters will be completed]
[Translation & timing by @cshinjam]