[Sanrio]
[JO1 x Sanrio]
[New Character Development Project]
[JO1 Creative Co. who gathers early in the morning in the meeting room]
Good morning
These are the documents for the development project
Thank you
[Busy with meeting preparations]
Good morning
UAHHHHH
- It hurts!
- Are you okay?
- I think you weren't caught on camera LOL
[Cool-looking Kinjo's reliable gag]
You were in too much of a hurry
I'm sorry...I was too over-enthusiastic
- Be careful
- I'm sorry
It's only 7.30 in the morning, are you okay?
Be careful
- You keep slipping up, are you okay?
[By the way, what's the topic of today's meeting?]
- You're slipping up
Finally, it's the birth of the characters
I'm looking forward to it
You're so cute!
Director!
A special delivery from Sanrio-san has arrived!
[It's here!]
It has arrived
Something huge has arrived
This is the completed key visual!
It has finally arrived
Wonderful!
- Your eyes are bulging
[We've been waiting~!]
We've sought JO1's confirmation and as a result, the character name has been decided!
The character name is...
[Anticipation]
[Great satisfaction]
[JOCHUM]
It has a cute ring to it
You feel like saying it
It seems it would be loved by everyone
That's right, it has that cuteness
JOCHUM also has other meanings
So we will explain that too
Yes
Let's look at the completed key visual first
Yes please
Then, I will open it
Yes
Is everyone ready?
Yes!
The motivation of a live show is coming out
Ah that's right, because I was invited to attend JO1's live...
That feeling is coming out
Here I go!
Dokidoki waki(?)waku
Waki waku?
[T/NL: Waku-waku = excited]
Whoaaaaa
- What is this?
[What happened?]
Somehow he looks familiar...or not...
I'm sorry! I got it wrong. It's not this
- Please get your act together
(Audience mode)
Please forget that for a moment
- It's this one, I'm sorry
- So it's that one!
I'm sorry
Just saying sorry doesn't mean you'd be forgiven!
I'm the Section Chief, you know?!
[I'm sorry]
Here I go?!
I'm sorry, the one earlier was wrong
This is the real key visual
- Please
- I'm looking forward to it
- I'm really opening it now...everyone, here I go!
Yes!
[Finally! Presenting JOCHUM!]
- Cute!
[Introducing the distinctive 11 members of JOCHUM!]
- They have expressions too
- And movements
[Introducing the distinctive 11 members of JOCHUM!]
- They're really cute!
- How is it?
- They've really been brushed up
- Amazing, isn't it?
- They're cute
The 'CHUM' of 'JOCHUM' also means friends
And it also can mean roommates living in the same room
I see
It seems like to fulfill each of their dreams, they are doing a room-share
It seems there's also a key visual for the house that they are doing the room-share at
Kono-san, please
That's right, we received it too
Wow!
Then, I'll like to open the key visual of the house!
Yes please
Cute!
[Key visual of the house that anyone would want to stay in]
And also
Regarding this, actually...
He's the manager of JOCHUM's house
So he's the manager
That's true, now that you mention it, he looks like one
So they'll get along and live together as friends
Yes
By living in this house, it seems like dreams would come true!
That's true
Since we have the visuals for the house
How about we decide each character's room?
- That's a great idea
[Agreement]
- Each of the 11 characters
- That's right
That's a good idea
While capturing the characteristics of the character, we will decide the rooming
That's great
- Yonashiro-kun likes training
[YA-NU-KA-MI's room]
The 3rd floor has a training room, so I think up there would be good
For Kono-kun's micoon...
There's a Karaoke & theatre space
So I think he would do really well there
- The 2nd floor may suit him well
- The 2nd floor is good
I think the corner room would be nice...he would like it to be quiet
That coming from a mic?
He doesn't like it to be noisy
I recorded that
- You recorded that?
- Yes, I just recorded your words
I'm keeping it as evidence
I'm in charge of Sukai-san
According to my information, he's 22 years old...a doublet
He often says "22 years old doublet"
If I go by this information, room 202 may be good
And Sukai-san loves watching movies
Karaoke too, since he's a vocalist
I'm a little curious, Syoya-kun & Mamehara-kun's character seems very active
It's as you say. I just thought of it too
Kimata-kun's character is a rabbit. And rabbits jump
I'm sure his footsteps would be noisy
Kimata-kun has also been warned that his footsteps are noisy
According to Sukai-san, Kimata-san walks from his heel
Right, he walks while stepping firmly on the ground
He was taught by his mother
And according to Sukai-san, there have been many complaints from members
Sukai-san is amazing...
It's all from Sukai-san
- Hence, the 1st floor...there's food as well
- That's right, the kitchen is there too
I'll go for the room next to the manager
That's great
This is my opinion
- For Mamehara-san's character...
- 103 please!
Oh it seems he has a room he wants
He likes to take walks, so somewhere that he can immediately go out
Then, 103 please
It's also the 1st floor for me
Because he's a dog
Unexpectedly the 1st floor is popular
[With CHULALA moving in, the 1st floor is fully occupied]
Keigo-san's character is a flower, so photosynthesis is important
- So how about the 3rd floor?
- There's plenty of sunshine
No, he's fine with the flower bed
Flower bed?
Yeah, he's fine there
How about 303?
The 3s look like a flower
Wonderful!
But maybe by the outer rooms are better, because there are windows?
Then you'd like a corner room?
No, I'll go with 303
So you're going with 303 after all...
303 please
Moco-chan is an angel
- He can fly
- I see!
He can fly so he can exit by the window
That's true, even from a high floor, he can leave right away
So I was thinking 305 may be good
- But he's an angel, so please protect everyone from the middle
- Should he protect from the middle?
If he can exit from the window, any room is the same, right?
That's true
This kid loves magic
It seems he often does a magic show on the stage
So I think the 2nd floor would be good
And I heard from the manager that due to the noise problem, the rent there is cheap too
I think room 205 is good
For RURU-chan, I heard that Shiroiwa Ruki-san likes the bath
And if you take a closer look, there is an open-air bath
So I think he would be in the open-air bath for a long time
So I think the 3rd floor would be good
What about Kawanishi-san's character?
[Only left with POP-POH]
There are still quite a few rooms available, is there somewhere you like?
There are 3 rooms available
Umm...I'll take 3 rooms
That's a little unfair
POP-POH...POP-POH-chan? POP-POH-kun?
POP-POH
The way he says it...
[Full of everyone's expectations, "POP-POH" is...?]
POP-POH
[Without a doubt, becoming JOCHUM'S HOUSE's idol!]
[Everyone in love with POP-POH]
They're available, so I'd like to rent them all!
- Sounds good
- Thank you very much!
[With POP-POH moving in, JOCHUM's house is fully occupied]
Before we announce the characters
As a warm up before the present(?)
It's 'presentation'
- As a warm up before the presentation...
- Unit Chief, are you ok?
To understand each others' characters better, we'll play a game by team battles
[Profile fill-in-the-blanks game]
Split into 2 teams
- Each team's character's profile has "dream", skill", "trademark phrase" blanked out
- Fill in the blanks of the opposing team with the prepared cards (time limit 5min)
His charm point is "sparkly eyes"...that's nice
His skill is...
Shall we start filling it in from the top?
What do you think is YA-NU-KA-MI's trademark phrase?
Isn't it this?
- That's right!
[Nankuru naru!*]
[T/N: Things will work out! In Okinawan dialect]
Mocomoco?
[Mysterious word card -> mocomoco]
Is 'Can sleep anywhere' Mamehara-kun's?
[Full-out -> Kiss]
- Isn't this 'Why?'
- Ahh he seems like he would say that!
- What do you think of this?
[Become a pilot]
For Sukai-san's character
Become a pilot. Oh that fits
I think this is it
The trademark phrase as 'Why?', isn't it wrong?
It's 'Why?'. Or is it wrong? I don't know
I'm curious about the 'Po'
- Whose is this?
[Get onto a cloud]
This is difficult...is it really 'Why?'
It's definitely this
Is this okay?
Well then, we have decided...or rather guessed the character's details
So each team will show their guesses
Is everyone ok? We'll start from our team, ready, go!
They're pretty much on the right track, right?
Didn't we do it pretty well?
There's no way POP-POH-chan's skill is 'fighting' right?
- Definitely not
- That seems unlikely
But he's doing a fighting pose
Is it not?
He's doing this
Oh, in a cute way? Not like this?
Our team was like this
Then Ren-kun, please
Then next it's our team. Ready, open!
Ohhh aren't you on the right track?
We've also discussed a lot to decide on this
Somehow the name has also been changed
The size (of the blank) doesn't even match (the size of the card)
He has become 'Full-out-kun'
His name has been changed
Isn't this name better?
His trademark phrase has become 'space invasion'?
The trademark phrase
I don't think he looks like that type
I think it's a little bit wrong
But isn't it fine?
I think it looks good
Next time, we will check the correct answers
Look forward to next time too!
[Translation & Timing by @cshinjam]