[Translation by Luna @motto_yomitai and The First Take]
[Timing & formatting by Berry @BerryMagic_]
SHO:
We’ll groove, work the vocal dynamics
and have fun
SHO:
Let's have some fun!
You all good?
SHO:
Should we loosen our shoulders?
Let's do this
SHO:
Shall we?
JUNKI:
Move the soul
Jibun wo koete
[Surpass yourself]
SHO:
Michi no sekai e, go up
[Go up towards an unknown world]
SHO:
I can make my history
TAKUMI:
Move the soul
Koukai wa shinai
[No regrets]
REN:
Kirameku showtime, blow up
[Blow up this shimmering showtime]
REN:
I can make my fantasy, right now
SUKAI:
Meiro no naka deguchi sagashite
[Looking for an exit in this maze]
SUKAI:
Hayaku naru toki wo tsukamunda
[I'll grasp hold of this time that's quickening]
SHO:
Seikai no nai kotae motomete
[Searching for an answer, but no correct one exists]
SHO & SUKAI:
Samayou koto wa mou, stop it
[It's about time to stop wandering around]
TAKUMI:
Moyaseru bun follow
[Follow what you can burn]
TAKUMI:
Kachitoru kono race & role
[Seize this race and role]
TAKUMI:
Hi wo kaze ni nosete finale
[Set fire to the wind as the finale]
JUNKI:
Yume no goal mukatte kogasou ima wo
[We’ll burn this moment to reach the goal of our dreams]
SUKAI:
Todoku made
[Until we get there]
REN:
Start, set, OK, ima da here we go
[Start, set, OK, now's the time, here we go]
REN:
Ano denkousekka no hibi ga kazaru rainbow
[A rainbow adorned by those days that went by in a flash]
TAKUMI:
Ride on
SHO:
Chizu-doori no mirai
[A perfectly-planned future]
SUKAI:
Kimerareta asu wa
[A predetermined tomorrow]
SUKAI, REN, TAKUMI, JUNKI:
Mou nai
[No longer exist]
SHO:
Jiyuu-jizai ni
[You're in control, now]
Move the soul
JUNKI:
Jibun wo koete
[Surpass yourself]
SHO:
Michi no sekai e, go up
[Go up to an unknown world]
SHO:
I can make my history
Move the soul
JUNKI:
Koukai wa shinai
[Got no regrets]
SUKAI:
Kirameku showtime, blow up
[Blow up this shimmering showtime]
SUKAI:
I can make my fantasy, right now
JUNKI:
Oh oh oh oh oh
REN:
Movin' on, movin' on
REN, SHO:
Turn it up, turn it up
SUKAI:
Move the soul right now
JUNKI:
Oh oh oh oh oh
REN, SUKAI, SHO:
Movin' on, movin' on
Turn it up, turn it up
JUNKI:
Move the soul right now, ah ah
SUKAI:
Furimuku koto dekinai, I don't stop
[I can't look back, I don't stop]
TAKUMI:
Tadoritsuku basho kimatteru start
[When I start, the end is already determined]
SUKAI:
Racing and chasing, yume no chance
[Racing and chasing a chance at a dream]
TAKUMI:
Egake hajimari no iro wa bright
[I start painting with a color so bright]
REN:
Karada jyuu no endorphin ga
[Endorphins running through my body are]
REN, JUNKI:
Spinning, spinning, odorasete okou
[Spinning, spinning, I'll make them dance]
REN:
Kono beat ni
[To this beat]
SHO:
Yoko wo sugi yuku keshiki no light
[Lights from the scenery that passes by]
SHO:
Sono ten to ten wo ima koso tsunagou
[Connect those dots, now's the time]
SUKAI:
Set on
TAKUMI:
Machigai no nai mirai
[A future without mistakes]
SUKAI:
Kimerareta asu wa mou nai
[A predetermined tomorrow, they no longer exist]
SHO:
Genkai made
[To the limit]
Move the soul
TAKUMI:
Jounetsu wo ima
[Let your passions overlap now, go up]
SUKAI:
Kasaneru no sa, go up
[Let your passions overlap now, go up]
SUKAI:
Hajimaru history
[History begins]
Move the soul
TAKUMI:
Ichido shika nai
[Blow up this one-time-only showtime]
REN:
Kanpeki na showtime, blow up
[Blow up this one-time-only showtime]
REN:
Owaranai fantasy, right now
[A never-ending fantasy, right now]
JUNKI:
Faster, faster
SHO:
Move the soul right now
JUNKI, SHO:
REN:
Tomadotteru hima nanka nai kara
[There's no time to be bewildered]
SUKAI:
Mata tachiagare on your own
[Get up again on your own]
TAKUMI:
We gotta decide, setsuna no shoubu no sekai
[We gotta decide, in this world it's all determined in an instant]
JUNKI:
Mou ichido tobikomu
[We'll jump in again]
Move the soul
TAKUMI:
Jibun wo koete
[Surpass yourself]
SHO:
Michi no sekai e, go up
[Go up to an unknown world]
SHO:
I can make my history
Move the soul
TAKUMI:
Koukai wa shinai
[Got no regrets]
SUKAI:
Kirameku showtime, blow up
[Blow up this shimmering showtime]
SUKAI:
I can make my fantasy right now
TAKUMI, JUNKI:
Oh oh oh oh oh
REN, SHO:
Movin' on, movin' on
Turn it up, turn it up
SHO:
Move the soul right now
SUKAI, TAKUMI, JUNKI:
Oh oh oh oh oh
REN, SHO:
Movin' on, movin' on
Turn it up, turn it up
TAKUMI:
Move the soul right now
Thank you very much