JUNKI, TAKUMI:
Move the soul, jibun wo koete
[Move the soul, surpass yourself]
SHO:
Michi no sekai e, go up
[Go up towards an unknown world]
MAME:
I can make my history
TAKUMI, REN:
Move the soul, koukai wa shinai
[Move the soul, got no regrets]
JUNKI:
Kirameku showtime, blow up
[Blow up this shimmering showtime]
RUKI, SUKAI:
I can make my fantasy, right now
MAME:
Meiro no naka deguchi sagashite
[Looking for an exit in this maze]
REN:
Hayaku naru toki wo tsukamunda
[I'll grasp hold of this time that's quickening]
KEIGO:
Seikai no nai kotae motomete
[Searching for an answer, but no correct one exists]
SHO:
Samayou koto wa mou, stop it
[It's about time to stop wandering around]
SYOYA:
Moyaseru bun follow, kachitoru kono race & role
[Follow what you can burn, gain this race & role]
SHION:
Hi wo kaze ni nosete finale
[Set fire to the wind as the finale]
SHOSEI:
Yume no goal mukatte kogasou ima wo
[We’ll burn this moment till we reach the goal of our dreams]
SHION:
Todoku made
[We’ll burn this moment till we reach the goal of our dreams]
SYOYA:
Start, set, OK, ima da here we go
[Start, set, OK, now's the time, here we go]
JUNKI, SHOSEI:
Ano denkousekka no hibi ga kazaru rainbow
[A rainbow adorned by those days that went by in a flash]
SHION:
Ride on
TAKUMI:
Chizu-doori no mirai
[A perfectly-planned future, a predetermined tomorrow, they no longer exist]
SHO:
Kimerareta asu wa mou nai
[A perfectly-planned future, a predetermined tomorrow, they no longer exist]
KEIGO:
Jiyuu-jizai ni
[You're in control, now]
Move the soul
TAKUMI:
Jibun wo koete
[Surpass yourself]
SHO:
Michi no sekai e, go up
[Go up to an unknown world]
MAME:
I can make my history
Move the soul
REN:
Koukai wa shinai
[Got no regrets]
JUNKI:
Kirameku showtime, blow up
[Blow up this shimmering showtime]
RUKI, SHION:
I can make my fantasy, right now
Oh oh oh oh oh, movin' on, movin' on
Turn it up, turn it up
RUKI:
Move the soul right now
Oh oh oh oh oh, movin' on, movin' on
Turn it up, turn it up
SUKAI:
Move the soul right now