[Translation by Luna @motto_yomitai,
Timing & formatting by Berry @BerryMagic_]
JUNKI, TAKUMI:
Move the soul, jibun wo koete
[Move the soul, surpass yourself]
SHO:
Michi no sekai e, go up
[Go up towards an unknown world]
MAME:
I can make my history
TAKUMI, REN:
Move the soul, koukai wa shinai
[Move the soul, got no regrets]
JUNKI:
Kirameku showtime, blow up
[Blow up this shimmering showtime]
RUKI:
I can make my fantasy, right now
MAME:
Meiro no naka deguchi sagashite
[Looking for an exit in this maze]
REN:
Hayaku naru toki wo tsukamunda
[I'll grasp hold of this time that's quickening]
KEIGO:
Seikai no nai kotae motomete
[Searching for an answer, but no correct one exists]
SHO:
Samayou koto wa mou, stop it
[It's about time to stop wandering around]
SYOYA:
Moyaseru bun follow, kachitoru kono race & role
[Follow what you can burn, gain this race & role]
SHION:
Hi wo kaze ni nosete finale
[Set fire to the wind as the finale]
SHOSEI:
Yume no goal mukatte kogasou ima wo
[We’ll burn this moment till we reach the goal of our dreams]
SHION:
Todoku made
[We’ll burn this moment till we reach the goal of our dreams]
SYOYA:
Start, set, OK, ima da here we go
[Start, set, OK, now's the time, here we go]
JUNKI, SHOSEI:
Ano denkousekka no hibi ga kazaru rainbow
[A rainbow adorned by those days that went by in a flash]
SHION:
Ride on
TAKUMI:
Chizu-doori no mirai
[A perfectly-planned future, a predetermined tomorrow, they no longer exist]
SHO:
Kimerareta asu wa mou nai
[A perfectly-planned future, a predetermined tomorrow, they no longer exist]
KEIGO:
Jiyuu-jizai ni
[You're in control, now]
Move the soul
TAKUMI:
Jibun wo koete
[Surpass yourself]
SHO:
Michi no sekai e, go up
[Go up to an unknown world]
MAME:
I can make my history
Move the soul
REN:
Koukai wa shinai
[Got no regrets]
JUNKI:
Kirameku showtime, blow up
[Blow up this shimmering showtime]
RUKI, SHION:
I can make my fantasy, right now
Oh oh oh oh oh, movin' on, movin' on
Turn it up, turn it up
RUKI:
Move the soul right now
Oh oh oh oh oh, movin' on, movin' on
Turn it up, turn it up
TAKUMI:
Move the soul right now
SHION:
Furimuku koto dekinai, I don't stop
[I can't look back, I don't stop]
SYOYA:
Tadoritsuku basho kimatteru start
[When I start, the end is already determined]
SHION:
Racing and chasing, yume no chance
[Racing and chasing a chance at a dream]
SYOYA:
Egake hajimari no iro wa bright
[I start painting with a color so bright]
REN:
Karada jyuu no endorphin ga
[Endorphins running through my body are]
JUNKI, SHION:
Spinning, spinning, odorasete okou
[Spinning, spinning, I'll make them dance]
RUKI:
Kono beat ni
[To this beat]
MAME:
Yoko wo sugi yuku keshiki no light
[Lights from the scenery that passes by]
RUKI:
Sono ten to ten wo ima koso tsunagou, set on
[Connect those dots, now's precisely the time, set on]
TAKUMI:
Machigai no nai mirai
[A future without mistakes, a predetermined tomorrow, they no longer exist]
KEIGO:
Kimerareta asu wa mou nai
[A future without mistakes, a predetermined tomorrow, they no longer exist]
SHO:
Genkai made
[To the limit]
TAKUMI, JUNKI:
Move the soul, jounetsu wo ima
[Move the soul, let your passions overlap now, go up]
SHO:
Kasaneru no sa, go up
[Move the soul, let your passions overlap now, go up]
KEIGO:
Hajimaru history
[History begins]
JUNKI, REN:
Move the soul, ichido shika nai
[Move the soul, blow up this one-time-only showtime]
TAKUMI:
Kanpeki na showtime, blow up
[Move the soul, blow up this one-time-only showtime]
RUKI:
Owaranai fantasy, right now
[A never-ending fantasy, right now]
RUKI:
Faster, faster
SHOSEI:
REN:
Tomadotteru hima nanka nai kara
[There's no time to be bewildered]
MAME:
Mata tachiagare on your own
[Get up again on your own]
TAKUMI:
We gotta decide, setsuna no shoubu no sekai
[We gotta decide, in this world it's all determined in an instant]
JUNKI:
Mou ichido tobikomu
[We'll jump in again]
Move the soul
TAKUMI:
Jibun wo koete
[Surpass yourself]
SHO:
Michi no sekai e, go up
[Go up to an unknown world]
MAME:
I can make my history
Move the soul
REN:
Koukai wa shinai
[Got no regrets]
TAKUMI:
Kirameku showtime, blow up
[Blow up this shimmering showtime]
SHOSEI:
I can make my fantasy, Right now
Oh oh oh oh oh, movin' on, movin' on
Turn it up, turn it up
RUKI:
Move the soul right now
Oh oh oh oh oh, movin' on, movin' on
Turn it up, turn it up
TAKUMI:
Move the soul right now