Issei: Real earnings and Net... Income
Sho: Net Income, right here...
Issei: And the Tax (funds) Social Security...
Junki: This is important
Issei: [mumbles]
Issei: .... real earnings
Ren: We know the answer to this, but this is a study session before Mame's test
Junki: Now it is mame's turn to answer it
Sho: We can answer this instantly. For real...
Ren: That is a given
Syoya: What is that?
Syoya: Is it past exams' question collection?
Sho: he is studying for an exam
Syoya: I see...
Syoya: Is that real?
Ren: Yes...
Junki: Home Economics (Kateika↓)
Sho: Kateika↓?!
[The Members are arguing about the Pronounciation due to dialect differences]
Ren: It's Kateika→!
Sho: shouldn't it be Kateika→?!
[The Members are arguing about the Pronounciation due to dialect differences]
Junki: It's Kateika→???
Junki: Kateika↓ Kateika↓
Ren: It's Kateika→!
Junki: Shosei, isn't it Kateika↓?
shosei  it's  kansai dialect
Shosei: Kateeka↓?  It's Kateeka↓  [Kansai dialect]
Junki: Look!
Ren: It's Kateika→!
Syoya: It's just like how you pronounce Stability (Anteikan)
Ruki: Every single time everyone would argue about pronunciation...
Issei: Then, can you pronounce this one?
Ruki: Every single time everyone would argue pronunciation...
Ruki: But the right one is MINE!
[Kanto dialect is considered as Standard Japanese Pronounciation]
[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]