[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]
Ren: Here we go!
Today we will do a Youtube Live
Ren: Now... what do you call that?
Ren: The one that is shown at the beginning,
The Countdown!
Ren: We will start the live stream countdown
Junki: And the one who will do it is Kawashiri Ren?
Junki: Amazing!
Junki: That is cool
Ren: Raise your hand! Then, I shall start it
Junki: Let's go!
Ren: 1... 2... Beep
Junki: I am sure there are still more steps. Look!
Junki & Ren: There is 'Done'!
Ren: 'Done'!
Junki & Issei: Let's go!
Junki: Awesome!
Ren: There is one like!
Junki: This is truly amazing!
Ren: Then, let's press the like button from the Staff's phone
Ren: Wow, the comments are flooding in
Junki: Wow!
Junki: Amazing
Ren: You guys are so quick! As expected!
Junki: So quick~
Ren: Well, let's liven up this 12-min countdown with everyone's comments!
Junki: Someone asked what they should do during this 12-min
Junki: You know the answer already, we will watch 'REAL' MV.
[REAL MV]
Junki: Then I shall read this comment
Junki: It's about our Tour's information
Junki: Wow, amazing
Junki: "JO1 Single Album in my neighbourhood CD Store are already sold out"
Junki: So happy to hear that
Ren: Amazing
Junki: At what time will the live stream starts?
Issei: TEIYOU ga tsutsumu
[Mame changed the lyric from Taiyou (Sun) to Teiyou (Ram/Sheep)]
Ren & Junki: Teiyou?!
Ren: Everyone, please subscribe to our channel
Issei: Everyone
Issei: Please subscribe to our channel, press the 'Good' button, and leave some comments
Ren: That is an order from Mame
[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]