[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]
Issei: We are doing a photoshoot!
Ruki: And the next one in line is Kono Junki
Ruki: Ah, Kono Junki is fooling around
Issei: It's Kono Chunki
Ruki: Kono-kun
Junki: Good afternoon
Ruki: How is your styling for today?
Junki: For today...
Junki: I dyed my hair back to black
Ruki: Oh, that is true!
Junki: Yes
Ruki: It suits you really well
Junki: Really?
Junki: The outfit... I am wearing suits now
Ruki: Looks cool
Ruki: This outfit is cool, right?
Junki: Mine and Ruki's outfit is kind of similar, the shade
Ruki: I am not sure whether it is captured or not
Ruki: It does look similar
Ruki: Ah.. this mirror
Staff: Shall we do one more time?
Ruki: I am sorry
Staff: It's okay
Ruki: There are still a lot of things to do for today
Issei: Yes...
Ruki: Let's continue to do our best
Issei: I'm sleepy
Issei: I'll do my best! Bye bye!
[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]