[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]
Junki: For now, let's go first with Kawashiri
Ren: This is no good...
Ren: Can i do it like this?
Sukai: I think Rhythm is important here
Sho: You can do it however you like
Ren: This is okay as well?
Ren: Then this will be easy
JO1: Whoaaa
Ren: Like this
Sukai: Ren-kun have a good Rhythm, let's go with it~
Sho: I don't think that has anything to do with this
Sukai: It does have an effect
Sho: Is it so?
Sukai: Even in boxing they go with the rhythm
Ren: Here I go~
Machine: (beep - fail)
Ren: We haven't started yet
Junki: It could probably be an error
Ren: It was a 'Shadow' punch
Sukai: 'Shadow' 'Shadow'
Sho: Do a jab
Ren: Then I shall restart
Ren: Here I go
Sukai: It was a 'shadow'
Sukai: But the score is high
Junki: Isn't that amazing
Sho: It's 724
Sho: Isn't this good~
Junki: How to do this in one go
It only has 3 digits, so the maximum will only goes up to 999
Ren: That is true
Junki: I don't think I can accept this system
Junki: I don't like the fact that it won't go over 1000
Ren: Say that if you can actually reach up to 999
Sukai: That is impossible
Junki: I really can't accept this
Junki: Here i go~
Sukai: It's exactly 500
Junki & Ren: It is
Sukai & Sho: This looks nice
Junki: It's the effect of the ring
Sukai: The ring, the ring
Sho: Then I will take it off
Sho: Here i go~
Junki: He is strong!
Sho: Oh, and it's the same number
Ren: Whaaatt?!
Sho: It's 849! The same as previous one
Ren: Is this for real?
Junki: Sukai, we'll leave it to you
Sukai: If I want to surpass Sho-kun's record, how much should I score?
Sho: You can surpass me just by scoring 923 points, no... I mean above it
Ren: Go for 999
Sho: If it's possible, you should score 924
Sukai: I see
Sho: You should do this seriously
Sho: The sound is incredible
Sukai: Can I please try this out
Junki: No no no, you can't
Sukai: I don't think it's good to be very consious of this
Sho: It won't do if you don't do it naturally
Sukai: Here I go
Junki: There it is!
Sukai: Damn!
Junki: That is so close!
Junki: But that was so good
Junki: It looked like it would have surpass it
Ren: Junki....
Sho: Wow, it's 1612
Sukai: So for now I ranked 2nd
Sho: By the way, Junki needs...
Junki: I should surpass Sho-kun
Sukai: Will you surpass it with this score?
Sho: For Junki to surpass me, he needs 1109
Sukai: Will you be able to do that?
Junki: I can, I can, I can definitely do it
Sho: If you are able to score 999, we will let you win
Sukai: That is good
Junki: Hold on... I don't think that is right
Sho: The maximum score is 999, so...
Ren: If Junki able to score 999 that means the score is over it
Junki: I will do this for real
Ren: Go for it
Sho: It will be very cool if you can score it, Junki
Junki: Please let me win if I am able to score 500
Sho: So it's either 999 or 500?
Ren & Sho: Okay
Sho: So if you are aiming for 500...
Junki: That's not it. The thing is, that's my best score if I do it with all my might
Sho: Well if you get 500 here...
Junki: I can get the exact score
Junki: Here I go~
Sho: You can score higher
Junki: I score a bit higher
Junki: What's with this score...
Sho: It's 813
Junki: What's with this!
[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]