[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]
Ren: What time is it?
Shosei: Now it's....
Shosei & Ren: It's 17:54
Ren: Our 'Bokura no Kisetsu' MV will be released through YouTube premiere
Ren: It will be released on our channel in the next 3-4 minutes
Ren: Well, it just happens that we have time for this
Ruki: It's by chance
Ren: We will write some comments in the chat box
Ruki: Everyone, we will send it through JO1 official account, please find it
Ren: Better to write it in hiragana
Ren: Hiragana would be good
Ruki: Ren-kun, we have no time left
Ruki: We have no time, please do it quickly
Shosei: Ren-kun, Ren-kun, Ren-kun
Ren: This is 'Ren', 'Ruki'...
Ren: 'Shosei'
Ruki: This clumsy Ren-kun is cute
Ruki: Will there be anyone who notices this
Shosei: Not sure, will there be any~
Ruki: The comments are moving quite fast
Shosei: It's fast
Ren: Please... watch... the... MV
Ruki: There is only 30sec left
Ruki: Now it's 23sec left
Ren: Please... watch it... a lot
Ruki: 20sec left
Ruki: Ren-kun, 14sec left
Ren: And next we will... send this!!
Shosei: There it is
Ren & Ruki: There it is!
Ruki: Oh the chat stopped
Ren: It stopped!
Ruki: It is placed at the top
Shosei: Amazing
Ren: The others reactions are...
Ruki: Will there be a delay?
Shosei: Looks like it
Ren: "Ren, Ruki, Shosei are here!"
Shosei: Amazing!
Ren: Amazing!
Ruki: Oh, amazing... it reaches everyone
Ren: This is great! It's right on time
Ren: There are 2 minutes left
Ren: In 2 minutes, please watch our 'Bokura no Kisetsu' MV a lot, and let's make it a wonderful Season
Ren: Bye-bye
[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]