[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]
Junki: Can you please drink this a bit
Keigo: Okay.. okay...
Ren: That's enough
Junki: Syoya, you can go first
Ren: Fix the water bottle
Keigo: Please sit properly
JO1: Let's have a good match
Junki: We haven't started yet
Ren: That is no good
Junki: I'll go next
Junki: Oh no
Keigo: The water is moving
Ren: Yes, the wave
Syoya: My first try was very close
Junki: Let's make it that the one who fails treats the rest to juice
Keigo & Ren: Okay
Junki: I think it's better if you put force
Junki: That is so close
Keigo: This is hard
Keigo: It is nice if we have it in the middle
Keigo: We are in a pinch
Ren & Junki: The time has come
Syoya: Is it okay for you guys to make me as the youngest treat you?
Keigo: If I get this, then it is the end, right?
Junki & Ren: That is right
Syoya: Just do it quickly
Keigo: The timing is
Junki: He closed his eyes
[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]