[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]
Shosei: We will do Rock-Paper-Scissors to decide tomorrow's departing order
Junki: Our departure time...
Takumi: There are three of us, but we have to depart separately
Takumi: Wouldn't this be the first time that it happen?
Shosei: We're not leaving together all at once
Junki: Shall we divide it starting from the one who will leave the earliest
Takumi: It's 8AM, 9AM, and 10AM
Junki: Let's decide it with Rock-Paper-Scissors
Shosei: Seriously, won't you let the youngest decide first?
Shosei: For real
Junki: Isn't it supposed to be the other way around?
Takumi: Either way I am the middle-man, so I am okay with it
Junki: That is true...
Takumi: I am fine with either
Junki: We should not do that. I recommend to do Rock-Paper-Scissors
Junki: I do have intention to let the youngest decide
Junki: But I hope we can have fun and decide it through Rock-Paper-Scissors
Junki: Okay, let's do this
Shosei: Wow is this for real
Junki: The winner will have the privilege to choose
Takumi: To choose!
Junki: I don't think we need to choose though. Let's go.
Shosei: I am seriously scared
Takumi: Then there is possibility that we win and choose 8AM?
Takumi: If you do that, you will gain a lot of likability points
Takumi: Right?
Shosei: That is nice
Junki: There might be a person who wins and choose to go at 8AM
Shosei: That is surely cool
Takumi: He looks so nervous
Takumi: His eyes are very scary
Junki: You guys will go with Scissors, right?
Shosei: Hold on hold on
Takumi: That is such a new way (of intimidating)
Takumi: "You guys will go with Scissors, right?"
Takumi: What's with that
Takumi: It's the same result
[Junki peeks into his clasped hand to determine his next move]
[Takumi: Paper; Junki & Shosei: Rock]
[Takumi Wins]
Takumi: I'm sorry
Junki: That's so nice
[Shosei: Rock; Junki: Paper]
[Shosei Wins]
Junki: I still have chances
Takumi: That is right
Shosei: That is true
Takumi: Shosei, which is the best time?
Shosei: Me?
Shosei: 10AM
Takumi: So it's 10AM for you. And Junki?
Junki: It's 10AM for me
Takumi: Then I shall go with 10AM
Shosei: Damn...
Junki: I didn't expect I would lose
Takumi: To be honest, I am fine with any of the options
Shosei: Deep down I do want to start at 8AM
Shosei: but as expected it's too (early)
Junki: 10AM. Well well well....
Junki: How shall we do this?
Takumi: He has yet to decide it
Junki: What is your choice?
[Junki and Takumi messing with the intonation]
Shosei: What should I do?
Shosei: What do you want me to choose?
Junki: Basically I want you to choose 8AM
Junki: What is your choice?
Shosei: Then I will go with 9AM
Junki: It is all decided
Takumi: This time you are the Center
Junki: That is true. I have to wake up early tomorrow
Junki: The result comes out precisely
Shosei: Yeay!
[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]