JO1 are playing "Thumb Game" (Kansai ver.: Isse-no-de) where they have to guess the total of thumbs that will be raised by the players during their turn. The one who could get their two hands down is the winner.
Ren: I can envision it
Ren: Isse-no-de TWO
Shion: You gave it just like that!
Shion: What are you doing?!
Shosei: We are in trouble
Shion: Isse-no-de TWO
Shion: OIIIII!!!
Shion: Why not on my turn...
Ren: Okay, let's do this in a swift
Shosei: Isse-no-de ONE
Sho: Wow that is amazing
Shion: He is strong
Shosei: What do you mean by strong?
Ren: He is strong
Sho: Isse-no-de ONE
Sho: Don't give up yet, Shion!
Shosei: Shion, you still have a chance
Ren: The two of them guess 'One' consecutively
Sho: They calculating it
Ren: I do have an intention to call out 'One'
Sho: This is a Death Match
Shosei: A death match...
Ren: On my count...
Ren: Isse-no-de TWO
Sho: This is just the beginning
Shion: Isse-no-de TWO
Ren: I will switch to Shion's mindset
Ren: If i switch my mindset to Shion's, I will know what he would do
Ren: Uhnnnnnn.... [Imitates Shion]
Ren: Isse-no-de ZERO
Sho: No one is getting it right
Shosei: It's a chance~
Sho: Let's go!
Shion: Isse-no-de ONE
Shion: On the contrary, isn't this amazing?
Sho: Looks like Shion will end up as the winner soon
Shosei: Looks like he will
Shion: Hold on, that makes me nervous
Shion: Isse-no-de ZERO
Ren: This is not looking good
Ren: The battle has started
Ren: Isse-no-de ZERO
Sho: Wow, amazing
Sho: You did well by raising it
Sho: Will this decide the winner?
Shion: Isse-no-de ZERO
Shion: I beat Ren-kun!
Shosei: He did said to do it 11 times
Sho: How come it can be this exciting
[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]