[23rd of March - 11:30AM. "Graduation Day"]
Today, I'm going to pick my graduation diploma at school
Throughout my three years in high school
I was able to experience many good things
So I feel kind of sad that my high school life is coming to an end
[11:30AM - The members secretly arrived at Mame-chan's school in advance]
Today is Mame-chan's graduation ceremony!
This is awesome. We will do our best to celebrate it
Congratulations on your high school graduation, Mame
"Teacher" is here to celebrate it
What? I can't do it right this time
- I just tied it perfectly for him
- I will do it myself
I did it right just a moment ago
Please don't record this
I am here to deliver these flowers
Probably it's too much to receive them all
Since we are here to celebrate Mame-chan's graduation which happens once in a lifetime
Even though we can only get these flowers for him and some message videos
It's a touching one
It would be nice if it will make him cry today
Mame will arrive at 11:58AM
- Now it's...
- It's 11:45AM
The members are all here as a surprise
So hopefully this will make him happy
It's almost time
I am getting excited
Excited!
According to my calculation, there is a 50% chance of Mame crying
One more minute
He will arrive soon, so everybody please be quiet
There he comes
He is coming!
Shhhh
There he is!
MAME!!!!! CONGRATULATIONS!!!
Congratulations on your graduation!
Congratulations!
You guys surprised me!
Actually, this is not the only one...
Is there something else?
A surprise!
Yep we got a surprise gift
IT'S HERE!
[A Surprise Video Letter from his hometown, Okayama]
Ah I see
Wow, there it is
This is so nostalgic
This brought back a lot of memories
"Kabuto Movie!"
Mame-chan, Congratulations on your Graduation!
They recorded this for you
He is wearing same t-shirt as yours!
He is my master
I don’t have much to say, since we spoke through video call on New Year’s Day
But I hope you will keep on working hard
[Messages from his Parents]
Issei, congratulations on graduating high school
We understand that it must have been extremely hard to balance JO1 activities and high school life
As parents, we are relieved now that you have graduated
and to JO1 members, we ask your continuous support for Issei.
Leave it to us!
We'll take care of him
Issei, congratulations on graduating high school today
It's a relieve that you are able to receive your graduation diploma today
Be grateful to the support you have received from many people
and don't forget that they are the ones that made who you are today
And from now on, as a member of the society
you will learn a lot of many new things
and focus on work to your heart's content
Like the meaning of your name, please grow up one step at a time
and
Repay all the supports you have received from many people
You must take care of your health
and please make sure to contact us more often
Well then, till the day you come back home to Okayama again
I will make Pork Miso Soup and wait for you
That touched me the most
Bye bye
You look just like your dad
He does
Isn't it great Mame?
Thank you so much
I didn't know about this at all
I am sorry (for crying)
Thank you
I once again realized that
I am supported by many people
I'm extremely happy right now
I will continue to work hard as a JO1 member
On your mark!
Go to the TOP! We are JO1!
Mame, Congratulations!
Congratulations!!!
You have grown up!
[Eng Translation by peanutbataa247. May contain inaccuracies]