[Translation by Shin @cshinjam,
timing and formatting by Berry @BerryMagic_]
TAKUMI:
Kagami no oku zutto samayoi tsudzuketa
[I’ve been wandering in the depths of the mirror]
MAME:
Kedo kidzuitanda
[But I noticed]
TAKUMI:
This is me
MAME:
REN:
Ippozutsu I will be there
[One step at a time, I will be there]
SHION:
Kinou yori mo chikadzuku yume
[A dream closer than it was yesterday]
SUKAI:
Kawaranai I will be with you
[Nothing will change, I will be with you]
KEIGO:
Motto motto todoketai
[I want it to reach you more and more]
SHO:
Taiyou ga tsutsumu
[The sun envelops you]
SHO:
Mabayui hikari kimi terasu
[The dazzling light shines on you]
JUNKI:
Egakunda sono hi wo
[Envision that day]
JUNKI:
Saigo no ippo tadoru hi wo, yeah
[That day where you take the final step]
TAKUMI:
Me no mae ni this is my desire
[Right before my eyes, this is my desire]
RUKI:
Motto takai basho
[Reaching a higher place]
REN:
Tsureteku yo te wo tsukande
[I’ll take you along, grab my hand]
KEIGO:
This is no dream, so real
MAME:
SYOYA:
Let’s go all the way
Kagami no naka
[In the mirror]
SYOYA:
Zutto toji komerareta you de, ay
[As if I had been trapped in here forever]
SYOYA:
1 step, toki ga tatte someday
[1 step, time passes, someday]
SYOYA:
2 step, omoi door aite
[2 step, open the heavy door]
SHOSEI:
Chiisana koro mita daydream
[The daydream I had when I was young]
SHOSEI:
Tashika na mono ni shite iku
[I will make it real]
SHOSEI:
I knew from the start
Mirai eigou ni like a star
[The future eternally like a star]
SHO:
Chirabatta kioku
[Scattered memories]
KEIGO:
Osanaki hi no akogaretachi
[The longing from my childhood]
JUNKI:
Te no hira ni atsumete
[I gather it in my palm]
SUKAI:
Tashika na mono e kaeru kara
[Because I’m gonna change it into something real]
MAME:
Taiyou ga tsutsumu
[The sun envelops you]
MAME:
Mabayui hikari kimi terasu
[The dazzling light shines on you]
REN:
Egakunda sono hi wo
[Envision that day]
REN:
Saigo no ippo tadoru hi wo
[That day where you take the final step]
REN:
Yeah
JUNKI:
Me no mae ni this is my desire
[Right before my eyes, this is my desire]
SHO:
Motto takai basho
[Reaching a higher place]
TAKUMI:
Tsureteku yo te wo tsukande
[I’ll take you along, grab my hand]
SUKAI:
This is no dream, so real
SHION:
So real, yume miteta basho sa
[So real, the place I dreamt of]
SHION:
Right here, egaita basho sa
[Right here, the place I envisioned]
SHION:
Kimi to boku no dice onaji basho de kasane
[Your dice and mine overlap in the same place]
RUKI:
Asu e tsuki nukeru my wings to
[My wings that will break through to tomorrow]
RUKI:
Hateshinaku tsudzuku story
[And an endless story]
SHOSEI:
Sou toii mirai ja nai darou
[It won’t be much longer now]
SYOYA:
Right now, right here, so real
TAKUMI:
Me no mae ni this is my desire
[Right before my eyes, this is my desire]
RUKI:
Motto takai basho
[Reaching a higher place]
JUNKI:
Tsureteku yo te wo tsukande
[I’ll take you along, grab my hand]
SHO:
This is no dream, so real
REN, RUKI:
Ay, we will be together now
Tsuyoku nigitte kono mama
[Hold on tightly, just like this]
KEIGO, SUKAI:
Ay, this is my desire
SYOYA:
Hateshinaku doko made mo
[It’ll be endless, no matter where we go]
SHOSEI, MAME:
Ay, we will be together now
Tsuyoku nigitte kono mama
[Hold on tightly, just like this]
SHO, SHION:
Ay, this is my desire
JUNKI, TAKUMI:
This is no dream, so real