[Translation by Shin @cshinjam]
[Timing & formatting by Berry @BerryMagic_]
TAKUMI:
Kokoro madowasu emi
[Your bewitching smile]
TAKUMI:
Kiken na amai kaori
[Your dangerous sweet scent]
TAKUMI:
Ippo machigaereba virus
[One wrong step would be a virus]
SUKAI:
Itami ni kawarun da
[Turning everything into pain]
REN:
You're in danger, girl
Ki wo tsukete dareka ga eien ni kimi wo
[Beware, someone may continue to torment you eternally]
JUNKI:
Kurushime tsuzukeru darou
[Beware, someone may continue to torment you eternally]
SHO:
Mayottara koko ni modoreba ii sa
[If you're lost, you can return here]
SHO:
Here can only save you
TAKUMI:
Yoku mite paradise
[Have a good look at this paradise]
TAKUMI:
Kimi ni okuru sign
[I am sending you a sign]
RUKI:
Where you want, when you need, yeah, yeah
JUNKI:
Tokubetsu na hito
[You're special to me]
JUNKI:
Mamoritai yo shine
[I want to protect your shine]
KEIGO:
I’ll give you all, say the word, oh
MAME:
You are not safe with him, safe with him
REN:
MAME:
Tadayou yami toki ni
[The darkness sometimes bewitches people]
MAME:
Hito wo hikitsukeru
[The darkness sometimes bewitches people]
MAME:
Ou hodo mieru mirage
[The further I chase, the better I see through the mirage]
SHION:
Sono saki wa nan darou?
[What lies beyond it?]
SUKAI:
You’re in danger, girl
Itami ni naru mae ni
[Before it turns into pain]
SUKAI:
Mou tomeyou delusion
[Let's stop the delusion]
SHO:
Motto niau basho ga aru baby
[There's a place more suited for you, baby]
JUNKI:
Kimi wa special
[You're special]
JUNKI:
Mamorareru beki hito
[You deserve to be protected]
JUNKI:
Here can only save you
SHO:
Himitsu no paradise
[Our secret paradise]
SHO:
Ore to futari no
[For just you and I]
MAME:
Where you want, when you need, yeah, yeah
JUNKI:
Kokoro yuku made
[I'll heal you to your heart's content]
JUNKI:
Iyasu to ii yo
[I'll heal you to your heart's content]
SHOSEI:
I’ll give you all, say the word oh
KEIGO:
You are not safe with him, safe with him
SUKAI:
REN:
Itsu demo koko de kimi wo matteru
[I'll always wait for you right here]
SHO:
Kurushii toki wa
[When you're hurting]
SHO:
Sou, wasurenaide
[Don't ever forget]
TAKUMI:
I’ll settle you down, settle you down
I swear chikau
[I swear, I swear]
JUNKI:
Eien ni nakasenai
[I would never make you cry]
SHION:
Yeah, you know me, I like the danger danger
Kimi wa marude angel, angel
[You're like my angel, angel]
SHION:
Ore no kotoba shinji saseru kara
[I'll make you believe my words]
SHION:
Kakugo kime zenbu kakereru kara
[I'm ready to put it all on the line]
SHOSEI:
Girl, it’s all about you
Yatsu kara chakushin naru
[An incoming call from that guy]
SHOSEI:
Ore wa zettai nakasenai, yeah yeah
[I'd never make you cry like that, yeah yeah]
RUKI:
Daiji na no wa kizuna shinjiau
[Believe in the bond you and I share]
RUKI:
I’m gonna take you to my world, bae, yeah yeah
SYOYA:
Come into my zone
Hikaru kimi wo
[You shine so brightly]
SYOYA:
Daremo kegasenai
[No one can taint that]
SYOYA: Just lock the door
TAKUMI:
Yoku mite paradise
[Have a good look at this paradise]
SYOYA: Just lock the door
TAKUMI:
Yoku mite paradise
[Have a good look at this paradise]
TAKUMI (JUNKI):
Kimi ni okuru sign (kimi ni okuru sign)
[I am sending you a sign]
SYOYA:
Where you want, when you need, yeah, yeah
TAKUMI (JUNKI):
Kimi ni okuru sign (kimi ni okuru sign)
[I am sending you a sign]
SYOYA:
Where you want, when you need, yeah, yeah
MAME:
Tokubetsu na hito
[You're special to me]
MAME:
Mamoritai yo shine
[I want to protect your shine]
KEIGO:
I’ll give you all, say the word oh
MAME:
You are not safe with him, safe with him
JUNKI:
You're not safe with him
REN:
You are not safe with him, safe with him