Shining gourmet food that satisfies people of virtue
The newest issue of the monthly magazine: Tokyo Calendar
cover: Kawaguchi Haruna
The highly praised magazine now on sale at nation wide bookstores, conbini & online bookstores
JO1
Shiroiwa Ruki
Q: The shooting is about to start now, but how do you feel about it?
Ruki: There is still that...
*The shooting took place with special attention to the measurements for infection prevention
Q: The shooting is about to start now, but how do you feel about it?
I hope to start my engine and shoot something good
Yes, please take care of me today
Q: What do you think about the shooting for Tokyo Calendar?
Ruki: I was really excited
Because it is a bit different from other shootings
in which I wear a jacket or other magazine interviews
which is a lot of fun
so again it was a shooting with a different atmosphere than usually
which made me learn a lot
The light is too strong
which made me a bit teary eyed
because I have to keep my eyes open the whole time
my dry eyes become even drier
Q: What do you think about Kawashiri Ren-san in the April issue?
Ren-kun is also
when he is with us he is, of course, normally in the position of an older brother
This is kinda a sexiness
I haven't seen of him yet
I honestly think
that Ren-kun looks so mature
Yes, I was able to see a new side of him
Q: A memorable restaurant for you?
It's not some rule of JO1 but
there is this restaurant JO1 regularly goes to
the CEO often takes us there
after we, for example, have worked really hard at the filming of a MV
But rather than this being something like my reward
It became our energy, our vitality
that we also work hard to go there
and it's something joyful that there is this restaurant, right?
Q: Something that evolved as JO1 celebrated their second anniversary?
Speaking of something that is different
Rather than that pretty much everything is different
It feels like that everything has improved
like of course the quality of our performances
or the talk at our second anniversary live stream
or the nature of our relationship and so on
and I think that through discussions with everyone
everything is going in a good direction now
Q: Regarding the fan's reactions on SNS
Right... If something becomes a hot topic
we do directly hear about it, too
It is our strength but
The fans who like me too,
are called JAM
and after all the fans are one of the important strengths of JO1
and after all we think that we cannot lose to their passion
We were able to meet them for the first time in two years at the lives
But I hope that the situation comes that
our opportunities to meet increase more and more
and have a relationship of seeing their smiles directly
so I really feel grateful for everything they do always
Also, I believe that I can do such wonderful schedules
like this is truly thanks to everyone
so thank you very much
Please make sure to check out the magazine
Q: Your feelings for the members upon doing solo activities?
When doing jobs alone like this
because there were always 10 other people around me for two years
it felt a little lonely in the beginning
and I was nervous
whether it was alright early on
but nowadays I get used to it more and more
and I feel that I improved
as the opportunities to have all kinds of solo schedules keep increasing
and only then I realized for the first time
how much everyone has helped me
and how much we helped each other
Hence, the moment when I can feel that I'm glad to be active in a group
is when I'm having a schedule alone
For example, I finally realized by being alone
that if so-and-so was here, they would say this and that
so right now I feel once more
gratitude to everyone... yes
Tokyo Calendar
subs by @pompom_lotus