Itchy ah, it's like an electric shock
Itchy ah, it's love
JUNKI:
Kusuguttai yo ne, tere warai suru kimi
[It’s tickling, you're smiling bashfully]
MAME:
Kore ga koi tte yatsu kana
[I wonder if this is love?]
MAME:
Kimi no smile ni tokesou sa
[I seem to melt into your smile]
SUKAI:
Tada no kaiwa nanoni me wo awaserarenai
[It’s just a normal conversation, and yet I can't look at your eyes]
SHOSEI:
Itsumo no boku ja nai mitai
[I don’t feel like myself]
SUKAI:
Because of you
SHO:
La-la-la-la kuchizusamu fukuranda kokoro ga
[La-la-la-la I sing to myself, my swelling heart]
REN:
Aozora ni ukande
[Floats up to the blue sky]
KEIGO:
Pon to hajiketa shunkan
[With a pop, the moment it bursts]
JUNKI:
Koi ga hajimaru mahou wa
[The magic that started our love]
REN:
Futari no mystery
[Is our mystery]
JUNKI/TAKUMI:
Kimi no yasashisa, kimi no koe, kimi no te, touch!
[Your kindness, your voice, your hand, touch!]
Itchy ah, it's like an electric shock
Doushiyou?
[What should I do?]
KEIGO:
Te ni furetara
[If I touch your hand]
Itchy ah, it's like an electric shock
MAME:
Unmei no yokan, just touch
[Premonition of destiny, just touch]
Itchy ah, it's like an electric shock
JUNKI:
Just touch
Itchy ah, it's love
SHION:
Wakarunda tsunaida te de
[I understand from our connected hands]
SHION:
Kimi no itoshii hitomi dake de
[Just from your lovely eyes]
SYOYA:
Kotoba wa iranai kara
[Because I don’t need words]
SYOYA:
I’ll stay with you
TAKUMI:
La-la-la-la kuchizusamu fukuranda kokoro ga
[La-la-la-la I sing to myself, my swelling heart]
SUKAI (SHOSEI):
Shabondama mitai ni
[Just like soap bubbles]
SHOSEI:
Pon to hajiketa shunkan
[With a pop, the moment it bursts]
SHO (REN):
Koi ga hajimaru mahou wa (futari no mystery)
[The magic that started our love (is our mystery)]
JUNKI/TAKUMI:
Kimi no yasashisa, kimi no koe, kimi no te, touch!
[Your kindness, your voice, your hand, touch!]
Itchy ah, it's like an electric shock
Doushiyou?
[What should I do?]
TAKUMI:
Te ni furetara
[If I touch your hand]
Itchy ah, it's like an electric shock
KEIGO:
Unmei no yokan
[Premonition of destiny]
RUKI:
Nando datte koi ni ochiru hajimete no kankaku
[I fall in love again and again, a sensation I'd never felt before]
SYOYA:
Kimi no yubisaki ni fureru to, all day, all night
[When I touch your fingers, all day, all night]
SHION:
Itchy ah, it's like an electric shock
Ichi byou mo muda ni wa shitakunai yo
[I don’t want to waste a single second]
JUNKI:
Setsuna no shunkan
[A fleeting moment]
JUNKI:
Mou sukoshi dake soba ni itai yo
[Just a little bit more, I want to stay by your side]
REN/JUNKI:
Kimi no yasashisa, kimi no koe, kimi no te, touch!
[Your kindness, your voice, your hand, touch!]
Itchy ah, it's like an electric shock
Doushiyou?
[What should I do?]
SHO:
Te ni furetara
[If I touch your hand]
Itchy ah, it's like an electric shock
REN:
Unmei no yokan, just touch
[Premonition of destiny, just touch]
Itchy ah, it's like an electric shock
MAME:
Just touch
Itchy ah, it's like an electric shock
MAME:
Just touch
Itchy ah, it's love
[Translation by Lima @casualima,
timing & formatting by Berry @BerryMagic_]