[Translation & romaji by Shin @cshinjam,
timing & formatting by Berry @BerryMagic_]
RUKI:
Unmei ni makasenai tayoru koto nai
[I won’t leave it to fate, it's undependable]
SYOYA:
Mienakute ii run up
[You don’t have to see it, run up]
SYOYA:
Jibun wo koete ike rise up
[Surpass yourself, rise up]
SHOSEI, SHION:
We go, we alright
KEIGO:
Moe agaru you na atsui kokoro de
[With a burning, passionate heart]
SUKAI:
Yume mita jibun ga ugoki dashita shunkan
[The moment I find my dream and start moving]
TAKUMI:
Isshun demo ii sa ichido dake de ii sa
[Even if it’s just for a moment, even if it’s just one time]
KEIGO (REN):
Te ni tsukamitai (sekai wo)
[I want to hold it in my hands (the world)]
SHO:
Unmei ni makasenai
[I won’t leave it to fate]
SUKAI:
Tayoru koto nai
[It's undependable]
MAME:
Mienakute ii run up
[You don’t have to see it, run up]
MAME:
Jibun wo koete ike rise up
[Surpass yourself, rise up]
REN:
We go, we alright
TAKUMI:
Mugen ni tobitai itsu made mo tomaru koto naku
[I want to fly endlessly, forever, never stopping]
SHO:
Kidou wo koe doko made mo kimi wo megakete
[Beyond the orbit, wherever you are, I’ll come for you]
REN:
We go up, we alright
Hikari wo oikakete
[Chasing the light]
JUNKI:
We go up, we alright
Genkai nante nai, we alright
[There’s no limit, we alright]
SHION:
I’m chasing hikari oe
[I’m chasing beyond the light]
SHION:
Tobikoe, ready to unlock the wings
[Jumping, ready to unlock the wings]
SHOSEI:
Yume wo jitsugen dekiru sono mabayui mirai wa kono te ni
[I can make my dreams real, that dazzling future is in these hands]
SYOYA:
Oh yeah
SHOSEI:
Yume wo jitsugen dekiru sono mabayui mirai wa kono te ni
[I can make my dreams real, that dazzling future is in these hands]
SYOYA:
Oh yeah
It's coming to prime time, ay, habatake tooku ni right now
[It's coming to prime time, ay, fly far away right now]
RUKI:
Matte ita shunkan ga kiteiru shine uchuu e
[The moment we have been waiting for is coming, shine into space]
RUKI:
We rockin’ around the star
SUKAI:
Nagai yoru hate no yume de mita
[I saw it in a dream at the end of a long night]
MAME:
Kiseki yori motto kiseki no you na
[Even more miraculous than a miracle]
KEIGO:
Hateshinai jikan wo hashiri tsudzukete
[Running through endless time]
REN (JUNKI):
Me ni yakitsuketai (sekai wo)
[I want to sear it into my memory (the world)]
SHO:
Unmei ni makasenai
[I won’t leave it to fate]
SUKAI:
Tayoru koto nai
[It’s undependable]
MAME:
Mienakute ii run up
[You don’t have to see it, run up]
MAME:
Jibun wo koete ike rise up
[Surpass yourself, rise up]
TAKUMI:
We go, we alright
MAME:
Jibun wo koete ike rise up
[Surpass yourself, rise up]
TAKUMI:
We go, we alright
REN:
Mugen ni tobitai
[I want to fly endlessly]
REN:
Itsu made mo tomaru koto naku
[Forever, never stopping]
JUNKI:
Kidou wo koe
[Beyond the orbit]
JUNKI:
Doko made mo kimi wo megakete
[Wherever you are, I’ll come for you]
SHOSEI:
Can you see me, right now, right there
Minna ga mireru you ni
[So that everyone can see it]
SHION:
Moeru honoo atsui mune kanjiru you ni everywhere
[So that I can feel the flames burning in my heart everywhere]
RUKI:
Kono kuukan sae mo, sono jikan sae mo
[Even in this space, even at that time]
SYOYA:
Koe egaiteta mirai sono kibou kanaeru you ni
[The future I envisioned beyond so I can make my wish come true]
TAKUMI:
Mugen ni tobitai
[I want to fly endlessly]
TAKUMI:
Itsu made mo tomaru koto naku
[Forever, never stopping]
SHO:
Kidou wo koe
[Beyond the orbit]
SHO:
Doko made mo kimi wo megakete
[Wherever you are, I’ll come for you]
REN:
We go up, we alright
Hikari wo oikakete
[Chasing the light]
JUNKI:
We go up, we alright
Genkai nante nai, we alright
[There’s no limit, we alright]