[Translation by Shin @cshinjam, timing/formatting by Berry @BerryMagic_]
TAKUMI:
Kokou nare, sorry I've changed
[Become aloof, sorry I've changed]
KEIGO:
Susunde iku like the boss
[Move forward like the boss]
KEIGO:
Parade no shuyaku ni nare, ore no stage
[Become the protagonist of the parade, it's my stage]
SYOYA:
Shikakeru Steppin’, kakugo kimeta jinsei wa muteki
[Provoke Steppin’, a determined life is invincible]
SHOSEI:
Diss ni ochi konderu hima wa nai ze
[I have no time to feel down from a diss]
SHION:
Misetsukeru ikizama
[Showing off is my way of life]
REN:
Right now
SHION:
Misetsukeru ikizama
[Showing off is my way of life]
REN:
Right now
SHO:
Tsumetai shisen to kotoba de korosou toshitemo muda da yo
[With cold gaze and words, even if you try to kill me it’s useless]
REN:
Right now
SHO:
Tsumetai shisen to kotoba de korosou toshitemo muda da yo
[With cold gaze and words, even if you try to kill me it’s useless]
SUKAI:
Zenbu netsu ni kae, boku wa moe agaru
[Turning everything into heat, I'll burn up]
Yatte miro yo I ain’t got damage
[Try me, I ain’t got damage]
Kiba wo muke kemono wa like a savage
[Bare your fangs, a beast is like a savage]
We’re on the another level
Oh yeah I Walk It Like I Talk It
Perfect mission for the trophy
Byou de kowasu barricade like a hurricane
[Barricade destroyed in seconds, like a hurricane]
MAME:
Yeah I Walk It Like I Talk It, takami mezashi
[Yeah I Walk It Like I Talk It, aiming high]
MAME:
Sky’s the limit genkai nado kaimu
[Sky’s the limit, we’re limitless]
SHION:
Moe sakaru honoo, moto moto so hot
[A blazing fire, naturally so hot]
SHION:
Tometai nara honki dase yo time’s up
[If you want to stop it, get serious, time’s up]
SUKAI:
Ta ni nai jinsei okuritai nara
[If you want to live a life like no other]
SHO:
Anzen ken mamoccha saki wa nai
[You can't get anywhere if you play it safe]
JUNKI:
Sonzai shinai chizu kaite ikou yo
[Let's draw a map that doesn't exist]
SYOYA:
Jidai furi kitte jigen koeru I’m gone
[Overturning the times, transcending the dimensions, I’m gone]
KEIGO:
Tsuki nuketa kui wo hito wa atezu ni
[No one can hit a stake that’s pierced too deep]
KEIGO:
Tada mi ageru darou
[And they can probably only look up]
JUNKI:
Mukai kaze no naka boku wa fuki areru
[In the face of a headwind, I'll blow up a storm]
Yatte miro yo I ain’t got damage
[Try me, I ain’t got damage]
Kiba wo muke kemono wa like a savage
[Bare your fangs, a beast is like a savage]
We’re on the another level
Oh yeah I Walk It Like I Talk It
Perfect mission for the trophy
Byou de kowasu barricade don’t be afraid
[Barricade destroyed in seconds, don’t be afraid]
JUNKI:
Shimeshite ageyou, all of my dreams come true
[Let me show you, all of my dreams come true]
TAKUMI:
Hateshinai michi wo
[An endless road]
REN:
Furi kaerazu ni susume
[Go on without looking back]
REN:
Genkai wo koeta sono saki wo mite mitai kara
[Because I want to see what’s beyond the limits]
RUKI:
I look at my dream approaching
Aruke ore dake no michi
[Walk down my own road]
SHOSEI:
Mottai buranai kotoba no toori
[Literally show off]
Cuz I Walk It Like I Talk It
Oh yeah I Walk It Like I Talk It
Perfect mission for the trophy
JUNKI:
Byou de kowasu barricade like a hurricane
[Barricade destroyed in seconds, like a hurricane]
MAME:
Yeah, I’m on my way, on my way, on my way, yeah yeah
SUKAI:
Ippun ichi byou ga showtime on the runway
[Each minute each second is showtime on the runway]
SHO, REN:
I gotta go straight, go straight, keep going
Oh yeah I Walk It Like I Talk It
Byou de kowasu barricade don’t be afraid
[Barricade destroyed in seconds, don’t be afraid]
JUNKI:
I Walk It Like I Talk It