3...
Keigo: His hand is huge!
2...1...
[Before Team Direct-to-Inn departs]
The road is long, so let's have a word of enthusiasm
Ok!
Ah?
Did he hibernate?
Don't do such a classic gag
[Restart]
I'll do it now
Do it!
Ruki look at me, I'm all ready to go
We're off to Winter Camp!~
We're off~
Is it ok to give this to us here?
Does anyone have a remote? To turn down the volume
My ears hurt, seriously
[Calling Ren]
Yes, the ingredients are...oden...
For real, right?
He's as loud as my mom
Right, loud like a mom
Mom goes 'HAH??'
What do you like the most in oden?
Good question
- Daikon for me
- Daikon for me too
Oh, daikon?
Mochi kinchaku
Ah, mochi kinchaku? It's yummy
I like potatoes
Wasn't it mochi kinchaku?
Oh potatoes isn't on the list!
No way, it isn't?
- Potatoes are yummy, right?
- They're yummy
- Wait, potatoes?
- Yeah
Heh~
There aren't potatoes in my hometown's oden
Maybe only in Kansai
Or maybe when you make it at home
[Keigo's chick melody quiz time]
It's quite high-tempo. A JO1 song?
A JO1 song. Ah~I want to give a hint. It's a JO1 song
The start is important!
[Everyone, try to guess as well]
The end doesn't matter, the start is important
Oh it's close! Try singing together once
Oh! You know it, don't you?
I can only think of 'Never Ending Story'
Wrong
Try stretching out the pauses
Ah, I see
[Difficult]
You must know it!
Takumi, you know it, right?
I don't know. I really don't know
Completely wrong
The correct answer is Run & Go
Isn't it a little wrong?
Wow!
- How can you make it so nicely?
- Look!
Wow!
[Screenshot time]
I'll break your heart
You've done it! You broke it in half, cleanly
♫ I'm going to show them myself, just as I am ♫
[Japanese version of 'Let it Go']
♫ Just as I am ♫
There's someone trying to make a snow dome for real
Wait wait wait...hey
Shall I tell you something, person from Okinawa?
A snowball fight is fun, but when it gets to your face it sucks
[By person from Nara]
It dampens the mood
Can you think about that?
[Before the snowball fight]
I got the duck too
Cute...look
Excuse me, we only have one snowball maker here
Sho: Then, I'll give you another
- Give us one
Keigo: You do have more!
There's no way we can throw such a cute duck!!
Sho: You can't throw that
I only can display it
Sho: You're gonna display it!?
Junki: He made a lot to display
[Thank you Takumi]
[After deciding on the rooms,
what was each room doing during break time?]
- With 4 of us, isn't it crazy?
- It's crazy
Now that we've settled down
Isn't it crazy, Shion?
What is?
This
Isn't it like during DOMINO?
Yeah
These 4...
We were the first 4 in DOMINO
[I see!]
This is just like...
It's coming! x2
Chibi Maruko-chan...
Teaming up with the Great Demon King Satan
[Tsurubo World Open!
Great excitement in STRANGER Room]
It's equal to that
Bubbles...
It's really bubbles!
It's definitely Syoya
Syoya is over there
[Bubbles flying from outside the window]
It's Syoya
He really likes 'Kimi no mama' so he'll be in CHALLENGER
[Room next door is CHALLENGER]
[Correct]
What would happen if we blow bubbles when it's cold?
I wonder...Let's do it!
I'm sleepy! We played too much in the snow
[Culprits of the bubbles]
Wow
They don't freeze
But if we do them non-stop, they'll probably freeze, right?
They're really pretty
[After bubbles time,
Relaxing time]
I wanted to build a snow dome~
I'm so happy we did both Summer camp & Winter camp~
It's all thanks to JAM
Will the next one be Spring camp?
We have to do Autumn camp too
♫ Do you wanna build a snowman~♫
[Talking about the horror movie Keigo watched recently]
Shosei: [Searching]
Really? I can't do it
Is it scary like 'bam!'
'Bam!'...not like that
Here here here...
It's impossible for me!
It was impossible even for me!
Even for Keigo-kun?
It was impossible even for me
How shall we sleep?
Shosei, you sleep here
[Shosei's spot]
Shosei also has to make dinner, we're all the same
[All of 'Just as you are queen' team assembled - except Mame]
[Special Segment]
We'll introduce what's in our bags
It's spilled like crazy
- In the meantime
- I'll start
Switch! I love Switch
Cable, charger
This is a must, isn't it? Camera. To make memories
That's all!
I'll go next
That's huge!
It seems like anything could come out
Anything can come of of this
After Produce101 ended, we go out often, right?
So I bought this bag
- Isn't this LV?
- It's LV
It's a classic. I use it often
First, we ate a lot on the way here, KitKat
Toiletries, cosmetics etc.
That's huge!
Toothbrush, many other items
Everything is properly organized
Keys
That's about it
Is it alright if I go next?
Sure
This, I use this very much and bring it pretty much everywhere
It's really cute
Toothbrush, mask, another mask, vitamins
Nasal spray, I use it everyday
Makeup pouch. I have a pouch in a pouch
There's still more?
This is the most important, me
Can badge
Hair clip
That's about it
Thank you for sharing
Next is Ruki
First, it's really cold so a scarf
Hat
You always use this
You use it often
I wore this during J-LOG as well
The price starts from 5000 yen
We have to brush our teeth everyday so,
electric toothbrush & toothpaste
Also, I'm particular about my hair so
The rinse type?
The kind of treatment you don't wash out
Before using the hairdryer
- And charger
- Right
That's all!
Whoa!!
I pack light
So few~!
I'm into local procurement, so I don't bring much but I buy at the area
Plus I'm the type who can endure
Then, let's go make dinner!
It's exactly these members
Just add Mame
We are the dinner-making members
Yay! Then let's go!
We will introduce what's in our luggage
Hello!
These are contacts. This is a hat I received from Sukai
That's nice
Yes
Doesn't it match well with this outfit?
- It matches this outfit
- It really matches
The staff from the drama handed me this as a prop
And after I told them I've always wanted this, they gave it to me
What do you mean 'you've always wanted it'
Eyemask
And a gadget to help train my lung capacity
I introduced it to him
POWERbreathe
This is to help spread my toes
That's cool I should buy it too
I use it when my feet are tired
I should buy it too
My headphones, and I changed the color here myself
[Syoya's customization]
This color. I made it navy
These are my glasses
Real glasses
The key case I use normally
This is the charger I use normally
This is the smartphone charger I use
It's the same!
Ah! That's nice
Sunscreen
Thermometer!
That's important
Signature stamp
That's no good
- Earphones
- AirPods
This is my favorite item, nasal stick
Nasal stick
Ah, here it is! Propolis
Our matcha
It's matcha
♫ It's surely fun~so I'll fly to the blue sky ♫
I have an open pack of whole grain flavor too
That has been our Winter Camp luggage introduction
I brought something interesting but it's gone somewhere
Didn't this bag use to have a ton of accessories on it?
I have moved that elsewhere
'Moved that elsewhere'
This is the bag I bought before I started working as an employee
Uwah you really love Ditto
I have a squashed croissant
Dangerous!
When is that from?
This morning x3
Does anyone have anything interesting?
Then, I have one
Should we take out the most interesting thing we have?
[Introducing contents of the bag X
Finding interesting things ???]
Nostalgic!
I think Ren-kun will definitely say this is nostalgic
Which?
[Can badge?]
Nostalgic!!
When Shion and I went for a schedule we received it
Right or left?
Right x2
Right is my signature stamp
That's not interesting
Me too, right or left?
Right
Korean won
Why
This is Japan
30,000 won!
30,000 won LOL
That's 3000 yen
I don't get you
Bringing out such a thing
It's scary, seriously
Why??
We're waiting for work
Speaking of which
- There it is
- I think I have it too
- What's the name?
- ISSEI
Mine has a heart
Only for me
This is what we should be bringing out
I have one more
What number? x2
Number 130!
- Number 86
- Takumi's is 86
If it wasn't this bag, I'd have more awesome things inside
Same
Right now, it's Don't Break the Ice JO1 championship match
Let's start
The championship match that does not end easily
I've done it!
Junki-kun may win this
If it can withstand this
That was close!!
Yay!
This is like...this!
It's cute
I won
[Championship match with 2 players - Junki's win]
Then next is...
Pop-up Pirate
Championship match [again]
It seems the younger player gets to go first
I'll start
Eh?
[CHALLENGER Room after horror appreciation]
The horror movie was scary
Can I take the middle bed?
The walls are scary! x2
Because they'll come out from the walls?
Yeah
The walls are scary
[Shosei enters]
I'm seriously scared
He's come!
I was just saying that I'm scared
[Scaredy-cat 1]
I'm so scared this is impossible
[Scaredy-cat 2]
That is like the video recording (in the horror movie)
It's kinda scary
Maybe something is reflected
I'm scared! Wait a minute!
This room is dangerous
Wait x2
This room is plain dangerous
Wait, wait, hey you!
If you say something like that I'd become scared
Wait a minute!
I became more scared
I'm scared
Let's play some music to go to sleep
- How about classical? - This is bad
[Big brother appears]
Sho: What happened?
Shosei came in, and there's a video here, right?
'Wait! Isn't this like just now!' he said
[Junki who tells his big brother about Shosei]
'It's just like that!' he said
[Okay~]
He's terrible
[On the other hand,
STRANGER room + Keigo]
Apparently (ghosts) gather at places where the
difference between noisy times and quiet times is large
That's why I heard there are a lot at school, karaoke etc.
Is that so
[Shosei, Sho]
It's scary, I don't want to go in
- It's fine
- I'm scared
It's scarier that you make me go in alone
What room is this? What...
Hurry up, come over here
The night of JO1 WINTER CAMP deepens