[In the previous part]
[Wake-up call by Ren & Sukai]
[After waking the members up...]
- Thank you for the meal
[Everyone eats breakfast together]
[Relaxation time after breakfast]
I'm wondering how each person
wants to spend their relaxation time
- Is there anything you want to do?
- What we want to do?
- Snowball fight
- Snowball fight?
- Yes
- We did that last time, right?
Igloo!
- You want to build an igloo?
- I do
So that it's warm
- Massage
- Massage?
- There's one right there
- Yes
Massage, eh?
But we're not doing that today
To decide what we'll do for our relaxation time today...
Yes
We'll have a scallop fishing showdown
[Applause]
So scallop fishing isn't the relaxation part
- It's just used to decide, right?
- That's right
[Scallop fishing showdown]
1) Challenge scallop fishing
2) Time limit is 3 min
3) Person who catches the most decides how to spend the afternoon
4) Will be split into 2 groups based on the amount caught
First, there are lots in here
We'll use these to decide the order that we will compete
Okay
[Lottery to decide the order]
1) Draw lots that have numbers 1~3 written
2) Split into 3 groups
3) Challenge scallop fishing starting from group 1
[Deciding groups and order]
- Those who got number 1?
[Announcing the numbers]
Here!
Those who got number 2?
Ohhh~
I'VE GOT THIS!!!
Those who got number 3
Here
- Oh~
- 3 of you
Let's start right away!
- Yeah!
[JO1 Scallop Fishing Showdown!]
Let's go~
- Well then!
- Yes
Are you ready to fish some scallops?!
YEAHHHHHHHH
[Fired up]
Ready, start!
Keigo is in my way
[Pushing him lol]
[Shosei GET]
- Wow
- You're good
[Observe Keigo's left hand]
[Security camera in operation]
[He grabbed the scallop with his bare hand!?]
- I got it!
[At the same time, Sho GET]
[Bad example | Good example]
- Hey! Don't get in my way!
- Don't get in my way!
[This time Keigo legitimately fishes it]
1 minute has passed
Do your best everyone~
[Observe Sukai's right hand]
[This time, Sukai grabs the scallop!?]
[Puts into Keigo's basket]
[Serious]
I've only got one
- Yay!
[Ren GET]
Finally got one
- This guy is stirring it!
[Keigo hinders by stirring the water in the tank]
[At the last second, Ren GET]
End!
It's over~
- You're great, Ren-kun
- I got it~
- Then...
[Announcing results]
- Starting from Shosei
- Yes
How many did you catch?
- I got 2!
- 2!
Wow
- I got 5
- 5?!
Though you were bothering others, you caught so many!
But actually...
I caught 2 of them with my bare hands
[Keigo properly owns up]
Then it's 3
I'm sorry, I'll return 2
- Did you really pick them with your hands?
- I really did
Next, Sho-kun
- I have 1!
- 1!
Ah~
Finally, Ren-kun
- I have 3!
- Whoa~
These 3 are legitimate
Then, the 2nd group
Ready, start!
Go Mame!
Oh I got it
Oh nice
- Nice, Junki-kun!
[Junki GET]
Take it off slowly
Oh!
You're so good!
[Shortly after, 2nd one GET]
Shall I aim for the one in the middle?
Oh that's good~
So close...
Nice one
- Oh you got it!
[Sukai GET]
- I got it...
- He got it!
- Isn't Junki too good at this?
[Junki GET again]
- Junki-kun is so good
[Mame's fish hook also...?]
End!
Starting from Syoya
I got....
Zero! Yay! (??)
Next, Mame
- Zero...
- Zero!
Then, Sukai
- I have 1 muscle
- 1 muscle?
- A man?
- He said it coolly
Lastly, Junki-kun
- I have 4!
- 4! Wow!
Bring it on!
He has the most so far
That's amazing
The time limit is 30 minutes
30 minutes!?
[Suddenly the rules changed??]
- You could catch them all
- Training?
It's become training?
- You can't go home till you catch them all
- We'll go home as pros
It'll take more time
- Well then
[Collecting themselves]
- Time limit is 3 minutes
- Yes
- Let's do our best
- We'll do our best
Scallop fishing, ready, start!
- I'll do my best!
- Go!
Player Tsurubo uses his wisdom to make the string shorter
Shosei come here
Shosei quickly
[Ruki GET]
You're good, Ruki!
Nice
Shion's method is very unique
You're pretty much grabbing it
[Splash!]
[So close!]
Shosei come here!
[Shosei call ♥]
[At the same time, Takumi caught a...?]
[Not a scallop but a sea snail!?]
Takumi caught one too!
Shosei!
[Shosei call again ♥]
- 30 seconds left!
[The two of them get along ♥]
End!
- Okay, the last one!
[At the last second, Takumi GET]
Let's announce the numbers starting from Shion
He's sulking
How many do you have?
To me, there are 5
To us it looks like zero
- Next, Ruki!
- Yes
[Big catch!!]
- I have 4!
- Wow!
Takumi-kun
- I have 2 + 1 (?)
- Whoa!
What do you mean?
I got a sea snail!
WOW!
1 sea snail = 5 points
That would make him the winner
The sea snail wouldn't let go!
Result announcement!
First place is...!
Oh?
[Rhythm Squad Appears!]
[DJ too!?]
Me!
No fair!
- Eh??
- I'm sorry
It's because of that unusual thing I caught
There was a strange little roll in there
Apparently that's 5 points
Wow~
[Takumi who got 1st place, can choose
how to spend his relaxing time]
1) Ride a horse carriage around the park
2) Take it easy in the lounge
What will you choose, Takumi-kun?
What should I choose?
Both are wins
Whether you prefer something active or laid back
I have decided
Going around the park in a horse carriage!
[Clap clap]
[Scallop fishing showdown results]
[Top 5 members will ride the carriage,
bottom 6 will go to the lounge]
[Carriage team | Lounge team]
[Split into 2 teams for relaxation time ♪]
We have arrived and the carriage will be arriving soon
Oh
What image do you have of a carriage?
- Pumpkin [Romanticist]
- Ah, a pumpkin
Cinderella
- Unicorn [maiden]
- Ah, unicorn!
A unicorn horse with horns would be cool
Right, and they can fly
- Oh!
- Eh?
- Wow!
- It's here!
- Wow! - It's huge!
[Today's carriage makes an appearance]
- Hello!
- It's huge! And fast
[Taken aback by the unexpected size?]
Wait, stop
- Can I touch it?
- Go ahead
- Wah so cute!
[Emotional first time touching a horse]
- I like this
- You like it?
- I like it
[Putting his hands inside the mane]
- Is it warm?
- It's warm!
Right? It's warm, right?
Kirara-chan!
Wah it's warm!
[Prince who naturally becomes familiar with the horse]
Cute~
We'll be in your care
- Pardon the intrusion
[Heading into the carriage right away]
Wow!
- It's warm
[Warm and toasty from the firewood stove]
We'll be in your care
- Wow!
[Off we go!]
Wow wow wow!
- It's faster than I expected!
[Excited by the first time riding in a carriage]
Off we go~!
[At the same time, the lounge team is...]
- Shall we go?
- Let's go!
- The lounge is right in front of you
[Members heading to the lounge]
- Where?
- Isn't this it?
- This?
- That's it
- Wow!
- We've arrived!
[Lounge by the waterside]
Hello, pardon the intrusion
[Vibes like a private house]
What's this?
Whoa!
The wind is amazing!
Wow!
[Discovered something at the stunning lounge terrace!]
Hey everyone, there's something growing here
- Sho-kun, quickly!
- What is it?
Something's growing
What's this!
- He's reaching his limit
[Sukai entertains with a handstand]
Wow!
Today we can take it easy here
For real?
Ready, go
Thank you for the meal
It looks so rich
[Apple juice]
Delicious!
- The one that looks like choco?
- It's fruit and choco
- Hm?
[What is this snack?]
- It's fruit
- Shall we try the choco?
[What is this snack?]
Yep
This place feels great
- It's choco!
- Yum
- Oh?
- It's good!
It's dried apple with a chocolate coating
Uwah, it's yummy!
- Oh, so that's what it is
- Yum! So this is apple?
It's dried apple with a chocolate coating
He already said that
- He just said that
- Ahaha~
I'll try one more
The one without chocolate
[Checking the taste]
Ah, this is that...
Is this apple?
It's dried apple without a chocolate coating
Oh~
Then it's just apple
This is that...!
It's dried apple without a chocolate coating
How many times are you gonna do that?
It's the same
Ah! Isn't that...?
- The carriage!
- Isn't it fast?
[The carriage that Takumi and the others are riding goes past]
Huh? Are those our members?
- Our members are there
- Where?
- Hey~!
- What are those guys doing, seriously?
HOW DOES IT FEEL RIDING IT?
THIS ONE DOESN'T HAVE CHOCOLATE COATING
This one has it!
As if they can tell!
DRIED APPLE FRUIT!
[Did their voices reach them?]
They keep saying stuff but I can't tell what
What did ya say??
WHAT DID YA SAY?
Nah it's impossible
[They didn't manage to have a conversation]
- Wow
[Kirara-chan working hard to pull them along]
I wonder if she gets tired?
Thank you Kirara-chan
- Isn't it tough?
- I wonder if she's okay
We are approaching a bridge
Wow
Do your best just a bit more~
[Keigo who encourages Kirara-chan]
- The scenery is amazing!
- Oh, beautiful
It's like a fantasy world
A fantastic scenery
This is amazing
The carriage will sway a little
[Starts to sway]
[Kirara-chan starts to run downhill!]
She's letting us have fun
Thank you!
This is so calming
You're right, this swaying is calming
- We've arrived
[Carriage stroll END]
Thank you very much
[Tired?]
Cheers!
[With apple juice]
Delicious!
It was amazing
Thanks to Kirara, we got to see the beautiful surroundings
Yeah
This is a great place
It's peaceful and the air is fresh
We had fun!
Thank you Kirara!
[Spending a relaxing time at the lounge...]
[Member excited by the luxury apple juice gifted to them!]
- That's the one I was gonna buy earlier!
- Thank you very much
Not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet
[How much are you planning to fill?]
Stop
Thanks
It's so rich!
We have bartender Ohira
Ah! It smells so apple-y!
I'm wondering where they extracted this flavor from
It's totally different from the one earlier
Delicious!
Completely different
[While playing at the balcony...]
You guys, it's dangerous
He's the dad
Papa
[Sukai who suddenly becomes the Papa]
- Be careful
You'll fall in
Be careful
Papa!
[Parent and child skit??]
Papa you've been drinking too much since the afternoon
It looks like orange juice
Have you already reached the age to drink too?
[It's juice]
Mmm!
Papa! I'm already...
45 years old!
[He was playing a 45 year old son]
[With a beautiful scenery and apple juice,
The relaxed talk inevitably shifts to about Aomori]
Places with a lot of nature have beautiful skies
It is
- The night sky was amazing
- It was
The view from the outdoor bath was amazing
- We could see everything
- The Orion was visible
In Tokyo if you look up, it's just full of clouds
The city is too bright
- Ah, that could be a reason
- Yeah, so you can't see the sky well
Is Shion legit sleeping?
Shion is sleeping
I have been sleeping
This place is comfortable
It really is
- Look, there's a drone
- Huh?
It's our drone
Bye bye!
[Dinnertime]
We all had fun at our various activities
How was it, Takumi-san?
I've never been able to try something like this before, so it was really fun
We rode a horse and went one round around the park
Did you hear us talking to you?
- We did
- But we couldn't tell what you were saying
But apparently Keigo-kun heard it
You said "What silly thing are y'all doing?!"
- We never said such terrible thing
- You didn't?
That's what I thought
He just says whatever he likes
We couldn't hear
We rode Kirara-chan
Kirara-chan?
That's the horse's name
I see
She has so much power!
How many horsepower do you think she has?
One horsepower
Alright then...
I think we're all hungry too
Have a look at this
- Amazing!
[Super luxurious dinner]
This has been prepared for us
What is this?
- Let's eat!
- Yes!
Ready, go
Thank you for the meal
This is amazing
Let's do cheers
Cheers~
Our breakfast was luxurious too, but this is special
- Right?
- Yum!
[Yum!]
Are these the scallops we caught in the afternoon?
Probably not
When JO1 eats good food everyone stops talking
So good!
[Yum ♥]
[Good]
I want to go around the country with everyone and eat all the foods
Eat all the delicious foods across the country with the members
That's right
[It was too delicious that everyone continued to eat quietly]
[What's after the meal...?]
[Winter Camp ends with members enjoying free time]
[How was Winter Camp?]
This time Sukai joins us too
And we ate a lot of good food
And it's also my first time in Aomori
So it was really fun
The greatness of Aomori, like the food and scenery
Being able to share that with everyone
It was a joyous time
It felt like a family trip
I was tasked to wake the members
You could see the individuality of each member
Once again, I felt like I could see the members comfortable selves
As an older brother
I could see the younger brothers' growth
It was a warm and fluffy Winter Camp
[What's your impression of Aomori?]
- Onsen and the fresh air
The scenery is beautiful too
The seafood is delicious too
The apples are delicious too
I'm really satisfied
The food is so delicious I could eat it forever
I'm sure I'll put on weight in Aomori
The stars are beautiful and the air is fresh
I was stunned
I would like to come again
That's how nice this place is
[What do you want to try in the next Winter Camp?]
- I've only tried it twice, but I want to try snowboarding
Snowboarding
I've tried snowboarding once
But I only have memories of falling on my butt
But now, I think I could do it
I want to try it while being taught by the members
I want to make an ice temple
[Where do you want to go for the next Winter Camp?]
- Hokkaido
- I think I want to go to Hokkaido
If I were to build an ice temple...
I want to build it with all my might at a place like Hokkaido
Please take us to the Himalayas
[One word to describe "With Us"?]
- Bond
Us being here is also thanks to JAM
In our daily activities
We align our steps
To walk towards our various goals
Aside from JAM, I also have the members
And though you can't see them, the staff who are supporting us
It's a song with all of that packed into it, so my word is "bond"
[What made you feel a bond with members recently?]
- Arena Tour
We managed to complete KIZUNA
We managed to perform in front of everyone as 11 including Sukai for the first time
And we managed to complete it without injury or sickness
So that was a moment that made me feel the bond
It was something we all wanted to do
And that was granted to us by JAM
So there's a feeling of everyone becoming One
[What left an impression on you from "With Us" MV filming?]
- We started makeup at 3am I think?
There was a scene that I was running in the early morning
At a place like a sandy beach
Me, Sho-kun & Junki-kun
Running in the desert when it was pitch black
Then there was a scene where I encountered Sho-kun
We laughed a little
That was fun
Jasmine-chan who showed up in the MV was the cutest
She was so cute and friendly to people
I was moved
[Make a poem with (WI)-(T)h-(U)-(S)]
- This is difficult...
W?
"I (W)as happy"
"You and (I)"
"(T)ill the very end"
Till the very end...
"I love (U)"
Till the very end I love u...
"(S)o much"
Is that okay?
W-i-t-h-u-s
"(Wi)nter Camp"
"(T)oo cold"
"(U)ndoubtedly tomorrow is cold too"
"(S)orry..."
"(W)ow I'm happy"
"(I)'m always with everyone
"Zunki-kun is laughing (T)oo"
"My love for (U) is gonna overflow"
"I love you (S)o much! JO1!"
W...W...
"(W)e"
I...
"(I)n our usual way"
"(T)ill the very end"
"(U)nwind and have fun"
S...
"(S)pend a great time together!"
Yep
"(Wi)n-win"
Win-win...
Win-win "(T)ogether forever"
"(U)pbeat and cheerful"
"(S)o amazing JO1"
That's it
Yes, I made it
[We had a lot of fun in this Winter Camp in Aomori!]
[It's all thanks to JAM!]
[Thank you JAM ♥]
[Translation by @cshinjam]