[English translation and romaji transliteration by Shin @cshinjam, timing and formatting by Berry @BerryMagic_]
MAME:
Yeah, we’ll be together
RUKI:
Itsu made mo baby
[Forever baby]
SHION:
Kimi wa oboete iru no
[Do you remember]
SHION:
Bokura ga deatta hi wo
[The day we met]
SYOYA:
Sorezore no yume kasanatte
[Each of our dreams overlapped]
SYOYA:
Soko kara hajimatta ne
[And it started from there]
SHOSEI:
Takusan no mahou ga
[Lots of magic]
SHOSEI:
Bokura wo musunde
[Tied us together]
SUKAI:
Hitotsu dake no kiseki ga deki agaru
[And a single miracle was created]
REN:
Come with me, everything's all right
Kimi to ireba
[As long as I’m with you]
SHO:
Donna toki mo With us
[At all times With us]
KEIGO:
Tomo ni iku yo With us
[Go together With us]
JUNKI:
Kasoku suru keshiki no saki
[Beyond the scenery that accelerates past us]
JUNKI:
Souzou koeru mirai e with us
[Is a future that surpasses our imagination with us]
TAKUMI:
Shinjitai with us, with us
[I want to believe with us, with us]
KEIGO:
Onaji yume mezasu nakama ga iru kara
[Because we have friends aiming for the same dream]
MAME:
Nagai toki hete bokura koko ni tateta ne
[After a long time, we could stand here]
SUKAI:
Kurai yoru demo so shine
[Even in the dark night we shine]
SUKAI:
Kata wo narabete go high
[Stand shoulder to shoulder and go high]
RUKI:
Tsurai hibi nori koe
[Overcoming the tough days]
RUKI:
Hashirou sono mirai e
[Let’s run towards that future]
JUNKI:
Here with me, we will be all right
REN:
Be all right
JUNKI:
Here with me, we will be all right
Soba ni ireba
[If you’re by my side]
REN:
Atsui mune de With us
[With a passionate heart With us]
MAME:
Tomo ni sakebu With us
[Shout together With us]
JUNKI:
Nuri kasane egaku iro wa
[The overlapping colors that we paint]
JUNKI:
Kitto bokura wo musubu with us
[Surely tie us together with us]
KEIGO:
Mamoritai with us, with us
[I want to protect this with us, with us]
TAKUMI:
Kawarazu ni always together
[Same as ever, always together]
REN:
Itsu made mo always together
[Forever, always together]
JUNKI:
Kawarazu ni always together
[Same as ever, always together]
JUNKI:
We’re gonna be together
SHO:
Doko made mo with us, with us
[No matter where we go with us, with us]
RUKI:
Mada kore kara ga
[From here on]
RUKI:
Kimi to boku ga egaku drama
[The drama you and I envision]
SHOSEI:
Kono michi ga futashika demo
[Even if the road is uncertain]
SHOSEI:
Tachi domarazu arukou
[Let's walk without stopping]
SYOYA:
Bokura wa hi ni hi ni grow up, tagai ni go up
[Day by day we grow up, we both go up]
SYOYA:
Issho nara ikeru yo TOP made baby
[If we’re together we can go to the TOP baby]
SHION:
Mezasu toko made nobotte
[Climbing up until our goal]
SHION:
Onaji keshiki nagameyou
[Let’s gaze at the same view]
SHION:
Yeah mou ikkai baby
[One more time baby]
SHO:
Donna toki mo With us
[At all times With us]
MAME:
Tomo ni iku yo With us
[Go together With us]
TAKUMI:
Kasoku suru keshiki no saki
[Beyond the scenery that accelerates past us]
TAKUMI:
Souzou koeru mirai e with us
[Is a future that surpasses our imagination, with us]
JUNKI:
Shinjitai with us, with us
[I want to believe with us, with us]
SHO:
Kawarazu ni always together
[Same as ever, always together]
REN:
Itsu made mo always together
[Forever, always together]
MAME:
Kawarazu ni always together
[Same as ever, always together]
MAME:
We’re gonna be together
[We’re gonna be together]
TAKUMI:
Doko made mo with us, with us
[No matter where we go with us, with us]
[Find more fansubs at
@ArchiveforJAM on Twitter]