[Disclaimer: Lots of talking over and inaudible parts so
please excuse inaccuracies and non-translated parts]
[Video starts at 06:40]
Sho: Hello everyone. Ready, go
Go to the Top, it's JO1!
Sho: Right, for what reason are we doing today's livestream?
Sho: Mame!
Mame: Yes
Mame: Umm...Releasing on 25th May, our 2nd album KIZUNA's
Mame: Title track 'With Us' MV will be released at 18:00!
Sho: Right! And we have some drinks, so shall we have a toast?
Yes!
Sho: Yes! The drinks are in front of you so please grab one freely
Junki: Yes~
Ren: Which would you like?
Takumi: Then...this one
Ok!
Shion: The cranberry juice...afterwards you can't (inaudible)
Ren: These are definitely the same
Ren: I want the one with the curly straw
Keigo: Where's mine?
Takumi: Keigo-kun's...
Keigo: Where's mine?!
Keigo: Mine...!
Junki: JO1 cheers?
Sho: JO1 cheers. Then, Keigo
Junki: Let's go in this direction
Syoya: It ends with Sho-kun
'J'
Takumi: Broadcast accident
Takumi: Suddenly
'J'
Takumi: Sudden broadcast accident
'JO1~'
Keigo: The rhythm is...
Itadakimasu~
Takumi: It's difficult to drink
Syoya: First time I've seen a curly straw like this
Sho: The straw has a shape
Takumi: (The drink) takes a while
Sho: We did an IG live and TikTok live from 16:00
Sho: But there are also others who are first seeing us here
Sho: So shall we do a brief greeting
Yes
Sho: Here is the greeting camera
Junki: Wow wow
Shosei: Ah, there?
Sukai: Wah! It's here
Junki: Wow
Sho: Yes, we'll introduce ourselves one by one
Junki: Okay
Sho: Haisai everyone-
Sho: Ah, sorry I hit you
Takumi: I'm fine
Sho: Haisai!
Sho: I'm the leader Yonashiro Sho, nice to meet you
Sho: Please enjoy yourselves today!
Sho: Okay, Keigo
Keigo: I'm JO1's Sato Keigo, nice to meet you
Shosei: I'm JO1's-
Keigo: Sato Keigo~
Shosei: Hey wait wait
Shosei: I'm JO1's Ohira Shosei
Shosei: Let's have fun
Sukai: I'm JO1's Kinjo Sukai
Sukai: Yes, and the 3 of us together are...
Sukai & Keigo: The 3 of us together are...
Sho: Ready, go
Sukai: Avocado Salad
Sukai: Eh? The wire can't stretch any further
Sho: No, Junki is...
Ren: Junki is stopping it
Syoya: Careful of the drinks
Sho: Careful of the drinks
Ruki: Hello, I'm JO1's Shiroiwa Ruki, nice to meet you
Mame: Yes, I'm JO1's O-Mame
All: Mame! Cute~
Mame: I'm Mame, nice to meet you
Syoya: I'm JO1's...
Syoya: Oh it's here
Syoya: Sushi...not
Syoya: I'm the subleader Kimata Syoya, nice to meet you
Shion: Yes hello, I'm JO1's ikemen, nice to meet you
Ren: He doesn't say his name!
Sho: Say your name
Ren: His name is Shion
Ren: Hello, I'm Kawashiri Ren
Ren: Everyone, we have a huge iPad here
Ren: If you comment, we can read it!
Ren: Yes, everyone please leave comments!
Junki: Yes, I'm JO1's BRAIN, Kono Junki
Junki: BRAIN means 'brain'
Junki: I'm the smart one in JO1, please remember that
Syoya: That's worrisome
Takumi: Hello, I'm JO1's BLOOD, Kawanishi Takumi
Takumi: BLOOD
Ren: BLOOD means?
Takumi: Um...'blood'
Junki: Ah it's 'blood'?
Shion: JO1's blood, right?
Sukai: Brain and Blood
Shion: JO1's blood
Sho: You can put it back already
Takumi: Okay
Junki: Yes, thank you
Shosei: Thank you
Sho: Okay, now that we've finished self-introductions
Sho: We would like to talk about 'With Us'
Okay
Sho: Right, our 2nd album KIZUNA's 'With Us'
Sho: After this, the MV will...
Ren: Yes
Sho: Yes
Ren: At 18:00, right?
Sho: At 18:00 it will be streamed
Yes
Sho: We'll talk about how it was like
Okay!
Sho: How was it? It's already our 2nd album
It's fast!
Ruki: It feels like we did 'Shine A Light' just the other day
Sho: We released our 1st album and now it's already the 2nd
Sho: This time it's called KIZUNA (bonds) plus Sukai has returned
Ruki: That's right
Sho: The lyrics of 'With Us' are really nice, after all
Yeah
Sho: Please comment the lyrics you think are good and paid attention to
Junki: I have one
What is it?
Junki: Really, from the start...
Junki: ...Was it the start?
Junki: Um...I...Shion's part?
♫ Do you remember~ ♫
Junki: 'Do you remember the day we met'
Junki: 'Each of our dreams overlapped'
Junki: 'And it started from there'
Junki: It's really...
Shion: Seriously?
Junki: It's like what JO1 & JAM has created together up till now
Right
Junki: And at the end, it's like we will envision the future together
Junki: I think it's a wonderful song
Junki: I love it
Wonderful
Sho: And our MV hasn't been released yet, but there was teaser 1 & 2
Yes
Sho: It stimulates the imagination
Sho: A curious teaser
Sho: Everyone, you've already watched it, right?
I've watched it!
Sho: That was quite amazing, right?
Shion: It was amazing
Ren: I like that thing
Sho: That?
Ren: It spins and becomes a merry-go-round
Shosei: That's cool
Syoya: We worked hard for that scene
Ren: We worked hard to spin it
Junki: Syoya spun it?
Syoya: That's right
Junki: Oh is that so?
Syoya: I built everything
Sho: That's too amazing
Keigo: And actually..!
Actually?
Keigo: This time, I'm the protagonist
Huh?
Syoya: First time I've heard this
Shion: Possible
Shosei: Really?
Sho: This face
Keigo: There's no such thing
Sho: It's not
Keigo: Everyone is the protagonist, I'm sorry
Sho: That's right
Shosei: Cool~
Sho: By the way, earlier we did IG & TIkTok live, right?
Sho: What did y'all talk about?
Sho: We talked about what we did during Golden Week
Ren: We did too
Sho: The echo was a little
Keigo: Ours was more interesting, right?
Keigo: Let's ask, which was more interesting?
Junki: Between IG & TikTok, which was more interesting
Sho: For ours, due to the echo our voices were kinda
Junki: That's right
Ren: But we did ours at the same location
Keigo: They sure are making excuses
Sho: Was it so hyped?
Keigo: Ours was really hyped, right?
Sho: Everyone, please comment which was more hyped up
Keigo: For those that watched neither, they can just enjoy here
Sho: That's right
Junki: They said Instagram
Ren: Wow. I only saw one Instagram
Junki: There's more TikTok
Shosei: It says TikTok
Keigo: There's more TikTok after all
Junki: There's quite a lot of TikTok
Shion: Hang on, there's only TikTok
Keigo: But if you mix us, like water & oil, we'll match
Water & oil don't mix
Junki: No no, especially those 2 you can't
Sho: We'll pass the camera around
Sho: Be careful of this
Sho: Should we put the drinks below?
That's dangerous
It'll spill
Sho: 2nd Album 'With Us'...
Sho: Everyone look there
Keigo: Let's say something about 'With Us'
Sho: About 'With Us' or 2nd album songs
Junki: I'm happy we get to release our 2nd album
That's right
Keigo: How is it, Mame?
Mame: Yes!
Keigo: Anything about the 2nd album?
Mame: 2nd album?
Keigo: Songs that you like etc.
Mame: Ehhh.....it's that...umm.....
Mame: 'Walk It Like (I) Talk It'
That was dangerous
Mame: Is it correct?
It's correct
Sho: That song is nice isn't it?
Mame: It is
What do you like about it?
Mame: The dance!
Keigo: Oh that's great
Shion: Oh the dance is epic
Keigo: It's real hyped
Keigo: I bet if we perform it at a live, it'll be so hyped up
Sho: Please look forward to it
Sho: And Junki, is there a song you have in mind?
Junki: Eh?
Junki: What is it?
'What is it?'
Sho: It's this, right?
Junki: 'Touch'?
Ren: 'Touch?'
Keigo: What memories do you have about 'Touch'?
Junki: We can't talk about 'Touch' yet, so
Keigo: So we can't "touch" on it yet?
Junki: I would like to keep it that way
Junki: Wait I'm getting red
Junki: This is Sho-kun's fault
Shosei: It's a good song, right?
It's a good song
Keigo: What about Sukai?
Sukai: Yes
Keigo: Is there a song you like?
Sukai: A song I like?
Sukai: 'Ryuuseiu' (Meteor Shower)
Ahh 'Ryuuseiu'!
I get it! It's a great song
Keigo: Which part?
Sukai: Which part?
Sukai: The lyrics are...
Shion: The words he doesn't say, I will translate
Ren: Ah, you'll translate?
Shion: Go ahead
Shion: 'Those who are not watching now'
Shion: 'You know that you're dumb right?'
Scary!
That's not an explanation
Sukai: But really, the lyrics are great
The lyrics are great
Sukai: 'It would be great if your wish and mine could cross paths'
AH~
Sukai: That kind of image
Ren: Your 'AH~' is too loud
Junki: AH~
Junki: Ren-kun what about you?
Ren: My favorite is...
Ren: 'ZERO'
AHHH~
Ren: Your 'AH' is loud
Keigo: You mean you have NO favorite?
Ren: Huh? Well, let's just say it's so
Junki: it's a song called 'ZERO'
Keigo: We have a song called 'ZERO'
Keigo: What do you like about it?
Ren: Who are you asking?
Keigo: Ren-kun
Ren: Ah, me
Ren: The lyrics are beautiful
Shion: You're so right
Ren: I think it's best conveyed listening to the song while following the lyrics
Sho: For the 2nd album, we want them to pay attention to the lyrics
Sho: Pay attention to it and let us know what you think
Keigo: Lots of emotions were put in
Sho: The 11 of us put in our emotions to sing
Sho: Let's read the comments too
Okay
Keigo: Rukkun, read the comments
Ruki: Shion will read it
Shion: The comments are seriously fast
Keigo: Whatever you manage to see
Shion: Whatever I manage to see
Ruki: Oh, random
Shion: 'Junki~'
Junki: That...thank you it's Junki
Shion: 'Ruki-kun are you drinking coffee?'
Ruki: This is cola
Sho: It's cola
Shosei: Can you drink coffee?
Ruki: Recently I can. The one Sho-kun recommended
Sho: For the first time, during practice
Sho: He said he was sleepy so I made him drink coffee...not *made* him but...
Ruki: *made* me drink lol
Sho: He can't drink it black
Ruki: Right
Sho: But the coffee I make is the only one he can drink
Sho: Black
Shosei: It's good
All: Really?
Sho: Shosei drank it too, right?
Keigo: Is there something different about this black coffee?
Sho: Yes
Syoya: That...right?
Sho: The taste right?
Syoya: That is yummy
Sho: I have one that's a little fruity
Sho: I made him drink it
Sho: Saying I *made* him drink it is a little...
Made him drink it?
Syoya: He blessed it
Sho: What is it...
Keigo: You recommended it, right?
Sho: Right, I recommended it
Sho: After I recommended it, he drank it
Sho: He gulped it down
Sho: Yeah...
Sho: I was happy
Shosei: It's delicious
Ruki: It means Sho-kun is good at making coffee
Sho: That's what it means. Wonderful
Sukai: Ah! There's a comment
Sho: Yes
Sukai: Umm...it's a good one
Sukai: Shosei, do a funny face
Shion:  Uwah!! That's a good one!
Sho: We only saw it from afar
Sukai: Ah! I found a comment
Sukai: Shosei, do a funny face~
Shion: Shosei, it's great
Sukai: It's great
Shion: Really great
Sukai: Today is going well
Shosei: I feel like I'm gonna lose various things
Shion: Various things?
Keigo: You will lose Golden Week
Shion: You just lost half of the member's LINE
Shosei: That would be the toughest
Sho: You did well
Junki: 'I'm watching from Huis Ten Bosch'
Wow!
Keigo: Really?
Junki: Where is Huis Ten Bosch?
Sho: Ehh??
Syoya: It's like a resort
Keigo: If you don't know, don't say it
Ren: In Nagasaki
Sho: Nagasaki
Junki: I thought it sounded like somewhere amazing
Keigo: You didn't know?
Takumi: 'Thought it sounded amazing...'
Shion: That's embarrassing
Sho: I thought you knew!
Keigo: You didn't know??
Junki: It sounded amazing
Takumi: 'Sounded amazing...'
Sho: It seemed like you knew it
Sho: Are you watching from Huis Ten Bosch?
Junki: Huis Ten Bosch is amazing
Keigo: Do you really not know?
Junki: Nagasaki Huis Ten Bosch?
[*It's a theme park]
Shosei: It says 'I'm Dubai JAM!'
Shosei: Thank you for watching from far away!
Keigo: Thank you!
Sho: Thank you!
Sho: Watching all the way from Huis Ten Bosch
Keigo: Enough of where you're watching from, we already did that
Ren: Wow, it says 'Shosei you've worked hard', 'Shosei you're cute!'
Shion: There's lots of 'Shosei's the best'
Shosei: So kind!
Ren: It says 'Shosei is the cutest in the world'
Ren: But no one said you were funny
Shosei: You didn't have to mention that
Sho: He made quite a deep wound
Shosei: They followed up perfectly for me but I got attacked here
Keigo: What did everyone do for Golden Week?
Shosei: Oh! I wanna know
Junki: It's also what they are doing/going right now, right?
Sho: By the way, does anyone know what day it is today?
Junki: We know it, don't we?
Sho: Those who answered earlier, don't say it
Sho: Do you know what day it is? Keigo
Keigo: Greenery!
Junki: Ahh it's close
Ren: Does Shosei know?
Sho: Shosei knows it?
Shosei: Ohira Shosei Day
Shion: Oh no
Shion: Now you probably lost your family too
Junki: Hey! Dummy!
Shion: I mean their LINE
Shion: He lost his family's LINE
Junki: Family's LINE
Shion: He lost it
Shosei: Plus I lost 100 fans
Keigo: Then Takumi may know the actual day
Takumi: I really do
Sho: He answered it earlier
Keigo: Ah he did
Sho: Right
Sho: Mame do you know it?
Keigo: Mame what day is it?
Mame: Children's Day
Keigo: Ah it's not
It's close~
Takumi: Plus I guessed it right
Syoya: Yeah Takumi-kun did
Sho: Does Ruki know?
Ruki: Health(Kenkō) Memorial Day
Sho: Yes, correct
Ruki: OH REALLY?
Ruki: I DID IT!
Takumi: Eh? It's wrong
Ren: It's a little different
Ruki: ?! Ah? He scored me kindly. Thank you
It's Constitution(kenpō) Memorial Day
Ruki: Ah, Constitution Memorial Day
Sho: Well, it was pretty much correct
Takumi: 'Pretty much correct'?!? It was completely wrong
Sho: Because of the coffee thing
Ruki: I was the most shocked. Getting it right from randomly saying something
Keigo: By the way, do you know what day it is tomorrow?
Ren: Tomorrow?
Keigo: Tomorrow
Junki: We know that, right?
Ruki: Keigo, do you know?
Keigo: Well that's why I asked
Ruki: You know hence you gave the question, right?
Ruki: Shion?
Keigo: Then can I ask? Syoya what is it?
Syoya: Then, Greenery Day
Keigo: It's wrong
Syoya: It's wrong?
Ruki: Shion, Shion
Shion: Huh?
Keigo: Shosei
Sho: What day is it, Shosei?
Shosei: Ohira Shosei Day
You just wanted to do that
Sho: By the way, Syoya you were right
Syoya: Really? Is it really correct?
Sho: Greenery Day
Keigo: No it's not?!
Ruki: The ones who got it right get shocked
Junki: It's Greenery
Keigo: It's not
Sho: It's Greenery
Keigo: Ah, really?
Sho: Yes
Takumi: He asked though he didn't know
Ruki: By the way who wrote the 'see you later' on twitter?
Ruki: Who wrote the 'see you later'?
Junki: That's me
Ruki: Ah, is that so
Junki: Yes
Ruki: Heh~
Ren: xD 'heh~'
Syoya: No interest!
Sho: That was a little sad
Ruki: Everyone was curious
Ruki: And this is what it is, that kind of 'heh~'
Sho: Couldn't you be a little more...
Ruki: A 'thank you for answering' kind of 'heh~'
Junki: It was halfhearted
Ruki: Sorry about that. Sorry if I made you feel that way
Ruki: My shyness came out
Sho: It wouldn't anymore!
Mame: Why would your shyness come out now
Shion: There are many interesting comments
Ruki: There are
Sukai: Everyone is writing pretty seriously
Ren: There's an interesting comment about Junki
Sho: What is it?
Keigo: Go ahead
Ren: I think this question has good sense
Ren: 'JO1's BRAIN Junki-kun'
Junki: Yes! It has come
Ren: What is a Japanese word you learnt recently?
[I think this is often asked to K-pop idols learning Japanese]
Shion: How you think of this is important
Ren: This pressure!
Shosei: Tsurubo's word...
Shion: How will you think of this?
Shion: By the way, you can't escape
Takumi: Scary!
Shosei: We're marking you with all our might
Sho: As time passes, your (?) reduces
Ruki: The Ogiri* brothers are watching
[*Some sort of entertainment style]
Sho: Ogiri brothers!
Junki: Okay
Ask the question once more
Keigo: Kono Junki, What is the Japanese word you learnt recently?
Junki: Okinotori Island
Ren: I like it though
Shion: Is that recent?
Junki: Recently...that's right
Keigo: Rather than a word it's...well it is a word, I guess
Shion: I know
Ruki: It seems there's a Japanese he learnt recently
Really? What is it?
Keigo: Tsurubo Shion, What is the Japanese word you learnt recently?
Shion: Toilet bowl
Sho: Why are you clapping!
Junki: This is weird...this is weird!
Shosei: It was good
Keigo: Ohira Shosei, What is the Japanese word you learnt recently?
Shosei: Weather
Shion: I like this
Junki: This is good
Ren: None of the staff are laughing
Keigo: It's ZERO
Shosei: I'm sorry
Junki: Because JAM are kind
Junki: I believe that they are laughing
Ren: It says 'I can't stop smiling in the train'
Sho: They're watching in the train?
Ren: They're watching in the train
Keigo: Because it's Shosei Day, right?
Takumi: The comments are so fast
Sho: The comments are so fast I can't read it
Sho: Even if I try to stop it, it moves on its own
Junki: Today's TMI
What is TMI?
Junki: It's really...(mispronounces)
(making fun)
Junki: Not a big thing, that happened to yourself
Keigo: That happened recently
Ren: To yourself
Junki: A really tiny news
Syoya: Ah yes
Sho: Yes
Syoya: I had a meal from the Kono family
Junki: That's right
Why? When?
Junki: Right now my dad & mom are at my house
Junki: Then they happened to ask me 'call Kimata-kun over'
Shosei: Invite us too!
Keigo: They came to Japan to play?
They are from Japan in the first place
Keigo: They're travelling within Japan
Junki: That's right
Syoya: It was yummy
Junki: It was yummy
What did you eat?
Syoya: Hamburger
That's nice!
Invite us
Keigo: The most homely taste
Syoya: And miso soup
Ren: There's 9 more days, can we make it?
Junki: Everyone, please come
Sho: You're inviting us 2-on-1?
Ruki: 'Please come' you say, but it's tough on your parents!
Keigo: They can't cook that much
Sho: They're probably watching now
Junki: Right, they're probably watching
Takumi: Plus it was quite big
Syoya: Ah, it was big
Syoya: I could taste the homely-ness
Keigo: Who else has a tiny news?
Shosei: Mame-chan?
Tiny news
Sho: Just now, Syoya, was that tiny?
Junki: That's a little bigger
Syoya: It may be a bit big
Sho: That is considered big, huh...what is it
Keigo: Something a little smaller
Syoya: It should be from today
Today?
No, just recently
Junki: Recently is fine too
Sukai: I have something
Please, what is it?
Sukai: I just noticed it today
Ruki: Really?
Sukai: My contacts...eh?
Sukai: I lost my contact lenses
Sukai: And I'm wondering how I'll go about tomorrow
Sukai: This is quite serious, I was discussing with our manager Naoto-san earlier
Sukai: 'What should I do?'
Keigo: That's a big news
Big news
Keigo: Something smaller
Sho: Small?
Syoya: Your contact lenses
Syoya: I see...
Sho: Something happened to Syoya
Syoya: I was thinking it's difficult
Sukai: Is there anything, everyone?
Shosei: We would like to know instead
Sho: Tiny information?
Sho: Isn't it that? From 18:00 is With Us MV release
Hey! That's a big news!
Junki: Don't say that as a TMI
Ren: That's too light! Say it properly!
Junki: A little more...what time is it?
Sho: It's :43 now
Just a little bit more
Ruki: Sho-kun did you have a TMI?
Sho: Something small, right?
Ruki: Really small
Sho: Wait I'll try to remember, please connect (the
conversation)
Ruki: Can it be really small?
Sho: We wouldn't remember something small
Junki: Really small
Syoya: Unexpectedly I think about it
Sho: Unexpectedly you think about it...what is small?
Junki: Like it will definitely happen today
Sho: It will definitely happen today...
Junki: It should
Sho: It should...
Keigo: But it's true we may forget because it's so small
Shosei: Eh? Something that happened? Not something that made us happy?
Ren: Whatever is fine
Shosei: Whatever is fine?
Sukai: Any kind of news
Keigo: It's not really small, but I'll connect it (to Sho)
Ren: 'I'll connect it~'
Keigo: LET ME SPEAK
Sukai: He's connecting the conversation
Keigo: Enough about the connecting, let me speak
Sukai: Sho-kun please think of something, because it'll connect
keigo: And if you already remember, please say it
Keigo: Yesterday I slept at 21:30 for the first time in a long while
Shosei: That's early
Keigo: And I slept until about 12:00
Ren : Oh, 12 noon?
Keigo: I slept for so many hours
Shion: About 14
Keigo: I was shocked, myself
Sukai: Without waking up?
Keigo: Without waking up
Wow
Keigo: I think it's the first time I slept this long
keigo: What's with that
Ruki: I thought you must be so tired, and got a good rest
Keigo: The way he's listening...
He's messing around
Ruki: I'm not messing around
Ruki: I was listening properly
Ruki: Probably most aren't even listening to Keigo's story
Keigo: It's real. Does anyone have this?
Ruki: Sleeping this long?
Keigo: Yeah
No. Not recently
Keigo: When I woke up I opened my eyes
Keigo: I couldn't see anything
Keigo: It was full of eye gunk
Sukai: Don't say such things!
Shosei: It's a joke
Keigo: I slept too much...
Keigo: For real!
Ruki: Umm...Can we have the person on the right answer soon
Shosei: It's hard to talk after you raised it to this level
Sho: I'm really sorry, I have nothing
Sho: It's too interesting here, I ended up like this
Ruki: You ended up listening
Sho: I did
Sho: Shall we do screenshot time now?
Syoya: We can do screenshot time from here
That side?
Syoya: Everyone, make yourself seen
Keigo: KP
Sho: What is KP?
Kanpai (cheers)
Syoya: It's screenshot time
Junki: Thank you
Syoya: Ok! Did you take a lot?
Sho: Did you take a lot?
Shosei: Yes!
Keigo: Is it free talk now?
Sho: Well yes there's-
Keigo: Okay so recently
Keigo: It's a really small talk
Keigo: Umm...what was it...uh...
Keigo: When I'm doing something, I make a sound
Keigo: I think during shooting I talked to Ren-kun & Takumi about it
Keigo: What did I say? When I do something...
Sho: What do you mean?
Sho: Remember it
Sho: When you do something
Ren: Right...for me...
Keigo: This is really funny
Takumi: For example, like (sound effect)
Keigo: Like when you do this, and you make a sound
Keigo: It's a little embarrassing
Sho: You do it subconsciously
Keigo: Like (sound) comes out
Keigo: There's someone who makes a unique one
Ren: When I come out of the bath and dry my hair
Ren: I don't do it like this, but like this
Oh I get it. Facing down
Ren: I'm the type who looks down and does it
Ren: At that time, I rub it like this so
(Ren noises)
Keigo: He makes a sound
Ren: Really...when I was in middle school...my mom was like...
Ren: 'Why do you always make a sound?'
Ren: She told me. Before that I never noticed
Ren: After that I became aware that I was saying it
Ren: No, someone definitely says it too
No we don't
Junki: I can't this is too funny
Keigo: I laughed a lot when we talked about it
Takumi: We were like 'EHH?' right?
Sho: What about Keigo?
Keigo: Mine was funny too
Ren: What was it
Keigo: Right, I forgot
Ren: Yet you brought it up
Shosei: You don't know but you said it
Keigo: Mine is funny too. When it's funny it comes out
Sho: Like when you sleep?
Keigo: No that's sleep talking
Shion: That's famous
Keigo: Sleep talk is funny
Sho: Do you think you can recall?
Keigo: Impossible
Sho: Impossible, huh
Ren: If you can recall it
Sho: If you remember it before this ends
Keigo: Until the end
Sho: With that, the fun talk is coming to an end
Sho: With Us MV will be released on JO1 official YouTube Channel at 18:00 via premiere
Please watch it!
Ren: It's premiering now
AHHHHH
Shion: Oh no oh no
Sukai: It spilled
IT SPILLED
BYE BYE
Sukai: Tissue
Sho: Keigo's face...
Sho: He can't recall
Keigo did you recall something?
Shosei: Nothing!
Keigo: I remember!
-END-